Chapter 382

Kennel (3)

◆

BDISSEM. She revealed her true form in the thick salt water.

“Hohoho- surprise.”

She winked at Vikir with a smirk, her rosy cheeks gone from the corners of her mouth.

What took her place was a flower in full bloom.

Vikir exclaimed in pure amazement.

“...A seaweed-based Ent? I didn't realize such a thing existed.”

He has heard many tales of forest-dwelling Ents during his time living in the jungle of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

So naturally, he had the preconceived notion that they only lived in forests.

However, they also live in seaweed forests deep beneath the ocean floor.

Just as the Beastman descended from various animal families, the Ent descended from various plant families, and in the case of BDISSEM, she was descended from the seaweed family of kelp and wakame.

“Hmmm. This isn't going as well as I thought.”

Dragging BDISSEM into the water was proved to be a deadly move, as it grabbed Vikir's ankle.

Ordinary plants would have their leaves burned to a crisp by the salt, but seaweed actually revitalizes itself.

...Pow!

Vikir kicked out the flying chains of seaweed.

The rounded, hard spikes on the seaweed felt like they were kicked by a bowling ball full force.

'...This is troublesome.'

Vikir brushed off the leaves that clung to his arms and tried to rise to the surface.

But BDISSEM wouldn't let him escape the water.

“Hoho- where do you think you're going, you've only just come in, why don't you play some more~”

Chewy stalks of seaweed swooped in like sea serpents.

Kiriririk-

The black seaweed that sprouted from the bottom of the gulper eel farm moved like BDISSEM's limbs and grabbed Vikir's ankles.

Chararararak- Kwak...

Above it, the long, giant leaves of the seaweed grew diagonally and horizontally, forming a grid-like encirclement.

Snake net, fishing net, square net, gill net, drift net, cast net, drag net, trawl net....All kinds of nets were spread out targeting just one Vikir.

They were terrifying restraints, designed not only to trap but to imprison.

Spears of dried seaweed with pointed tips pierced the immobilized Vikir's body.

Bind him with nets, impale him with spears, and drain his mana and strength once they're in contact.

It was a must-win pattern that turned BDISSEM into an invincible monster.

Puff-puff-puck!

Blood, flesh, and guts exploded like firecrackers. The water instantly turned black.

“...Hmm.”

But BDISSEM narrowed her eyes, not liking the situation.

Countless spears of seaweed failed to reach Vikir in the end.

At a crucial moment, Vikir yanked the tail of a passing gulper eel and used it as a shield.

Peopeog! Peog! Peoeog!

The seaweed spears that followed were also blocked by the gulper eels that Vikir was pulling, causing a series of misfires.

“Ugh! It takes me years to grow one of these gulper eels! If D'Ordume and Souaré find out, there will be an uproar!”

Bubbles began to boil from the angry BDISSEM's entire body.

Bubbling, bubbling, bubbling...

True to its form, the plant was pumping out tons of oxygen from its body.

Seeing this, Vikir nodded.

'I see why everyone was so overprotective of her.'

In addition to crafting the BDISSEM restraints that bind prisoners' mana and power, BDISSEM has a very important role.

She provides oxygen to the prison.

In addition to her ability to block mana and physical force, she has the uncanny ability to eat things like sulfur and toxic vapors and turn them into oxygen.

So without BDISSEM, there is no Nouvelle Vague.

There's nowhere else to get oxygen from inside the fluffy dome of mucus.

'I like you even more now. You'll be useful in many ways.'

Vikir dropped the gulper eel he was using as a shield and climbed onto the next one.

Boom!

A spear of seaweed swooped down from below, piercing both the upper and lower jaws of gulper eel.

...Thud!

Vikir threw off the gulper eel and landed on the bottom of the tank.

“Hohohoho~ You're going deeper, that is suicidal.”

BDISSEM had spread out long strands of seaweed like a net, blocking his path to the surface.

Now Vikir was trapped at the bottom of the pool, unable to move.

Getting out was one thing, but breathing was the immediate problem.

But.

Shrrrrrrrr.

Even at an overwhelmingly vantage point, BDISSEM could not help but cringe at the strange phenomenon taking place in Vikir's right hand.

A stream of water flowing in a strange direction. It was slowly being sucked towards Vikir's right hand.

'What is it? Is there a hole over there?'

Unless there was a leak, there was no reason for the water to be flowing that way.

Suddenly, BDISSEM realized that something was wrong.

Kurrrrrr!

The strength of the current suddenly increased.

It's as if there was a leak somewhere, and the water was being sucked in at a tremendous speed.

Not only the seaweed around him, but also BDISSEM was almost dragged away by the current.

“What, what!”

An ominous foreboding flashed through her mind.

She realized she shouldn't be caught in Vikir's outstretched right hand. Her instinct screamed a desperate warning.

'Starvation drought.'

A trait possessed by the Blood Tree Daylily. The power to dry out anything with moisture.

Vikir was going to dry up all the moisture in the pool.

And as the water dried up and disappeared, the empty space was filled with new water, which dried up and disappeared again, creating a turbulent current.

Vikir emitted aura through Beelzebub.

Like a flame that travels forward through pouring oil, Vikir's aura shot forward through the swirling water currents.

The target was, of course, BDISSEM.

“Huh!”

BDISSEM was stunned by the eight flying teeth that split the water-filled space.

Black Sun. A small but dense and heavy black sun was rising at the bottom of the sea.

Kurrrrrr!

The black sun grew in size with an incredible speed, sucking in everything around it.

This black sheep, which was essentially Vikir's special move, was destructive, but it didn't have the power to pull in anything around it.

However, the fact that it was underwater, and that Vikir knew how to use the power of the Blood Daylily's Starvation Drought, made it work.

'That guy! He was aiming for this in the first place, trying to get underwater...!'

BDISSEM realized that she was completely caught up in Vikir's plan.

The black orb was a collection of countless teeth, and she knew what would happen to her if she was dragged into its center.

Her entire body would be disintegrated, leaving not even a scrap of flesh behind.

“Kkyaaaaaghhhh!”

BDISSEM struggled to break free of the current somehow.

She pulled up all the available seaweed and shot it out, but all of it was sucked into the center of the black sun and turned into fuel for the fire.

The seaweed was torn to shreds and pulverized, and not even a leaf could be salvaged.

Strangely enough, the aura emitted by that monster-like thing did not fade even when it touched BDISSEM's seaweed.

If the people of Nouvelle Vague saw BDISSEM's seaweed, which nullifies all mana and physical power, being torn apart so helplessly, like a cheap piece of paper, they would probably be horrified.

But it wasn't all for nothing.

Kuleuleuleug... kuleug! Kkuleuleug!

As a large amount of water plants were hit by the black sun, the water flow became a little looser.

BDISSEM managed to break free from the current and rise to the surface.

“Puh-ha!”

After breaking the surface, BDISSEM looked back with a white face.

“Okay, I need to get out of here quickly, I have to tell D'Ordume and Souaré about this....”

But... she hadn't taken more than seven steps before she felt her body shake.

“...?”

Her vision spun. She'd thought she'd taken a straight path, but somehow her foot had twisted.

...Thud!

BDISSEM fell to the ground.

'?'

'Why?

'Why am I like this?'

'Why won't my body listen to me?'

'What's going to happen to me now?'

'What's going on?'

'Quick, I need to get away now...'

Unanswered questions only filled her head.

And then.

Chwaag-

Vikir broke the surface of the water and climbed out.

“You drink a lot of water for a seaweed.”

Vikir spoke in a dry voice to BDISSEM, his fingertips dripping with black blood.

Madame's poison.

Vikir had sneakily released his own blood into the water once, when BDISSEM had slaughtered the gulper eels, creating a spray of blood.

Afterwards, as a vortex was formed due to the water current, BDISSEM unknowingly inhaled a large amount of poison throughout its body.

The poison was diluted by the water, so the impact was delayed, but once the symptoms appeared, the outcome was obvious.

“...Heog! Heoeog! Keog!”

BDISSEM crawled on the ground with one hand on her throat and the other on her chest.

Syuuuuug-

Her body temperature rose rapidly due to the poison, and water evaporated from her body.

Dark spots, the marks of death, began to appear all over her body.

BDISSEM, who had changed from a girl to an adult woman, was now turning into a shriveled up old woman.

“Oh, no, no, no... if I die... the restraints and cages of the prisoners... will all lose their strength... that... that....”

And her forward in agony.

Jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog-

Night Hound, or rather of the Nouvelle Vague Hound, began to take steps.

Even in the deep sea, where not a single light shines, the shadow of death seemed to be cast.

Chapter 383

The Rotten Dog of Nouvelle Vague (1)

◆

Early the next morning.

There was an unprecedented uproar in Nouvelle Vague.

“WHAT THE HELL !”

A thunderous shout shook Level 9.

Colonel D'Ordume D D'Orcdile. One of the leading candidates to become the next head of the prison.

He turned his head, his expression filled with rage.

A group of mid-level officers, including Lieutenant Colonel Bastille, stood behind him, heads bowed.

It was because of the escape of Night Hound in the middle of the night.

Colonel D'Ordume had frantically scoured his men after reports of Vikir's disappearance.

But nothing had been reported, except that a mysterious doctor had slipped out of the prisoners' quarters under the guise of quarantine.

Colonel D'Ordume was barely able to contain his anger as he realized that the reason why the siege was so weak in the first place was due to the mysterious explosives found in the Level 10 sector, and Colonel D'Ordume's unreasonable orders to reassign the guards in order to force the construction work around them.

“There was nothing unusual about the night before, how couldn't anyone notice until it came to this?”

At Colonel D'Ordume's accusation, the guards all lowered their heads and remained speechless.

Then. A dispatch came in.

“Sir Colonel, I think you should go to the fifth floor!”

D'Ordume's thick eyebrows arched at the report from his out-of-breath subordinate.

The next thing he knew, he was running up the stairs to the fifth floor.

“What the hell....”

The first thing he sees is a giant hole in the wall of the Gulper Eel tank.

The next thing he saw was a large number of dead gulper eels floating in the water.

He couldn't even begin to estimate how many eels had been swept out of the water.

Luckily, the flubber mucus filled in the holes, so the flooding wasn't too bad, but the loss of so many gulper eels was devastating.

It is very difficult to raise gulper eels, and even in the process of becoming an adult, sudden or mysterious deaths occur frequently.

Their growth rate is also extremely fast.

An adult gulper eel could cost as much as a ship, and the loss of such a creature was unspeakable.

...However, Colonel D'Ordume's focus was elsewhere.

Gulper eels were nowhere in sight.

The problem was the little girl squatting in the corner of the tank, shivering.

Wrapped in a towel from the guards, drinking warm sea cow, she was BDISSEM!

“ ... What's going on?”

D'Ordume asked in disbelief.

BDISSEM snorted and answered.

“I was trying to catch an escaped prisoner last night and lost him.”

“No, I don't know why you're here in the first place... haa.”

D'Ordume sighed, pressing a hand to his forehead.

Just then, a figure approached him.

“What are you doing here? You have been slow.”

Colonel Souaré. She eyed him with a sneer.

“Is that how you're going to became head of the warden?”

“Shut up, Souaré. I was off duty last night, a once-in-a-year occurrence.”

“Aha- so you were out of the loop while I dealt with the flood damage, the gulper eel deaths, and BDISSEM's security?”

“....”

D'Ordume didn't answer.

He merely grinded his teeth with such force that they seemed to wear down.

Souaré looked around.

“Thank goodness Brigadier General Flubber took care of that hole in the wall. There's some flooding damage, but it's nothing that can't be repaired with the labor of Level 1 prisoners. The loss of the gulper eels is a pity, but so be it. We'll just have to be satisfied that BDISSEM is safe. We could have had a major accident of epic proportions.”

“...Where are the prisoner?”

“Why are you asking me that? It's not even my jurisdiction. I'm just cleaning up the damage.”

He's right.

It was D'Ordume's job to capture the prisoner, and Souaré's job to torture them and keep them in solitary confinement.

D'Ordume couldn't help but ask the trembling BDISSEM.

“Where are the prisoner?”

Then BDISSEM jumped, more startled than necessary, and cried out.

“He's dead!”

“...Dead?”

D'Ordume was silent for a moment.

There was no way anyone could have escaped from Nouvelle Vague.

With no mana, limited strength, and a body weakened by poor diet and harsh labor, it would be impossible to escape from this harsh environment while wearing the BDISSEM restraints.

On top of that, this is 10,000 meters below the surface of the sea.

But the job had to be done.

“Then where is the body?”

D'Ordume asked in a hard tone, and BDISSEM quickly averted her gaze.

“...He went out to sea on a gulper eel.”

“Then he's not dead.”

“Of course he's dead!”

BDISSEM had a point.

In fact, there was no way to get to the surface on a gulper eel.

It was a military secret that only the wardens knew, a secret that the prisoners would never know.

The fifth floor of the Nouvelle Vague, where the gulper eels are kept, is surrounded by more than 3,000 circulating currents, of which only one leads to the surface.

This means that it's all about which point you push the eels to, and without knowing the exact path, there's only a 0.00033101622% chance of reaching the surface if you choose a random path.

The rest of the time, the gulper eel is left to wander in circles in the depths of the sea at the mercy of the currents, returning to where it came from, a journey that can take as long as a hundred years, and by the time the gulper returns, the person in its stomach is reduced to a skeleton.

“He doesn't seem to have any idea what the circulation currents are that lead to the surface, so he's bound to get caught in a trap current, and he'll be stuck in the deep for the rest of his life.”

“ ... Maybe? It sounds like you didn't see it.”

“Yes, yes, yes, I saw it, Haa, I saw it, and I saw him ride a gulper eel out of that hole in the wall before I passed out!”

BDISSEM desperately answered.

D'Ordume crossed his arms and was silent for a long moment.

“ ...You did indeed witness his last act, didn't you?”

“Oh, that's right! What are you looking at me for? And no matter what, I'm the one who cares... don't look at me like that!”

BDISSEM broke out in a cold sweat.

Because she was lying now.

'I can't tell you that I passed out and then woke up and he was gone!'

If she did, it wouldn't be just another day in captivity.

When Warden Orca returned, she might be locked up as a prisoner for life.

“Yeah. There was a hole in the wall! He tried to drag an eel out. He probably took the eel with him, and he's probably wandering around somewhere in a daze right now. Fucking asshole!”

BDISSEM rationalized herself. She said it was something that could not be helped.

And Souaré 's testimony coincidentally backed up BDISSEM's words.

“Come to think of it, the guy who came into the cell this time said something strange, the one on level eight, the guy Sakkuth or something, he said that the Night Hound was about to break out?”

“Sakkuth? The plague leper?”

“Yep. He said some guy named Vikir tipped him off about the escape. I thought it was bullshit and ignored it, but he was right.”

The testimony of Sakkuth De Leviathan, who is currently in solitary confinement for his role in a recent riot, was pretty conclusive.

BDISSEM was eventually cleared of the charge of missing an inmate.

“Hey, that's it, I'm going back to my room.”

Fearful of being reprimanded by the warden and belittled by subordinates, BDISSEM decided not to dwell on the matter and kept her mouth shut.

D'Ordume felt suspicious in many ways, but decided he could not pursue the investigation further.

A hole in the wall. The missing gulper eel. BDISSEM's unwavering testimony.

In the end, D'Ordume could only nod.

“Night Hound died trying to break out of Nouvelle Vague. I suppose we can treat it that way.”

“Well, I agree, it's a shame, he was quite charming.”

Even Souaré nodded in agreement.

D'Ordume found Vikir's name in the list he was carrying and scribbled it down.

<Night Hound 'Vikir Van Baskerville'>

With that, Night Hound was officially declared dead in Nouvelle Vague.

“Send a mana transmission to the surface and have it recorded.”

D'Ordume roughly tossed the register with Vikir's name crossed out to one of the junior guards beside him.

“Yes, sir. Colonel.”

The junior guard bowed his head deeply and took the list with both hands.

He turned and walked away to fulfill D'Ordume's orders.

Souaré caught a glimpse of the junior guard's sideways glance as he walked past her.

He wore a tattered guard's cap, unkempt bushy hair, and a large burn scar across his face.

And a crisp uniform that looked brand new.

The name tag on his chest patch, which looked like it had been freshly inlaid, read 'Garam Nord'.

'The atmosphere is strange? Was there a guy like that among your subordinates?'

Souaré shook off the thought.

'Eh, what the hell.'

She was a colonel and the next head of the prison, there was no way she could remember the names and faces of such a lowlife.

Right now, it was more important to Souaré to make up for the mistake Static D'Ordume had made and put on as much color as she could.

“Anyway. Let's wrap this up. I'll take a look upstairs.”

“....”

D'Ordume merely puffed away at his cigar.

The Nouvelle Vague prison break, which could have been an unprecedented event in history, ended somewhat in vain like this.

Chapter 385

The Rotten Dog of Nouvelle Vague (3)

◆

“You bastards! You want me to eat this? Are you crazy!?”

“How can anyone work in a place like this!”

“At least give us a break!”

“When are we going to see our families?”

“Prisoners are people! They have human rights!”

A group of prisoners on the first floor of Level 1 was making a ruckus.

They were Nouvelle Vague's newest arrival, overnight pups who hadn't yet adjusted to the ecosystem in the midst of the chaos.

“By the way, did you hear, there was an escape yesterday?”

“Nouvelle Vague is surprisingly not that special.”

“The guards are showing up for duty, and it looks like it's full of holes.”

“They must be weak. Maybe I should try to break out.”

They were low-level prisoners that the guards were too busy to pay attention to, so they were lucky to be located in the blind spot of the military discipline, so they hadn't yet grasped the atmosphere.

Then.

Jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog-

The sound of military footsteps was loud and clear.

Prisoners at Level 1 could be organized by the hands of lower-ranked guards.

The guards, so-called lieutenants, lined up against the Level 1 prisoners.

Each had a club, sword, whip, or axe in their hands.

“...What, what are these deadly weapons?”

“Are you trying to kill us?”

“Are you crazy, you're going to swing those things at us in handcuffs?”

“You guys are out of your mind....”

The prisoners seemed to cower at the mere sight of the guards' weapons.

That's what you get for being a bunch of little chicks.

The major-ranked guard at the front spoke to the second lieutenant and lieutenant-ranked guards at the back.

“Listen carefully, the most riotous floor in the Nouvelle Vague is surprisingly Level 1, or Level 2.”

You know what you see. It's an eternal truth.

In Nouvelle Vague, lower-level prisoners tend to riot more and higher-level prisoners tend to riot less.

This is because the higher-level prisoners feel the horrors of the place more deeply and live to tell the tale, while the lower-level prisoners think that they can be more fearless because they have no eyes to see.

“Especially those on Level 1, they don't know what to expect. Especially the ones who are newer and less socialized, they will start riots, saying it's a human right, an organized protest, or profanity.”

The lower-ranking guards listened calmly as their boss spoke.

The major smirked and continued.

“And we secretly condone, even encourage, riots on the lower levels, like Level 1 and Level 2. Sometimes, it is created artificially using planted insider. Although today was a spontaneous riot, it's all for your practical experience.”

The Major's words had a strange nuance to them.

It was a tone that simultaneously instilled confidence in the junior guards and intimidated the prisoners.

The prisoners stopped shouting and looked at each other, wondering if what they had done was actually the guards' evil plan.

By the time they realized that there is a insider hiding inside, their cohesion had already broken down.

In the midst of it all, the Major drives a wedge.

“These are Level 1 prisoners, but they're criminals who made a name for themselves on the ground, strong men who survived the transport to Nouvelle Vague and the entry process. They may be wearing BDISSEM handcuffs, but don't let your guard down! Do you understand?”

“Yes!”

The junior guards shouted in unison.

And with that, the bloody suppression began.

It was a common thing in Nouvelle Vague.

◆

Blood and gore sprayed into the air.

The guards trampled and beat the prisoners senselessly with maces and clubs.

Even if they were low-level guards, they could easily surpass the level of the prisoners on Level 1 wearing the BDISSEM restraints.

“Hic! This is human rights abuse!”

“Human rights? Why are you looking for them 10,000 meters below the surface?”

One of the guards crushed the wailing prisoner's face with a military boot.

Lieutenant Kirko. She raised her head without even wiping the blood splattered on her face.

Her cold, piercing gaze swept over the criminals.

“There is no such thing as human rights for you, you unredeemable scum. No human rights for you dark-haired beasts, parasitising on the social system that ordinary citizens have worked so hard to build, and threatening their very safety.”

Under Kirko's gaze, the prisoners shrank like squid tossed over a flame.

Just then.

Peoeog-

A chain slammed into Kirko's back from behind.

A Level 1 prisoner in BDISSEM handcuffs and restraints glared at Kirko with bloodshot eyes.

X

A man with an impressive cross-shaped scar on his forehead.

“Hohoho- you know who I am, don't you?”

He said confidently.

But Kirko only frowned as she touched her throbbing back.

“No. I have no idea.”

“What, you don't know me?”

He gritted his teeth together, and then exclaimed.

“I'm Attendance Number 8... No, I'm Pal Euspear, the 'Monster of the Crossroads'!”

He was Pal Euspear, a prisoner who had been recently brought to Level 1.

If there was one thing that setted him apart from the other prisoners, it's that he used to be a prestigious academy student.

He was a student at the Colosseo Academy, one of the best institutions in the empire, but at some point he fell into a life of crime and had been imprisoned here in Nouvelle Vague ever since.

'Damn it. I messed with two high-ranking nobles inside the Hell Tree and got punished outside of it... Who knew the Hell Tree would disappear so suddenly?'

He had been trapped inside the Hell Tree that had suddenly appeared in the Colosseo Academy.

He'd gotten off to a lucky start as all the old powers and hierarchies were reorganized, and with the stats and items he'd gained, he'd been able to take on the high-ranking children he'd never dared to look at before.

Especially Dolores. Euspear, who had been targeting her, had been building his notoriety by harming countless classmates, until suddenly the Hell Tree was gone and he was back in his original world.

“Damn it. I thought the Hell Tree would last forever....”

Naturally, the many people who had been victimized by him in the tower never forgot that debt and repaid it.

After being expelled from school, Euspear fell into a life of crime and eventually ended up imprisoned here in Nouvelle Vague.

However, he had a decent amount of stats from his time in the Hell Tree, so he didn't suffer too much of a loss in combat while wearing the BDISSEM restraints.

“Die, bitch!”

Euspear wrapped the chain around Kirko's neck, slipping it between the cuffs on each wrist.

“Keugh!?”

Kirko momentarily lost her grip on the longsword in her hand.

Kirko hadn't expected a prisoner with this much strength on Level 1.

This guy should have been at least level 2, and at most level 3.

He must have been hiding his power all this time.

“...!”

Kirko gritted her teeth and spun around.

But Euspear was determined, locking on to her and holding her down.

Rolling on the floor like that in the chaos of so many prisoners and guards, she would be out of sight in an instant.

Even now, there wasn't a single guard around to help Kirko.

“Hehe- were there women like this in Nouvelle Vague? I'd like to unpack some of the things that have accumulated for the first time in a while.”

Euspear looked down at Kirko and licked his lips.

Kirko squeezed her eyes shut.

In all of her years as a guard at Nouvelle Vague, she'd always been prepared for the day when she'd have to face the harsh things.

It had always been sharpened in her mind as she lay in bed, as she stood watch alone in the silence of her post, as she showered, as she ate her meals.

'Today is the day.'

The consequences of letting her guard down for a moment are frightening. Such is the life of a guard at Nouvelle Vague.

Whatever the future holds for her, Kirko is determined to accept and take it all in stride.

At that very moment, ...

Peoeog! Hududug- hududug- hudug-

Something hot splattered over Kirko's face.

“...?”

Kirko narrowed her eyes, not knowing what the sticky liquid that covered her face was

It was bright red blood.

Blood that had spurted from the Euspear's mouth as it rode over her body.

“...Ugg!? Eueub! Ugh!?”

Euspear was struggling with his head raised, looking very embarrassed.

That's because there was a thick, hard, and long stick that forced his mouth open and stuck deep into his throat.

A three-tiered baton.

It tore off Euspear's upper and lower lips, knocked out all of his front teeth behind them, and burrowed into his esophagus.

No wonder all the flesh and uvula in his mouth was crushed in the process.

“Eueub! Ub! Eoeogh! Gueogh!”

Euspear struggled to spit out the baton that had been forced into his mouth, but it was impossible.

The hand holding the baton had a tremendous amount of force and weight behind it.

“ ...Are you okay?”

The man with the three-tiered baton asked Kirko in a bland voice.

He was a man she knew well.

Garam Nord.

Age twenty-one. Rank: Second Lieutenant. A junior guard in the Nouvelle Vague and Kirko's ally.

Garam was looking at Kirko with an expressionless face.

Ssuug-

A three-tiered baton slipped out of Euspear's mouth.

“Ewwgh! Gweeeeeegh! ...kuhugh!”

As the three-tiered baton, which had been almost all the way into his stomach, was pulled out, Euspear vomited blood, tears, snot, and sweat.

Ppeoeog- jjeog!

He was immediately knocked out by the stomp of a military boot on the back of his head.

“...You?”

Kirko stuttered and opened her mouth.

'I never thought I'd see the day when I'd get help from Garam, who used to be called 'Stupid Garam' and 'Rotten Dog'.

'No, isn't this the second time?'

Kirko had unwittingly accepted help from him before during a previous riot.

But it felt a little different back then.

Then.

“Haa!?”

Kirko realized that now was not the time to be lost in thought.

She was in the middle of a battle, a prisoner riot in full swing.

So Kirko shouted in panic.

“This is no time for this, Garam! What happened to your sector and why did you come here? You need to subdue the prisoners in your sector before you help me...!”

But she couldn't finish her sentence.

For Garam opened his mouth to answer her briefly.

“Does not exist anymore.”

“...What?”

For a moment, Kirko doubted her ears.

But it soon turned out that her performing ears had done their job well.

Garam's three-tiered baton, bent into an L shape and dripping blood.

Behind him, more than a dozen prisoners were laying dead and writhing in a pool of blood.

“No more prisoners to suppress.”

The short, echoing words of Garam were enough to stun not only Kirko, but also the others who had just rushed up behind him.

Chapter 386

The Rotten Dog of Nouvelle Vague (4)

◆

“....”

Kirko looked up, a puzzled expression on her face.

Normally, Garam would have been embarrassed and averted his gaze, but somehow he didn't care that Kirko was looking up at him.

But that was to be expected.

Garam was Vikir in disguise.

An escaped prisoner who became a guard overnight. Vikir was now standing here in the shoes of the dead Garam.

“Stay back, it's dangerous.”

Vikir's words were not spoken for Kirko's sake, but to honor what he had learned from the diary.

-I want to show her the outside world.

-If I could just once show her the blue skies and salt-free lakes and wild animals running through the fields where I was born...

His wishes were now forever unfulfilled.

Vikir knew the wishes that Garam had left behind in his palm-sized diary, pressed tightly against the old, damp note so as not to smudge it.

And at the same time, he knew it was impossible.

Garam was already dead and gone.

'However... I can help this woman you wanted so badly to protect to the end, to get out of this place.'

As far as Vikir could see, Kirko had immense talent and potential, and could make a great contribution to the human race when she grew up.

So Vikir decided to protect Kirko as much as possible.

To raise her as a secret weapon of the Alliance, a sword that could be used against demons in the future.

'In my previous life, she probably died namelessly somewhere, but... that will not be the case in this life.'

That would be the way to honor Garam's will. It was a win-win situation.

With that, Vikir picked up his three-tiered baton, which had bent from being swung too hard, and began beating the prisoners in front of him with it.

Ppeoeog! Ppeog! Kwagik-

The skulls and eyeballs of the prisoners who charged at Kirko exploded.

Many had their teeth knocked out and their tongues cut out.

Suddenly, Vikir's attention was drawn to the face of a prisoner sprawled on the floor.

X

Seeing it, Vikir nodded.

'Hmm? It's been a while since I've seen him.'

There was no way he could not remember the mark he had once carved.

'Was your name Pal Euspear?'

They had crossed paths a few times during their time at the Colosseo Academy.

Vikir remembered the face and the name, having fought with him when he was in his dog form, starting with the time he'd scolded him for bullying Pigi when he was a new student.

'I heard you were punished for causing a ruckus in the Hell Tree.'

Although he was struggling outside the Tower, inside the Tower he was acting viciously against his cool classmates and seems to have suffered harsh political retaliation.

Vikir knew that he had character problems, but he didn't expect to see him again at Nouvelle Vague.

'Well, at least it's nice to see a fellow classmate.'

Vikir kicked Euspear one more time in the stomach in a gesture of goodwill.

He could feel his intestines rupture under his toes, but he didn't care.

From then on, Vikir continued to swing the three-tiered baton.

At first, he didn't have time to control his strength, but now he's got the hang of it and was able to subdue his opponent in moderation.

A moderate suppression that would only break a few teeth and fingers or dislocate a limb.

Prisoners who fought back would have their toes crushed by the heels of military boots, rendering them unable to stand at all.

All of this was done as naturally as water.

Vikir moved like a shadow between the fiercely fighting guards and prisoners, swinging his three-tiered baton with ease.

Already more than a dozen prisoners were bleeding to death as Vikir's three-tiered baton slithered soundlessly between their sides and crotches.

The thing was, neither the fallen prisoners nor the guards who had knocked them down and were blinded by excitement, see who had subdued so many prisoners.

...But.

Just one person. There was one person who watched Vikir's actions from start to finish.

Kirko. She was watching Vikir's every move with a mesmerized gaze.

'What is that? Was Garam always that strong?'

She had never seen Garam seriously engaged in suppression before.

He was born so gentle and kind that he was incapable of causing harm to others.

Every time Kirko saw him, she thought to herself, 'He doesn't seem to be fit to be a guard'.

If that's the case, then why did he come all the way here and suffer such hardships, she couldn't understand or empathize with him.

Kirko even felt a little pathetic.

...But the Garam she saw with her naked eyes was completely different from the image she had of him before.

Had he awakened after Sakkuth's riot?

The way he was beating the prisoners with his expressionless face, it was like he was a veteran among veterans.

It was like watching a mad dog who had spent his life harming others.

The stealthy movements, the outbursts of violence, the swirling strength, the outstanding combat prowess... but nevertheless, the emotionless demeanor!

All these things made Kirko feel a shiver run down her spine.

If there was such a thing as a perfect prison guard in the world, wouldn't it probably look like that?

“Kughh!”

Kirko scrambled to her feet and gripped the handle of her sword tightly.

Her back and legs throbbed, but she couldn't afford to rest like this.

As long as she was an ace, she couldn't afford to lose to the Stupid Garam, Nouvelle Vague's Rotten Dog.

“Hwaaaap!”

She joined the fray, shouting in triumph, and followed closely behind Garam.

Once again, the bloodbath was raging.

◆

About twenty minutes later. The situation was completely under control.

The organizers of the riot were shackled in ever-larger and heavier BDISSEM handcuffs and led off to their cells, while the rest of the prisoners were thrown back into their cells in rags.

No medical treatment or meals, of course. Tomorrow, at 4am, the same labor will be imposed.

If they cannot endure it, they will die ...

The Major in charge of the suppression at the rear nodded with satisfaction.

“It was indeed a perfect suppression. We were a little overwhelmed by the madness of the prisoners in the beginning, but the second half was a game changer. Well done, boys!”

The Major was particularly salivating over the left wing of the suppression squad.

“The left wing, Group B, did a great job, and that's why we were able to make the early breakthrough so quickly. Who's in Group B?”

The major pushed his way through the bloodied and gasping junior guards to the area where the first prize of the day, Group B, was located.

And there in Group B stood Kirko.

The moment the major saw Kirko, he exclaimed.

“I knew it was you! You're even better than before! You cleared the prisoners on the left wing with such speed that the reinforcements were able to spread evenly to the right wing in time. Well done!”

At the Major's praise, all the lower ranking guards around Kirko looked at her with envious eyes.

But.

“...I didn't do it.”

Kirko shook her head, denying the fact.

“There's someone else who did. Over there....”

Kirko, who was about to look back at Garam, paused for a moment.

Garam was not where he was supposed to be standing.

Behind them, with the cleaning team, he was cleaning up blood and stone debris.

This was something that was usually done by guards whose achievements were so minimal that they were excluded from public affairs.

'No, why is he in there....'

Kirko was about to open her mouth in disbelief.

“Such humility to give credit to your colleagues! What an example to follow!”

The Major nodded his head, clearly convinced that Kirko was the hero of the day.

Meanwhile, the other junior guards behind Kirko had their say.

“It's you, Kirko. You always do well in every riot.”

“Well, this one was a bit of a riot, but you've beaten your own record, Kirko.”

“She's a genius. She's not in our league. She'll be a captain in three years at least.”

“That's true. Oh, and by the way, where the fuck did this asshole go?”

They soon started looking for an easy target for bullying.

Garam. Once again, the one behind the scenes.

The junior guards gave him a stern look.

“Hey, you didn't do anything this time, did you?”

“Didn't you catch another prisoner?”

“Anyway, I heard you were holding onto Kirko's ankles.”

“Wow, Kirko must be really good to be able to take on such an idiot.”

They began to giggle and throw punches at Garam.

Hitting him on the back, arms, and back of the head with their fists, stroking his hair, and so on.

...However, Garam's reaction was a little different than before.

“....”

After so many blows and so many swings, the three-tiered baton was bent.

The blood of the prisoners hadn't even dried yet, and it sliced through the lower abdomen of the junior guards in the blink of an eye.

Pug-pug-pug!

The sound of a hammer hitting a snail.

“Uh-hugh!”

“Kuagh!”

“Kuhughh!”

“Kehok!”

The four junior guards froze, clutching their stomachs.

“Hey, what is it?”

The Major turned his head to see Garam holding his stomach and supporting his four fallen comrades.

“It seems to be an acute stomach ache. I'm guessing it's from straining, so I'll take them to the infirmary....”

“Tsk tsk – I can't believe you're that nervous about this little riot. Fools.”

The Major quickly turned his attention away from the junior guards.

Garam turned to his comrades, who were laughing at him, and stalked off.

“Now, my friends. Let's forget about the past and discuss the future.”

His eyes were the same as they had been when he had subdued the prisoners earlier.

There was no hiding his power, no room for mercy.

And as she watched Garam's back, Kirko could only mutter quietly to himself.

“ ... As expected, something is strange.”

Chapter 388

The Worst Torture (1)

◆

Another few months have passed since then.

The anomaly in the monthly evaluation was not a single occurrence anymore, but had become the norm.

1st place. Task completion rate 114%.

1st place. Task completion rate 121%.

1st place. Task completion rate 136%.

1st place. Task completion rate 142%.

1st place. Task completion rate 155%.

1st place. Task completion rate 161%.

1st place. Task completion rate 178%.

1st place. Task completion rate 185%.

.

.

The other junior guards could only gape at his ever-increasing record of overachievement.

By then, nobody among the junior guards looked down on him.

It was natural to be treated as a colleague by them, and it was crowded with people who approached first because they wanted to hang out with him.

“Hey, Garam. You were first place this month too.”

“It seems like all of the prisoners in your charge are very disciplined.”

“What's your secret?”

“Let's play poker after dinner.”

The first ones to pretend to be friendly were surprisingly the first to be beaten by Garam.

After that, one by one, the number of guys who pretended to be friends increased.

But there were some who had always kept a certain distance.

Kirko was one of them.

“....”

She was always number one, but suddenly she was number two.

Ever since then, Kirko had been watching Garam.

As she ate her meal in silence, she thought back to the scene she'd seen of Garam at work a few months earlier.

'I can't believe he was doing that.'

It turns out that Garam's method of overachieving was actually quite simple.

Nothing much at first.

He beat the prisoners' vital parts with a triple baton, telling them not to be lazy.

Garam knew.

Like Santa Claus, who knew who was a good child and who was a bad child, Garam knew all too well which parts of the prisoners' bodies to hit to maximize the pain, but not interfere with their ability to perform their labor.

The three-tiered baton did not rest as if it was pounding meat for pork cutlet.

With each swing of the three-tiered baton, the prisoners, who had defied him, turned 180 degrees and acted as if they would jump into the fire at his command.

These prisoners, all of them known for their temper and strong-will on Level 1 or Level 2, were transformed into perfectly obedient workers after a month of working with Vikir, a.k.a. Garam.

Even the intelligent prisoners, who used to tease the guards not with strength but with brains, psychological warfare, and a sharp tongue, trembled at the sight of Garam.

'But up to that point, it was something I could think about.'

Up until this point, Kirko hadn't seen anything out of the ordinary.

Garam's method, or as it was sometimes called, the “Rotten Dog”, was incredibly efficient and straightforward, but it's not all that different from Kirko's method.

If that's the case, Kirko was already doing a good enough job.

...However, there was something special about the way Garam worked.

Peoeog- pasag!

Garam himself began to join in the labor with a shovel and pickaxe.

As an onlooker, Kirko couldn't help but raise a question mark over his head.

A guard doing labor? How is this any different from a real prisoner?

'No, why would a guard be in between the prisoners in the first place...?'

But regardless of that thought, Garam was very good at his labor.

It was as if he had been doing it his whole life.

Garam nagged the prisoners one by one, as if he had experience doing labor himself, and as if he had decades of experience building up his skills.

If a prisoner tried even the slightest trick or worked inefficiency, the nagging came back.

The prisoners were completely deprived of the leisure they had gained little by little while avoiding the eyes of the guards.

But that didn't stop him from scouring the prisoners.

'...The rumors were true.'

Garam shared his entire meal with the prisoners.

She didn't know what they were eating, but they didn't show any signs of malnutrition.

'But it seems to be a little different than the rumors?'

From what Kirko had heard, Garam was a pathetic man who was deprived of his meal by the prisoners.

But what about the reality?

The prisoners looked at Garam like he was a monster, doing more labor all morning and afternoon than all twelve of them combined, while never eating lunch.

Strong, overwhelming, all-knowing, charismatic.

Whether they were giant thugs, cunning manipulators, intelligent criminals, or naturally lazy slackers, the prisoners were all lambs before Garam.

Even if she knew how to do it, she wouldn't dare to follow.

Kirko finished her recollections with a shake of her head.

'What kind of a guard would do that to a prisoner if he did the work himself?'

◆

But Vikir had a different idea.

'It would be much faster for me to do the labor myself than for the prisoners to do it for me.'

The goal was performance, and then promotion.

Sooner or later, he'd have to earn the right to command high-level prisoners and activate the Poseidon in the Level Ten area.

Of course, right now there were a lot of prisoners digging, and the impact was probably being absorbed by the roots of the Poseidon.

'But there's nothing like a direct impact on the surface of the shell.'

So Vikir couldn't wait to get promoted and move up the ranks to deal with bigger, stronger, more ferocious prisoners.

If they didn't listen to him, he would starve them and beat them.

A little bit of the torture he'd learnt in the Age of Destruction, coupled with the ability to sneakily trigger the Starvation Drought, could bring a prisoner down to their very soul.

'One of these days, surely D'Ordume will give me instructions. Get rid of those pesky explosives.'

That would be the big opportunity.

That would be the time when the prelude to a full-scale jailbreak would take place, so he had to time it right.

Right on time.

“Attention, everyone!”

A guard burst into the dining hall.

It was a mid-level guard of the rank of Major, the rank that Vikir was currently aiming for, with a single leaf insignia attached.

“There's a riot! All guards on duty and those on standby are to assemble! Tell those off duty to do so immediately!”

The atmosphere in the dining hall was tense.

As if that weren't enough, the Major blurted out a shocking statement.

“Riot! Level 8!”

A riot by the prisoners of Level 8.

It was a lot different from the riots of the low-level prisoners on Level 1 or Level 2.

The complexions of the lower-level guards turned white, and the middle-level guards also stiffened their expressions.

The Major broke out in a cold sweat.

“The reason we're gathering all the low-level guards is because of the tactics. The senior guards are currently absent.”

D'Ordume and Souaré made a rare trip to the ground.

It was a call from the prison warden, Lieutenant General Orca, who said that the convoy was understaffed.

“Colonel D'Ordume and Souaré, they are on the ground escorting new prisoners. Brigadier-General BDISSEM and Brigadier-General Flubber are off... Commander Black Tongue is too dangerous, as you all know, and if he makes a move, his navel could be bigger than his stomach. We'll have to make do on our own.”

The riot of the Level 8 prisoners was so terrifying that even the Major-level guards were terrified.

Naturally, the lower-ranking guards, the so-called Lieutenants, looked on, not daring to step forward.

Then.

Drrrr-

The sound of a chair being dragged across the floor could be heard.

Everyone's eyes turned to see Garam walking out with a nonchalant expression.

There was no worry, no hesitation, just an immediate reaction.

Then.

...Tud!

Someone grabbed him by the wrist.

It was Kirko, sitting at a table diagonally across from him, observing him.

“Hey, are you crazy?”

She said in a small voice.

“It's Level 8. We're dead if we go.”

“Then what are we going to do? They tell us to come.”

“....”

At Garam's words, Kirko fell silent.

After all, you can't just not go when you're ordered to.

To a place where there was a 98% chance of being killed.

“Let's go see what the situation is.”

Vikir walked away with a nonchalant expression.

His demeanor was so calm that it was almost as if he was going somewhere good and doing something good.

Eventually, the other junior guards also rose from their seats, their bodies and minds heavy.

Wasn't Nouvelle Vague a place where a command is a command, and a protest is impossible?

Everyone walked down the corridor, anxious and nervous.

And it was Vikir who stood at the head of the group.

Unlike the rest of the group, Vikir's eyes were calm and bright.

'Maybe this is a good opportunity.'

Is there anything more helpful in personnel evaluation than a riot by high-level prisoners?

Chapter 393

The Worst Torture (6)

◆

Four months had passed since then.

“Today is a happy day! I am able to welcome so many new and capable subordinates!”

As Lt. Colonel Bastille wept tears of joy, a small ceremony was taking place in Nouvelle Vague.

It was called a promotion.

Although it was not a formal promotion ceremony held once a year, it had everything needed for a simple promotion ceremony.

As everyone applauded, the newest candidates for the promotion walked up to the podium.

Lieutenant Colonel Bastille, the officer in charge of the promotion ceremony, tearfully embraced each and every one of them.

But it was Garam, or rather, Vikir, who he hugged the hardest and longest.

“Congratulations, Captain Garam Nord!”

Originally a Lieutenant, Garam Nord had been promoted two ranks to Captain.

It was an unconventional promotion, almost unheard of among lower ranking guards.

But the even more surprising was the fact that no one seemed to think it was unreasonable that Garam had been promoted from lieutenant to captain in one swoop.

“Second Lieutenant Garam always exceeded his work quota anyway, so he deserved to be promoted to Captain on that basis alone.”

“Add to that the fact that he subdued a Level 8 prisoner's rampage four months ago, and he's proven to be capable. I think that's enough for a promotion to Captain.”

“Anyway, promotion to two ranks would have been natural over time... Lieutenant Colonel Bastille is showing off at this moment.”

“I don't know. As a rule, a promotion of two ranks requires a full investigation of one's background and a full investigation of one's past life, which not only takes months but is incredibly detail-oriented. Lieutenant Colonel Bastille thinks so highly of this young man that he spared that process.”

Everyone welcomed the new mid-level guard, Captain Garam Nord.

Many of them had been disciplined or demoted for their rowdy behavior.

Lieutenant Colonel Bastille personally pinned the three diamonds of Captain's rank on Vikir's breastplate and said.

“Since your exploits, the prisoner has been in solitary confinement for three months, and since his release he has been very faithful in his labor.”

“That's good. I think it's a testament to everyone's bravery.”

“Humbling. You were the bravest of them all. But....”

Lt. Colonel Bastille spoke in a low voice.

“What in the world did you do to make that rascal go down like that, by your own words?”

“I didn't say anything, I just used logic to convince him that there's no good in going on a rampage.”

“Hmmm, is that so, hahaha – okay, well, that's not exactly what I'm here to talk about, but I'll have a chance to hear more later.”

Lt. Colonel Bastille, a typically likable man, smirked, as if an unconventional answer wasn't so bad after all.

With that, Vikir descended from the stage, receiving the enhanced weapons and letters of appointment only given to those with the rank of Captain or higher.

...Good!

The weapon Garam chose was a three-tiered baton.

'It feels good in my hand.'

It was the weapon that the real Garam had used in his life, but it was also a good fit for Vikir.

Having spent his entire life as an assassin or swordsman, Vikir rarely had to use a weapon like the three-tiered baton, which was designed to beat and subdue, not kill.

'But the more I use it, the more I appreciate it.'

The cold feel of it against his palm, the crackle of the handle, the way the tip extended with two cheerful snaps with each swing.

In many ways, it was a weapon he'd come to love. It was like finding a second passion.

[Human. Is that what you've opened your eyes to?]

“Hmm. You mean nonlethal rather than lethal, then I suppose that's possible.”

[No. Not that one.]

“?”

Decarabia blurted out another unintelligible word.

Vikir shut him up and steps down from the stage.

He had gotten the Captain's rank he wanted, and that was enough for him.

◆

Dakkak-

Vikir closed the door on the visit.

The new quarters he'd been assigned upon his promotion to captain were far more comfortable than his old ones.

Goodbye stone caves, where he'd been crammed in like a swarm of ants in cramped, filthy quarters.

The interior of the fifteen square stone room was neatly organized.

It still had the same salty dankness, but with a window to the outside and a separate shower, it wasn't as bad as the lower-level guards' rooms.

Vikir went to the window and looked out.

Behind the thin layer of bubbles created by the mysterious mucus substance Flubber, the dark depths of the ocean stretched out before him.

But he could see quite well, thanks to the coral reefs and colonies of glow-in-the-dark jellyfish below.

In the distance, a giant shadowy figure swam by.

“....”

Vikir stood by the window and watched the nameless deep-sea fish swimming for what seemed like forever.

Then.

There was a tap.

There was a knock on the door.

“Captain. May I come in?”

A cold, firm voice.

Vikir didn't say anything, and the door opened.

A uniformed woman stood on the threshold. It was First Lieutenant Kirko.

Ever since Vikir had earned the rank of Captain, she had been his adjutant.

Kirko herself said it was a natural progression, but Lieutenant Colonel Bastille told a different story.

'For some reason, Lieutenant Kirko, who has always refused to be someone's adjutant, did not specifically refuse the executive order to become your adjutant. Hahaha-'

Lt. Colonel Bastille trailed off with an inexplicable glance.

Vikir turned his head, tearing his gaze away from the scenery outside the window.

“What's going on?”

It was natural, as if the relationship had always been one of superior and subordinate.

But Kirko, too, had taken the change for granted.

“Prisoner Sakkuth De Leviathan, on Level 8, has had another seizure.”

“Is this the first one since his solitary confinement?”

“Yes.”

Vikir nodded at Kirko's report.

With that, Vikir grabbed his three-tiered baton and left the room.

Then.

“...Ah.”

Vikir turned around as if he had forgotten something.

“?”

Kirko scratched her head.

As he turned, Vikir carried a thick Lun bible out of the room.

Looking at it, Kirko made a strange face and opened his mouth.

“Captain.”

“Why.”

“Are you religious?”

“To a certain extent.”

“I've never been to the surface, so I don't know what religion is like on the surface, but I've heard... that it is quite corrupted. They take money and forgive sins.”

“I don't know what you mean.”

“I mean, I wanted to ask you if the book would help calm the prisoner down.”

Vikir smiled dryly at Kirko's question.

“It might.”

The answer was short.

With that, Vikir descended the steep spiral staircase to Level 8.

He could feel the stone walls and floor creaking as he entered the prison.

“I can't believe I'm being executed! That's not true, I've been doing hard labor since my solitary confinement, and that blue blob in the Level 10 construction zone is swelling like crazy, and it's not all the result of my pickaxe! Aaaaaaah!”

Sakkuth's voice echoed throughout the corridor.

It seemed to be a protest against the death sentence.

Lieutenant Colonel Bastille was, to put it in a good way, a good man, but in a bad way, he was a safety-minded person.

He was someone who wanted as few variables as possible in his upcoming promotion.

To him, noise is a nuisance.

A variable, dangerous man who could strike again at any moment.

'...Well, he deserves a quiet, unofficial execution.'

Vikir clicked his tongue inwardly.

It's one thing to hasten his own demise.

Meanwhile, Sakkuth continued his rampage.

He was scattering poison, a mixture of water mold, sulfur, and several types of soil.

“I finally met 'him' in solitary confinement! How long do you think I'm going to be locked in here! I'm getting out of here soon, and what's with the execution, cancel it now, you bastards, I've done my duties faithfully, what's wrong with that, Aghhhhh!”

Sakkuth ran wild, foaming at the mouth.

Just then.

“...!”

The rampage stopped and it calmed down.

Even the guards, who had been pulling at BDISSEM's chain, turned their heads to stare in surprise.

Vikir stood there.

“Seniors. May I have your attention for a moment?”

At Vikir's polite request, the guards all nodded and stepped back.

But Kirko was still standing close to Vikir's side.

Vikir turned to Kirko.

“You stay back, too.”

“I can't.”

“Why not?”

“I am Captain Garam's adjutant. I am obligated to stand by your side at all times.”

Kirko's demeanor showed determination and stubbornness as she answered like a machine without changing her expression.

Vikir shook his head once.

The next thing he knew, he was standing in front of the cage.

“You will be executed in a week.”

“....”

“This is the result of your rampage, so take it sweetly.”

To Vikir's cold voice, Sakkuth could only stare, unable to answer.

The guards stood at full alert behind him, not knowing when he might explode again.

Then.

Vikir passed something through the bars.

It was a Lun bible.

“Read it before your execution, and repent.”

“....”

Sakkuth took the Bible with trembling hands.

With bloodshot eyes fixed on the book, he began to flip through the pages.

After a moment.

“...!”

Sakkuth's pupils dilated.

On the middle page of the Bible, a small print appeared.

'The time is short. D-7'

A secretly hidden push.

Upon seeing it, Sakkuth's demeanor softened and he began to sob.

“I acknowledge my sin. I will accept everything sincerely.”

His words came as a shock to all the guards present.

“My God, that maniac can't be that soft after all this time....”

“I can't believe my eyes.”

“Garam, what the hell did you do?”

The guards, who were destined to be forced to take the man's whims for the next week, breathed a sigh of relief as if they'd been doing it for a decade.

They swarmed around Vikir, demanding to know what he had done.

Vikir replied in a dry voice.

“Nothing much, I just gave him hope.”

Of course, that hope is false.

A week later, he would be executed. There would be no appeal.

'...The torture of hope is the worst kind of torture.'

Vikir knew this all too well, as a man who had lived through an Age of Destruction.

There was no salvation at the hands of others.

You can only save yourself.

Vikir turned his back on the now subdued Sakkuth.

Planning a 'real' escape, not the false one he'd promised Sakkuth.

'...A jailbreak in Nouvelle Vague is not just a jailbreak.'

Vikir was right.

'When Night Hound is released from Nouvelle Vague, many things will change in the world.'

It is an 'entrance sign' to a world where demons have begun to appear.

It will be humanity's declaration of war, marking the beginning of a new age of destruction.

Chapter 394

Dead Man Walking (1)

◆

A week went by quickly.

...Boom!

Vikir burned all of Garam's journals.

He'd already learned all the information he needed, and he could copy the handwriting perfectly.

'The font forgery I learned from Chihuahua has come in handy again.'

Now he wouldn't hesitate to use his handwriting wherever it was needed.

It was a relief.

-I want to get out of here, with her.-

Vikir stared at the burning pages of the diary.

Garam's wish to leave this place would never be fulfilled.

It will only turn to black, white ash and sinks to the bottom of the dark deep sea

“....”

Vikir watched the dozens of notebooks turn to ash from the beginning to the end

It was a small and humble end to a young man's life's work.

'Still, I got a lot of information out of it. Thank you.'

Vikir held a moment of silence for Garam. Until the smoke from the diary cleared.

Then.

A knock.

There was a knock at the door.

He opened the door to find Kirko standing there, her face expressionless.

“There is three hours before the execution.”

“...Why are you here so early?”

“I just wanted to let you know in advance.”

“...I see.”

Kirko stood motionless in the doorway, as if waiting for Vikir to finish getting ready and come out.

Vikir got dressed, feeling a little overwhelmed by the stare he couldn't quite figure out what was going through Kirko mind.

Then.

“Captain.”

Kirko spoke.

When Vikir turned his head, she took a deep breath and spoke.

“Before you go to the execution, may I have a word with you?”

It was a rather out-of-the-blue request.

There was no reason to refuse, so Vikir nodded, indicating her intention to do so.

Then Kirko spoke in a serious tone.

“As you know, Captain, I was born in Nouvelle Vague.”

“....”

“Once upon a time, there was an incident where a prisoner raped a guard, and I am the result.”

Vikir stopped buttoning his collar at Kirko's blunt words.

'I warn you, this may be a summary execution. Because of an 'unsavory incident' between a guard and a prisoner 19 years ago, the actor is strictly controlled and punished.'

Vikir still remembered Colonel D'Ordume's words when Vikir had refused to labor for some unknown reason.

Kirko continued in a calm tone.

“Afterwards, my biological father and mother were both referred to the disciplinary committee and disappeared. I guess he probably escaped from prison... anyway, that's why I don't know who my parents are, and of course I've never been to the surface.”

“Why are you telling me that story now?”

Vikir asked.

Kirko hesitated for a moment, then spoke up.

“That's because I hated you, Captain, because of my personal past, which I mentioned earlier.”

Kirko did not like Garam. No, she hated him.

It had nothing to do with the fact that Garam was dull and cowardly, too good to be true, and full of mistakes at every turn.

A fellow his own age, with parents to miss and an earthly home.

But Garam had two things Kirko did not.

“You have a home on earth, and you have parents. When we first met, you said you came all the way here because you wanted to help your parents make a living. You also said you missed the mountains and fields, the streams and lakes of your homeland.”

“....”

“Maybe I was envious of that, no, inferiority complex, that's right, so whenever the Captain made a mistake, I filled my lack of self-esteem by looking at it as pathetic and despising it.”

Garam probably didn't realize that Kirko had such thoughts until the very end.

'No. Even if I had known, it wouldn't have changed anything.'

Vikir stared at Kirko.

It was as if he wanted to say something.

Kirko took a deep breath before speaking.

“I wanted to be honest about this and apologize, because I don't think I should have this kind of petty, old feelings toward my future superior.”

“Is that why you volunteered to be my adjutant?”

“...I didn't say it myself.”

“I see.”

Vikir nodded.

Then.

Kirko opened her mouth, sounding even more puzzled than before.

“Captain, you have nothing to say to me?”

“...?”

Vikir looked up, and Kirko gave a rare stutter.

“You know, back when you saved me from that prisoner rampage on level eight.”

“What?”

“I'm not without ears to hear!”

“...?”

Vikir frowned.

As if he didn't understand.

Then Kirko started to sweat a little.

Her earlobes were already red to the limit.

“Ah, all the seniors around me are saying something.”

“Saying what.”

“About that prisoner rampage on Level 8. About why the Captain was willing to take a hostage for me...!”

Vikir realized what Kirko was trying to say.

'You. Do you really like her that much?'

'A man risking his life for a bitch. Don't you know what it means to be held hostage by me?'

'Hmm. What. You're so obsessed that you don't care about any of that, you smoked a cigarette with my blood on it. You're crazy.'

'Did Garam like Kirko?'

'You didn't know? He was always staring at Kirko whenever he came to work.'

'But don't you think that's a little reckless?'

'He's a real man. Risking his life for the girl he loves.'

The sarcastic remarks flashed through his mind.

So do the gossipy comments of the other guards,

“I-I would like to make it clear that my becoming your adjutant is merely the result of a natural chain of command, nothing more. There's supposed to be a separation between public and private affairs, but if a superior and a subordinate have such a bad relationship, what can I say, there could be a setback in public affairs... also... eh?”

But Kirko couldn't finish her sentence.

Vikir, now fully dressed in uniform, had left the room.

◆

Ttog- ttog-

An underground passage that looks like the throat of a giant monster.

Salty water droplets fell from the corrugated ceiling.

Jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog-

The sound of Vikir's military footsteps is heavy.

Dada-dada-dada.

The footsteps of Vikir's companions behind him are also loud.

“Why would you leave so quickly when your adjutant is talking to you?”

It was Kirko.

At Kirko's grumbling, Vikir raised his index finger to her lips.

“Shhh. There's a lot of people now.”

“....”

Vikir and Kirko had come down to Level 5 to attend the execution.

There were a number of guards and prisoners gathered there, and in the center stood the protagonist of the day, Sakkuth, bounded and shackled.

Lt. Colonel Bastille, who was on the podium, spoke to him.

“This is not a formal execution. You will forever be recorded as alive in the books.”

In a gravelly voice, he shouted at Sakkuth and many other prisoners.

But Sakkuth didn't react.

His eyes flicked from one guard to the next with a slight, uneasy tremor.

Then.

“...!”

Sakkuth's face visibly brightened as he recognized Vikir's form among the group of guards.

Then, the guards who were to conduct the execution stepped forward.

The main one was Vikir.

Vikir dragged Sakkuth to the cliff ahead.

There was a jutting rock at the edge of the cliff, and Sakkuth stood precariously on the edge.

“Stay steady.”

Vikir, standing behind him, spoke in a low voice.

“The moment you fall off the cliff, a rescue operation will be launched. Do you understand?”

“I understand.”

Sakkuth replied with a calm face.

Being thrown off this distant cliff is the 'unofficial execution ceremony' of the Nouvelle Vague.

Hudeulhudeu...

Vikir noticed that Sakkuth's legs were trembling slightly.

“Pathetic. Are you scared?”

“Well, how could I be?”

“Don't worry. See those guards and prisoners over there? They're all included.”

Vikir gestured with his chin to the left and right of the cliff.

Sakkuth looked in the direction he pointed.

Sure enough, there are guards and prisoners whose postures are subtly stiffened or loosened.

They looked suspicious.

“Those are the insiders who will help you. They'll come running as soon as I give the word.”

“Well, well. You're amazing. When did you get so many people on your side?”

“....”

Vikir didn't bother to answer.

In truth, the guards he was referring to were just ordinary guards and prisoners.

They were merely taking advantage of the psychology that a cornered man sees what he wants to see.

Sakkuth stood at the edge of the Hundred Foot Cliffs with unfounded hopes.

“Kurururu, I'm done with life. Do as you please, bastards!”

Sakkuth bellowed at the guards around him, then turned his head and glared at Vikir.

And with that, he leaped off the cliff.

Whirring.

A prisoner falling into a deep, deep abyss, into a pitch black space.

But.

The expression on the guards' faces hadn't yet resolved.

The execution was not over when he jumped off the cliff.

...And now.

Purrrrrrr.

The 'real' execution had begun.

“Huh?”

He didn't even realize he was being executed.

And for Vikir, it was the first time he'd actually seen it.

Purrrrrrrr!

A long line was being drawn in the darkness.

It opened its huge, vast gaping mouth as if it were alive, revealing a wealth of unpleasant-looking, misshapen teeth protruding from within.

Its mouth gaped open in a long line, seemingly endlessly.

A huge face was looking up, smiling widely with its teeth bared.

“Uh, what the hell! What the hell!”

Sakkuth's face turned pale.

At the same time, Vikir swallowed hard.

Of the five wardens representing Nouvelle Vague, he is the one whose identity is the most shrouded in mystery.

'...I heard he wasn't human, but I never thought he'd look like that.'

It was the appearance of Brigadier General Flubber.

Chapter 397

Black Tongue (1)

◆

Jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog-

jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog-

jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog-

jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog-

Two footsteps echo in unison through the corridors of salty, sticky dampness.

The one walking ahead is Major Garam Nord, and the one following is Captain Kirko Grimm.

Wearing Garam's identity, Vikir is currently walking towards the Hearing Audit's Room, where Lt. Colonel Black Tongue resides.

'Finally, I get to meet all five wardens.'

Colonel D'Ordume, Colonel Souaré, Brigadier General BDISSEM, and Brigadier General Flubber... Each of the Wardens we've met so far has been unique.

However, Lt. Colonel Black Tongue has a reputation for being dark and unpleasant person to the point where the other prison wardens mentioned above seemed ordinary.

'How is it possible that he received fewer votes in the popularity contest than Brigadier General Flubber?'

In the popularity polls by junior and mid-level guards, Colonel Black Tongue always came in last.

This was despite the fact that they were allowed to vote in duplicate.

Suddenly, Vikir turned to Kirko, who was trailing behind him, hoping for a clue.

“Hey, Adjutant.”

“Yeah.”

Kirko's face flushed a bit, as this was the first time Vikir had spoken to her since he became her superior.

The next topic, however, was enough to set her expression back to grim.

“You don't seem to like Lt. Colonel Black Tongue.”

“....”

“I heard him earlier.”

Kirko was silent for a moment at Vikir's words.

Then she opened her mouth.

“I don't gossip about my superiors.”

“Just state the facts.”

Kirko exhaled for a moment. What the hell, if the boss is gossipy, so be it.

“Real name and age unknown. Rank is Lieutenant Colonel, nickname is 'Black Tongue' or 'jailer catcher'. I think he got that nickname because he has a black tongue and he's on the Hearing and Audit team.”

“I heard he uses a sword, right? I hear he's very skilled.”

“Yes. It is said that in terms of ability alone. It's been said that he's ranked above Colonel D'Ordume and Colonel Souaré. However, his personality is so psychotic and his work reputation is so terrible that he should have been promoted to Brigadier General a long time ago based on seniority alone, but he's still a Lieutenant Colonel....”

“Internal irregularities, military discipline, hey, he take care of internal disciplinary action and various audits all by himself, right?”

“That's right, such things are rarely done within the Nouvelle Vague, unless it's at the whim of Lt Colonel Black Tongue himself, like today.”

“You seem to be very moody.”

“Yes. The problem is, it's not just his mood that are severe, but his impulse control disorders and sexual tendencies. He is notorious for molesting and torturing not only prisoners, but even guards.”

Kirko goes on to list the names of those who have been victimized by Black Tongue so far.

Most of them dead, crippled, or missing after horrific torture.

“23 years ago, Lieutenant Valentine Grimm, Lieutenant Farran Farrandle... 12 years ago, Lieutenant Yang Bortz, Captain Gordick... 7 years ago, Lieutenant Aubry, Major Jean Dayle... 3 years ago, Lieutenant Marsong, Lieutenant Yodle... 1 year ago, and most recently, Lieutenant Virginia, according to one of my colleagues....”

Among them was the name of what must have been Kirko's mother.

'So that's why you were grinding your teeth.'

Vikir tore his gaze away from Kirko's cold face.

It takes a lot to meet someone with a dark past.

◆

The hearing audit room where Lt. Colonel Black Tongue stayed was located in a dark and damp limestone cave.

Narrow, steeply sloping stone passageways, twisting back, forth, left, right, up, and down, the caverns were intricately twisted, but there was no need to worry about getting lost because it was a single road.

“It's so twisted. There is no decent person who lives in a place like this.”

“Normally, I wouldn't infer a person's character from where he lives, but... I have to agree with you on this one.”

At Vikir's words, Kirko nodded in agreement.

With that, they entered a fairly wide-open space.

It was nothing more than a wide extension of the path they had traveled so far.

Stalactites jutted up and down like teeth, salty water trickled down the walls, deep pools of water pooled on the floor, and....

“What is this?”

Kirko scratched her head at the black ball-like objects on the floor.

The black balls, which looked like eggs of some sort, became more and more numerous the further they went, until they covered the floor, walls, and ceiling.

Neither Vikir nor Kirko knew what these black spheres, about a meter in diameter, were.

When they poked at them with their fingers, they could only feel the softness, but they couldn't tell what was inside.

Then.

Kkuleuleug-

The black ball that Vikir had kicked with his military boot made a strange noise and twisted.

Juljuljuljul...

Red, yellow juice with an unpleasant smell began to leak from the top of the black ball.

“Ugh! What is this smell, it's like rotting meat....”

The odor was so disgusting that even the squeamish Kirko frowned.

With that, Vikir pulled out his three-tiered baton and struck the black ball.

Peoeog!

The black ball popped, and its contents began to gurgle out of the narrow hole in the top.

“...!”

In an instant, Kirko's eyes widened to tears.

It was a corpse emerging from the black ball.

A thin skull and thick blood poured down onto the floor.

Vikir kicked at the black balls next to him, one after the other.

...Peoeog! Kkuleuleug! Kulkeog!

Then the same unpleasant popping sound erupted and a foul odor began to emanate.

The black ball spat out different things inside.

A skeleton with only bones left, blood that has coagulated like jelly, chunks of yellow fat and flesh, or a desiccated mummy with only bones and skin remaining.

Vikir realized at once what the black balls were.

“Leeches.”

Leeches. Vampires that attach themselves to their victims and suck their blood.

But the leeches here in Nouvelle Vague are different.

There are blood-sucking leeches, bone-sucking leeches, skin-sucking leeches, and so on... Each leech here sucks different things.

A blood-sucking leech would quickly turn a human-sized person into a mummified mess of bones and skin.

Bone-sucking leeches remove all of the bones from the body, leaving the victim as a living “blood bag,” literally floating in a pool of blood and guts inside the skin.

When a skin-sucking leech bites someone, they are left with nothing but bones and blood, and the blood quickly solidifies, turning into a jelly-like substance with bones trapped inside, creating a strange and creepy sight.

The leeches at this point were all full-grown adults, each having swallowed a human in one bite, rolling the body into a ball and digesting it in their stomachs.

Surprisingly, some of those trapped in the leeches' stomachs were still alive.

Kirko heard a thin voice calling his name.

“Ki, Kirko....”

The voice sounded as if it could be cut off at any moment, no louder than a breeze.

Kirko's eyes widened as she recognized the voice.

“Virginia!?”

Lieutenant Virginia. Kirko had been missing since she'd been caught breaking military law and taken to Lt. Colonel Black Tongue.

At best, she'd helped Colonel D'Ordume embezzle military supplies as a low-level subordinate, but at most, she was taken to the auditor's office for the crime of embezzling a few bags of sugar that were supposed to be returned to the birthday person, and she never returned.

But Virginia's voice was coming from inside the black ball in the distance.

Peoeog!

Kirko immediately drew her sword and struck the black ball with all her might.

The leech's tough skin slowly sliced away as it touched the aura.

Kirko finally scratched the leech's flesh and twisted it open.

Chwaaaag-

The leech's bodily fluids spilled out, revealing Lieutenant Virginia inside.

“...!?”

Kirko covered her mouth with both hands at the sight of her companion, whom she hadn't seen in a year.

As Kirko stood dumbfounded, unable to find the words to say, Vikir stepped to her side and spoke.

“It must have been a bone-sucking leech.”

Sprawled on the floor, Virginia was in tears.

Desperately, she moved her mouth, shaping her lips to convey her last words.

“Kill... Me...”

Kirko stood dumbfounded, unable to close her eyes or mouth at the horrific sight.

It was Vikir who raised his hand in her place.

Kwag-

The skilled hound cut off the breath of his target with as little pain as possible.

“Aaah... aaah....”

Kirko dropped to her knees, her eyes moistened with tears, and clutched what had once been her companion with both hands.

Then.

“Hathathathathath- what the hell is this?”

The voice that greeted Vikir and Kirko echoed from the depths of the cavern.

A black ball, a single shadow stretched out amongst the countless leeches.

It was a singularly black color that stood out clearly against the shadows and darkness that surrounded it.

“....”

Vikir squinted his eyes.

At last, the most sinister and unpleasant man in Nouvelle Vague had appeared.

Lt. Colonel Black Tongue.

The last of the Five Warden.

Chapter 398

Black Tongue (2)

◆

“Hathathathathat- what the hell is this?”

There is a thick and muddy bass sound.

Vikir squinted to face the man in front of him.

The entire skin visible under the uniform was black, and there was not a single hair on the smooth skin.

Tightly defined muscles were subtly different in placement from human ones.

The face lacked eyelids, nose, and lips, revealing the eyeballs beneath the torn orbits and the sharp teeth.

Bugeulbugeulbugeul...

The muscle fibers that made up his body moved separately, strand by strand, bubbling like boiling tar.

Lt. Colonel Black Tongue.

He was the lowest ranking of the five wardens, but in fact, in terms of seniority, he was the most senior, except for Brigadier General Flubber.

'...D'Ordume and Souaré said he's been a lieutenant colonel since they were second lieutenant.'

Vikir scanned Black Tongue's entire body.

The seasoned hound was quick to formulate an estimate of his prey.

But even if he had a rough idea of its power, he still didn't know how evil it was, or what it was up to.

So Vikir met Black Tongue with the most benign and common-sense response possible.

“I'm sorry for carelessly hurting the leech. I'm so surprised... my heart is still pounding like it's going to explode.”

Vikir blustered, stealing a nervous sweat.

Like the hero of a past era, who hid under his desk, pretending to be startled and rattled by the sound of lightning, to hide his extraordinary abilities from his enemies.

Vikir's strategy of humbling himself seemed to have some effect.

The unpleasant, ominous aura that Black Tongue was emitting was diminished, if only slightly.

“Hathathat- I see you're Captain Garam, or is it Major, and you're not as gutsy as you're rumored to be.”

“It's a burden because it seems like it's being overvalued due to the current situation.”

“No. Judging by the rumors, you are a complete monster. Rather, it's nice to see a humane side, but what~”

“....”

“Ah! Have a seat, wherever you're comfortable, and don't mind the leeches, I threw them away when they became a nuisance. I often use them as cushions, though they don't have much to offer other than being fluffy~”

Black Tongue turned away with an unpleasant chuckle.

Every time he moved, Vikir could see the muscles on his back twitching, and upon closer inspection, they were all leeches.

The tiny, tough leeches were tightly woven throughout Black Tongue's body, as if each one were a single muscle fiber.

In other words, he was wearing leeches all over his body. It was like a suit-like full body armor!

'...I've heard that Lt. Colonel Black Tongue is human, but despite being human, he's not treated as such, and I can see why.'

Who would consider a human being to be a human being who wears leeches all over his body 24/7?

It was a rather generous assessment of a similar species.

“I see. You're here sooner than I thought, I guess that Bastille guy was in a bit of a hurry?”

Black Tongue naturally looked down on Bastille, who was also a Lt. Colonel of the same rank.

It was natural. If only for time, he should already be a Brigadier General or Major General.

As Vikir nodded, Black Tongue smiled.

It was an unpleasant smile, one of those smiles where you're smiling but not really smiling.

“I see. How's that Bastille guy doing, still acting like a helpless pet without his master?”

“...That's a difficult question to answer.”

“Hathathathat, from a subordinate's point of view. As for that Bastille guy~ he used to obey my orders when D'Ordume or Souaré were around, but now that those two bastards aren't around, he's just as stubborn as ever~ I often have to argue with him because his reactions are hilarious~”

Vikir looked at Black Tongue's face for a moment.

He'd heard that Black Tongue didn't get along with all of Nouvelle Vague's guards, but he was especially bad with D'Ordume and Souaré.

D'Ordume dislikes Black Tongue for interfering with his efforts to steal various goods from Nouvelle Vague, and Souaré has a deeply rooted feud with Black Tongue.

'Rumor has it that it was Black Tongue that blew off half of Souaré's face.'

It was recorded in Garam's diary that they had met and fought several times during their time on land, including a famous naval battle.

...Well, it wasn't exactly Vikir's business.

Meanwhile, Black Tongue landed on the leech in front of Vikir.

Ppujig!

He sat down on top of the leech, and it spat out a thick, purple juice from its mouth.

It sounded like a human groaning inside.

“....”

“....”

Vikir and Kirko shut their mouths as if they had made a promise.

It wasn't that they were hiding a secret, it was just that the atmosphere was so dank and unpleasant.

'Surely there are humans inside those cushioned leeches?'

'I'm sure there are, but let's sit down. If you're uncomfortable, sit on the floor.'

'...No. I'm not uncomfortable.'

Kirko looked determined and sat down on the ball of leeches in front of her.

It was a determined demeanor, as if she wasn't going to be overpowered.

Ppujig-

The leech beneath her ass shudders again, this time spewing out a thick stream of blood.

No human groans could be heard.

'Lucky.'

Kirko thought, the best of all possible worlds.

If she could hear a human groan from beneath her ass, she probably wouldn't have been able to maintain her expression.

Meanwhile, Black Tongue, seeing Kirko's eyes narrow for a moment, spoke up with a chuckle.

“You look like you're about to get fucked~”

“....”

“Joke. Joke. You look tense, so I'm trying to loosen you up~”

His face still didn't show much of a smile, but at least the leeches that had taken over his facial muscles could be inferred to be in full bloom.

“Okay, I'm going to start the interrogation now. It's simple, so don't be too frozen. If you're stiff, your blood won't flow as well, which is bad for your circulation. It's also bad for the flavor.”

“....”

“Joke again. A joke. You young people are so serious nowadays, you can't joke around.”

Black Tongue frowned, but continued in a friendly tone.

“Haha, I'm afraid I might be a little off-putting – both in appearance and personality! The average guard never gets to meet me anyway, and there are many who have spent decades in the Nouvelle Vague who have never seen me.”

“....”

“The ones I do see are always the same. Failure to pay their dues, violation of military honors, lack of discipline, desertion, insulting their superiors... They're all assholes. If you've lived your life upright, you have no reason to be afraid of me. Rest assured.”

Black Tongue continued to waggle furiously for a long time after that, preaching about how people shouldn't be judged by first impressions or appearances, how people shouldn't sin, and so on.

His eyes narrowed as he held in his hand the papers containing the findings of his investigation into Vikir, or rather, Garam.

'Let's see. Separate... Origin is from the land... had an ordinary lower-class family... Was your career a little below average? But your grades have risen sharply recently? When will this be the starting point? ... Umm, okay... After 'Night Hound' prison escape incident, your grades improved noticeably... At this time, did you get caught up in some serious accident and as a result you became awakened? Hmm... From then on, it was all success... It's like I've become a different person... After suppressing a Level 8 prisoner's riot, it's a special promotion... It seems like Lieutenant Colonel Bastille openly favored you and pushed you? It's not like you're his distant relatives or anything like that, right?'

Black Tongue stuck out his purple-stained tongue and interrogated Vikir with a poisonous snake-like gaze.

At the slightest hint of weakness, he could feel its intention to stick to it and suck out everything inside

...However.

“Yes. I come from the ground. I recently received a telegram telling me that my parents and siblings all died at once. I heard that everyone in my hometown suffered disaster.”

“Oh, I'm sorry to hear that, what happened?”

“They say there's a demon on earth and it's turned my hometown into a sea of fire, though I only heard about it in a few short sentences, so I don't know the full story.”

“Yeah, it's kind of hard to communicate with the outside world here in Nouvelle Vague, isn't it? Yeah, that must be frustrating. Anyway, did it make you feel like a different person?”

“It was a trigger.”

Vikir is an unseen being from the Age of Destruction, and his ability to conceal his mana and power is greater than anyone else in the current era.

What even Hugo, the master of Ironblooded Baskerville, had failed to notice in the first place, Black Tongue could not.

“Haathathat. They say there's been a lot of trouble on the ground these past few months.”

“Is that so?”

“Yeah. Well, demons or monsters suddenly appear, the dungeon opens, a gate appears, and what else? And it's been pretty crazy, and that's why Orca, D'Ordume, and Souaré went up to the surface to escort the exploding population of sinners to this place, though I'm only here, so I don't really know.”

Black Tongue muttered in a cheerful voice, checking off items on the paperwork.

Then he slammed the file shut.

“Interrogation over, then. Everything's fine, you. Clean~ clean~ clean~”

“If you're done with your business, I'll just head back.”

“Eh? Eh~ No matter what, I didn't ask you to leave, so how dare you say that first. I'm a Lieutenant Colonel, You're so bold, aren't you?”

“I'm sorry, I have a lot of work to do.”

Vikir rose from his seat, and Black Tongue opened his mouth in a smirk.

“Sit.”

“....”

“No~ What's with the scary look on your face? Relax~ I didn't mean what you said.”

Black Tongue waved at Vikir as if telling him to go out.

The place where his gaze is directed is behind Vikir.

“Hothothot. It's been a long time, hasn't it?”

It was Kirko's face.

Chapter 399

Black Tongue (3)

◆

Black Tongue was unperturbed by Vikir's request to get up first, and gave a brief nod of approval.

“...And so it is.”

The interrogation was over, and there was no reason to remain in such an uncomfortable place.

Vikir gave Black Tongue a curt bow and rose to his feet.

“Ah....”

Kirko opened her mouth to say something, but stopped herself.

Black Tongue had opened his mouth first.

“You may leave first. I don't think your adjutant's interrogation will be very long.”

“Yes, sir.”

Vikir saluted, then turned and walked out of the room.

Kirko watched his back with a complicated expression, then turned her attention back to the front.

“...!”

For a moment, she had to gasp.

The face of Black Tongue was now right in front of her.

“Hathathat, it's been a long time since I've seen you.”

Black Tongue took Kirko's hand and rubbed her shoulder.

“...?”

Kirko furrowed her brow in disbelief.

For one thing, this was the first time she'd ever seen Black Tongue.

But more than that, it was the cold, firm feel of it against her skin that was so unpleasant.

So Kirko leaned her upper body back slightly, avoiding contact with Black Tongue.

“I am new to you, Lt Colonel Black Tongue.”

“Hathathat- yes, I remember you. You used to say such cold things to me every time we met, no matter how hard I tried to woo you~”

“...What do you mean, I'm obviously meeting you for the first time today.”

“Awww~ Not again. Okay, I'll bear with you since it's been a while. How could I have forgotten your pretty face all these years? I missed you so much! I guess you're not getting any older, we....”

Black Tongue pulled the leech muscles across his face into a tight smile.

“Lieutenant Valentine Grimm.”

A moment. Kirko's expression went hard.

She barely managed to keep her lips from falling apart and managed to get a shaky voice out.

“...My name is Kirko, Captain Kirko Grimm.”

“Huh?”

Black Tongue looked dazed for a moment.

Then he raised a fist and made a gesture of punching himself in the head.

“Damn, look at me. You're here as Major Garam's adjutant, aren't you? You look so much like her that I've stopped mistaking you. Well, that was already a few years ago....”

Black Tongue began to flick through the papers in his hands.

“That's right, that's right, you got a surprise promotion to Captain today. Was Captain such an easy rank to attain?”

“....”

“I haven't seen a Captain so quickly since D'Ordume and Souaré. Ah, Major Garam, he's a bit of an exception.”

Black Tongue looked back and forth between Kirko and the papers and smiled.

“Age 22, hometown... Eh, Nouvelle Vague? You're from here? Ah, so you were born here, then, and your parents are guards.”

He rolled his eyes and thought about something, then slapped his knees.

“I see! Somehow, I thought you looked familiar. You're the child of 'those guys', aren't you?”

Kirko bit her lip at that.

'That incident', 23 years ago now. Kirko was the child born when a prisoner jumped on a guard.

Black Tongue was referring to that very incident.

However, things were going to turn out a little differently than Kirko had imagined.

“That's right, there was a reputation in the Nouvelle Vague at the time for being a good guy and a good girl. The higher-ups were even considering paternity leave.”

...?

Kirko shook her head.

Surely she was the child of a prisoner and a guard.

An ominous being whose very birth touched on unspeakable taboos.

A heretic whose roots lie in the lower reaches, unwelcome everywhere.

And yet, what Black Tongue was recalling was so different from what she knew.

“Yes. I remember them walking around holding hands in a secret love affair, both of them exemplary low-level guards. They made me jealous.”

Black Tongue's voice was hot and sticky with desire, like molten asphalt.

“Just looking at it made me feel sick to my stomach and I couldn't bear it, so I had him arrested for breach of military discipline. It happened to be around the same time that D'Ordume and Souaré were getting really tough on prisoners, so we had to keep discipline among the guards.”

Kirko's pupils dilate uncontrollably.

Before she could open her mouth to speak, Black Tongue spoke in a wide grin.

“So I decided to hastily fake one of the more shocking incidents – yes, that's right – your parents.”

The love of a male guard and a female guard, a secret love affair between lowly junior guards.

It was forged as an incident in which a prisoner attacked a guard.

The guards needed a story as shocking as possible to make the prisoners despise and hate them.

Kirko muttered in a daze.

“Dad wasn't... a prisoner? Mom wasn't... victimised?”

Kirko thought of her parents, whose faces she didn't know.

She hated her nameless, faceless father and pitied her mother, whose only name she knew.

And now, Kirko knew two things.

That her mother and father loved each other fiercely, and that her mother's face was eerily similar to her own.

“...Maybe I could have been loved by both Mom and Dad.”

Kirko closed her eyes.

The emotion rising in her chest was unmistakably relief.

“...Thank God, Dad's not a bad person, Mom's not a miserable person. I'm the only bad one.”

No more hating the father.

No more pity for the mother.

This alone seemed to lighten her heart, which had been imprisoned since birth.

...But there were still unanswered questions.

“So. What did you do to my parents?”

Kirko asked, glaring at Black Tongue.

Her tone had changed to a sharp half-speech, but Black Tongue didn't seem to mind.

“Why are you looking for your parents from me?”

“You dragged them away, and they've been missing ever since.”

“Yeah, I did that, huh?”

Black Tongue began to roll around in his eyeballs.

It looked like it was trying to think hard.

And then.

“...Aah!”

He slapped his knee, as if remembering something.

Black Tongue spoke brightly, like a boy remembering a long-forgotten time capsule.

“That's right! I dragged your parents away! I remember screaming loudly no matter how unfair it was... But they just disappeared? Didn't come back? Isn't that strange? Did they just escape?”

He set his jaw and thought for a while longer.

“That's right, that's right! I forgot and didn't let them out! I only locked them up for a few days and got busy interrogating them and forgot! Where do you think they are now...?”

Huddled eyeballs rolled separately to the left and right.

Then Black Tongue raised a finger.

“I remembered! There they are!”

Black Tongue stretched out his index finger and pointed.

That's where Kirko is sitting now.

It was the black ball under her bum.

“Hathathat- you're sitting on it now. On top of your mom.”

Hearing Black Tongue's words, Kirko's expression went blank for a moment.

For a moment, a flashback flashed through her mind.

It was a conversation she'd had when she'd first entered the stone chamber.

'Surely there are people inside those leeches that act as cushions?'

'I'm sure there are. Let's sit down. If you're not comfortable, you can sit on the floor.'

'...No. I'm not uncomfortable.'

She sat down, not wanting to be pushed by the momentum of Black Tongue.

For a moment, Kirko felt her legs give way.

As her weight was added to it.

Poof.

The leech beneath her ass shudders again, this time spewing out a thick stream of blood.

And Black Tongue grinned at her, as it had done so many times before.

“You look like you're about to get your ass kicked~”

He stood up from his seat with an exaggerated gesture and walked back to Kirko's back.

He stroked the black ball and said.

“Joke. Joke. I think you're nervous, so I'm going to loosen you up~ Your mom will be sad if you're so stiff, ahhh, this. I'm sorry about your parents. I really did tell them to let them go after a few days, but I must have forgotten and stuck them in a corner. I forgot about them, what the fuck?”

Black Tongue brushed off the dust that had settled on the black ball.

Then he kicked the side of the ball with his military boot, causing everything inside to spill out.

Chwaaaaak-!

Thick liquid spread across the floor. It smelled foul.

Black Tongue held out two hands and said.

“Say hello. This is your mom and dad. My forgetfulness has delayed this meeting. But how fortunate they are to meet you now. Does it feel good...?”

However, he didn't finish his sentence.

Sappug-

The tip of a sword sliced through the air and grazed his forehead.

“Gosh! What the heck is this? Bottomless?”

Quickly jerking his head back to dodge, Black Tongue turned to look at Kirko with a smirk on his face.

Kirko, who had drawn her longsword from her waistband, faced Black Tongue with a terrifying momentum.

Jjuuug-

Black Tongue pulled on his neck as if it were rubber, stretching it.

“That's a good look, just like your mom, that's why I like girls who do things like that.”

He didn't seem to intend to be provocative, but in truth, his every move was an enormous provocation to Kirko.

Even just smiling, even just breathing.

Sweaeg-

Once again, Kirko's longsword sparkled with light.

However.

Jjuuug-

The rubbery palm of Black Tongue slammed into Kirko's abdomen.

“Kuhugh!”

She flew like a kite with a broken thread and slammed into the wall behind the stone chamber.

“Keughh....”

It looked like a few ribs were broken.

Maybe sharp bits of bone were embedded deep in her guts.

“Hathathathat- Your eyes are still there, that must hurt a lot.”

“....”

Kirko gritted her teeth.

She must kill him, even if it means dying.

Prepared for death, she drew all her strength into her sword.

Flowing...

Soon, an aura as sticky and dense as honey glowed brightly at the tip of the sword.

Black Tongue saw it and clapped his hands in amazement.

“Wow! A Graduator at your age? That's what it takes? That's amazing. You're so talented, too bad you're going to die here. Have you ever thought about getting pregnant? I might be able to give you another year or so of life like your mother....”

“Shut up!”

Kirko's eyes finally rolled back.

Her sword sliced through the air with killing intent.

Of course, it did little to erase the genuine smile on Black Tongue's face.

...However.

A somewhat unexpected result occurred.

Kirko's sword failed to kill Black Tongue. That was to be expected.

But there was one thing she did succeed in.

It completely erased the deep smile that formed on the corner of Black Tongue's mouth.

...Of course, Kirko did not accomplish this alone.

Tsk.

Vikir. No, Major Garam Nord.

He had appeared out of nowhere, stepping between Kirko and Black Tongue.

Ttug- ttudug- hududug-

Black blood drips from Vikir's hand as he grips Kirko's sword blade tightly.

“...I apologise. I forgot my adjutant.”

Vikir said, his head half turned towards Black Tongue behind his back.

“My adjutant has a severe case of codependency, and when I'm not around, she has these intense anxiety attacks.”

But Black Tongue wasn't listening to Vikir at all.

It was simply staring at the drops of Vikir's blood dripping onto the floor.

'Yes. Get him.'

Vikir nodded, watching Black Tongue's eyes grow increasingly greedy and mad.

“Now, if you'll excuse me, I'd better get going, or my adjutant might go on a blind stabbing spree somewhere, and I don't mean the lower levels.”

“Uh, yeah. Go ahead.”

Black Tongue merely waved his hand, distracted for some reason by Vikir's blood on the floor.

Vikir picked Kirko up and held her close.

“Now, wait a minute... Ha!”

Kirko pushed against Vikir's chest, trying to protest, but the pain in her lower abdomen prevented her from finishing the sentence.

Jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog-

Vikir exited Black Tongue's chamber, still holding Kirko.

'Black tongue...I will see you again soon.'

The hound's eyes which momentarily moves away from the baited prey, remain calm as usual.

Chapter 401

Jailbreaker (1)

◆

Mealtime.

Vikir ate in the mess hall on a rare off-duty day.

Black bread, pickled sardines, and wilted greens. No corrosion. That was it.

Despite the fact that it was a meal for a Major-level guard, it was pretty poorly organized.

'They must be running low on supplies these days.'

If this was good enough for a Major, what about the lower ranking guards?

At this point, he couldn't even imagine what the prisoners were eating.

He didn't see many familiar faces in the labor camp these days, and he wondered if they've all starved to death.

Vikir was sitting alone, eating.

“Is that true?”

“Yes. It is.”

He could hear the muffled conversations of the lieutenant colonels at the table in front of him.

Vikir's superhuman hearing allowed him to pick up on conversations over great distances.

“They say the land is in an uproar. Demons and monsters are out in force.”

“They said a giant gate or something opened?”

“That's right. They said monsters are pouring out of it.”

“There must have been a breakdown in security. That's why the prisoner population exploded.”

“Who cares about security now? The entire empire is in danger.”

Most of them were chattering about surface matters.

Some of them didn't seem to believe in anything that happened on the land at all.

“Wow. How old are you, and do you still believe in demons and such? It's all fiction, invented by the religious fanatics of the Quovadis.”

“That's right, I don't believe in anything I haven't seen with my own eyes, but I'm 10,000 meters under the sea, is it possible to see it directly? Hahaha-”

“Hmm, but all the new prisoners say they've seen demons or something, including the gate.”

“Do you really believe the prisoners who come in here? They've all gone crazy with fear, being trapped in the Iron Maiden and sinking 10,000 meters down.”

Others took the rumor seriously.

“No, it's not right, I don't think we've ever had so many prisoners in Nouvelle Vague before. There must be some kind of disturbance on the ground.”

“Yes. If Warden Orca, Colonel D'Ordume, and even Colonel Souaré have traveled to the surface to escort prisoners, then something has indeed happened.”

“Yes. Not only is the Warden, the symbol of the Nouvelle Vague, away, but two of the five wardens have gone to the surface at once, which is unprecedented.”

“Isn't the surface already fucked? From what I've heard, gates are opening and demons are coming out of them, and the patriarchs of the Seven Great Families of the Old Country are getting assassination threats.”

But. Most of the guards weren't too interested in the topic.

“Well, we'll just have to deal with the criminals here.”

“That's true. It's none of our business.”

“Since when are we involved in worldly affairs?”

“If demons and monsters are running amok up there, wouldn't it be safer here?”

“Whatever's going on up there can't possibly have reverberated down here.”

The guards of Nouvelle Vague were mostly relegated and isolated members of society, with little love for the world or loyalty to the Empire.

It had been so long since they had been outside that they had little curiosity about how the world had changed.

They had little curiosity about how it had changed, because it was obvious that they would not be able to adapt to it anyway.

...But.

Vikir, listening to all of this, had a different opinion.

'Nouvelle Vague will not be free from the aftermath of the Destruction War after all.'

In Vikir's original history, Nouvelle Vague had been safe for some time after the war began.

Its geography – 10,000 meters below the surface of the ocean – was an advantage, allowing it to escape the aftermath of the war.

However, the demons took notice of Nouvelle Vague's existence and sent troops to this harsh place.

Despite the efforts of Orca Javert, the war hero of a previous generation who had put down the 47 riots, and the current head warden of Nouvelle Vague, and the five wardens under his command, the power of demons was impossible to stop.

Then, in the midst of their defeat, Nouvelle Vague fell for reasons that had nothing to do with the demons.

Most of the guards and prisoners perished in the process, and those who survived came to the surface with a hatred for demons and joined the Human Alliance Forces or fought demons through independent routes.

'That should hasten that time a bit.'

Vikir thought as he chewed on a wilted piece of greenery.

The condition of the vegetables on the ground must mean that things were deteriorating faster than he thought.

Then.

“There you are.”

The chair next to Vikir's screeched backward.

Lt. Kirko Grimm. She was suddenly sitting next to Vikir, taking her seat.

Having recovered her strength, she spoke in a calm voice.

“Apparently, being promoted changes the quality of information you get.”

“Did you hear anything?”

“Warden Orca says he's on his way back. With Colonel D'Ordume and Colonel Souaré.”

The 'Big Three' of the Nouvelle Vague.

They were currently on their way down to Nouvelle Vague with a huge convoy of prisoners.

Countless Iron Maidens would be sinking to the bottom of the pitch black waters, how many of them would make it to Nouvelle Vague alive?

“Are the guards coming in Gulper eels?”

“Colonel D'Ordume and Colonel Souaré will, and Warden Orca comes 'in person'.”

“...In person?”

“Yes. As usual.”

Kirko shifted casually to the next topic.

“Rumor has it that there is a great monster among the prisoners coming this time.”

“What's that supposed to be?”

“Apparently someone tried to assassinate the patriarch of one of the Seven Great Families, and for that crime it was sent straight to Nouvelle Vague without even a trial. Presumably this person will be transferred there as soon as the construction of Level 10 is complete.”

The arrival of a new prisoner was not exactly Vikir's concern.

“When will Warden Orca and the other two wardens arrive?”

“I'd like them to arrive within a week, if not sooner.”

“The new prisoners will arrive by then.”

Vikir's eyes turned cold.

The arrival of new prisoners meant the opening of an entrance ceremony.

It was the responsibility of Lt. Colonel Bastille, and Vikir, now that he has earned his trust, would be among them.

If there was to be an escape, this would be the time.

Especially since the escape Vikir had in mind wasn't the usual sneak-through-the-openings kind of escape.

“...I'm going to get busy.”

Vikir picked up his plate and stood up. There was a lot to prepare.

Then.

Drool.

As Vikir stood up, Kirko, who was sitting next to him, also stood up.

There were still a few pieces of black bread and sardines on her plate.

Vikir said.

“It looks like you're not quite finished eating, but why don't you finish?”

“When my superior gets up, I have to get up with him.”

“...Why?”

“Because I'm your second-in-command.”

Kirko replied as if it were obvious.

Vikir thought for a moment.

Ever since that day, ever since they'd been audited by Black Tongue, Kirko had followed him closely.

Always on call, always with him, and always on all the other little extra duties.

They even had rooms right next to each other, which meant that the only time they were apart was to sleep, shower, and go to the bathroom.

Whoever came up with the idea of scheduling shifts like this?

'...I have a lot of work to do starting tonight, and this is going to throw off my plans.'

Vikir thought for a moment, then turned to Kirko.

“So. Are you going to ask me to stay with you tonight?”

Vikir's voice was unusually loud.

Several of the guards returning the plates heard him.

Kirko's face turned bright red as she realized the wide-eyed stares of the guards around her.

“What do you mean by that?”

“That night. Don't you remember?”

“Oh, no!”

“That's exactly what you said that night. That you didn't want to be alone.”

Suddenly, Kirko's eyes became fierce.

She spoke clearly, in a low voice, and in an extremely business-like tone.

“I don't want you to be mistaken by the fact that it happened once before, but that was a day when I was unusually weak, both in body and mind....”

“I thought you said you didn't remember?”

“....”

Then Kirko's face flushed red to the tips of his ears.

“I thought it was a dream!”

But her words only reinforced the misunderstanding of those around her.

“Oh, no! That's not it! I'm not saying I thought I was dreaming, but I really thought it was a dream....”

Kirko, who was still panicking and making comments to herself, quickly disappeared from the scene.

Only then could Vikir clear his head.

The peaceful (?) life in Nouvelle Vague was over.

'The time for the Great Escape has come.'

Time was running out.

The time is short. A great unprecedented chaos will engulf the entire Nouvelle Vague.

This will be the signal for humanity's counterattack before the extermination.

It will illuminate the final thorny path the Hound will walk in the future.

Chapter 404

Jailbreaker (4)

◆

Vikir fixed his gaze on the sword in front of him.

He couldn't say for sure who it was, but he had a hunch.

An unprecedented Great Demonic Sword whose notoriety extended far beyond the Demon World and into Middle Earth.

The Seven Ancient Demon Constellations, also known as the Seven Great Plagues.

The remains of these Seven Ancient Demon Constellations were brought into the mortal world in some form, whether material or conceptual, and despite no longer being able to interfere with the laws of cause and effect, they retained some of the power of their lives.

One of these was this sword, Beelzebub.

'But there are six others.'

Vikir thought, looking at the red sword of Beelzebub protruding from the wrist of his right hand.

Humans called the seven swords made from the remains of the Seven Demon Constellations the 'Seven Demon Swords'.

This Beelzebub is one of them.

...And the sword in front of Vikir was also one of the magic swords included in the Seven Demon Swords.

The magic sword Asmodeus. A fearsome sword that rivaled Beelzebub.

One of the final weapons brought by the demons in the later stages of the Age of Destruction.

'It was one of the great weapons of the First Corpses, and I never thought it would be here.'

Vikir thought as he gazed at Asmodeus, the magic sword in front of him.

And Asmodeus's current owner, Black Tongue, stared at the wrinkled hilt with a mesmerized look in his eyes.

“Once upon a time, I had a leech that I loved... No, now that I think about it, maybe it wasn't a leech at all, well, anyway.”

Black Tongue was now explaining how he had acquired the magic sword Asmodeus.

“It had a great appetite for blood, very greedy, but it kept sucking blood, and it got too big and strong and out of control.”

Black Tongue laughed as he kissed Asmodeus' sword.

“So I tricked it, locked it in solitary confinement, and starved it to death. Souaré had a hard time with that, I guess?”

“....”

“But this one, it turns out, is so strong that no matter how long I locked it in solitary confinement, it wouldn't die. Instead, it just stays skinny and unmoving, like it's hibernating, and no matter how long I try to dry it with hot air, it doesn't die, it just shrivels up~”

Black Tongue grinded the leech, which had turned into a solid stick of meat, against a whetstone.

“There was a ton of meat powder coming out. But as a result, it became so sharp, right? Does it look like a real sword?”

It's amazing that the remains of the Demon Constellation didn't lose its bloodlust after such a long time after it was separated from its deceased body, but it's even more amazing that there was a madman who grinded it into a sword.

'So this is how the magic sword Asmodeus was born.'

Vikir marveled at the madness of Black Tongue.

But it's only admiration as a spectator to the show, the hound eyeing his prey with his usual lazy gaze.

“You'd better be careful. That sword does not serve an unworthy master. It'll take the opportunity to bite, and then turn around and eat you.”

Before the regression, he'd seen many examples.

Humans and demons alike have fallen prey to the sword.

But Vikir's warning did not fall on deaf ears.

Black Tongue smirked and lifted Asmodeus.

“This one still wants blood, even after all this time. Yes, he wants your blood, and he wants it hard.”

It was true.

Asmodeus was swelling up, drinking the blood of Black Tongue.

It pulsed like a madman, eager to lunge at the Vikir in front of it!

And then.

Clang!

The two magic swords clashed together.

“....”

Vikir swallowed a groan at the weight on his wrist.

He wasn't sure how dried out the large hunk of meat was.

It was certainly small in volume, but it weighed a ton, and its strength far exceeded that of any metal.

Just as a large hunk of meat becomes smaller and harder when it dries out.

Kiriririk-

Moreover, the sword itself bends at odd angles and slashes through gaps.

It was like watching a vampire itself, a single, blood-crazed leech.

Peoeog-

Asmodeus bent like a whip, avoiding friction with Beelzebub.

Peopeopeog!

Just as Beelzebub of Vikir stabbed Black Tongue in the chest, Asmodeus of Black Tongue also stabbed Vikir in the thigh.

“Aaaah!? You damned bastard, you're supposed to protect your master before your meal!”

Black Tongue screamed, but the shape of his mouth was smiling.

Madness. It is indeed the sword of its master.

“....”

Vikir frowned.

Even though the sword was rampaging on its own, it was all taking routes optimized for killing.

In addition, Black Tongue had considerable swordsmanship skills.

Perhaps he could even crush Colonel D'Ordume or Colonel Souaré with simple combat power alone.

Tsutsutsutsuts...

Vikir had tried to tap into the power of the starvation drought within Beelzebub, but it was clearly inferior to Asmodeus' bloodsucking abilities.

Moreover, Asmodeus was gulping down Vikir's blood, which contained Madame's poison.

“What a troublesome guy.”

Vikir said briefly, stepping back.

Black Tongue smirked and followed Vikir.

“Are you scared? Are you afraid? Why are you running away?”

“....”

Vikir stepped back, silent. He took the route back the way he'd come.

But Black Tongue wouldn't let him get away.

“Fear makes you blind and deaf, my friend.”

At the same time.

Grasp!

Black Tongue's arm snapped a little more grotesquely.

“...!”

Vikir saw Asmodeus, who had let go of Beelzebub, was also bent at an even more severe angle.

Black Tongue smiled.

“No wonder, the more blood it sucks, the more flexible it becomes.”

As dried beef jerky absorbs water, it becomes softer.

The same was true for Asmodeus.

Asmodeus coiled itself into an even more volatile shape than its previous trajectory, and then slammed into Vikir's face.

“...!”

Vikir quickly jerked his head to the side, but Black Tongue's deft swordplay only succeeded in pushing Asmodeus deeper and deeper into Vikir mouth.

Kwadeug!

Vikir's ear was ripped off entirely.

It was such a severe wound that even the organs inside, such as the cochlea and the semicircular canal, were ripped out.

“Ugh.”

A groan escaped Vikir's lips.

Even if the cotton swab was inserted just a little deeper into the ear, it hurt, but when the entire ear was torn and pulled out, the pain was indescribable.

Tsutsutsutsuts...

Basilisk's regenerative powers quickly healed the wound, but it would take time to regenerate the intricate organs within.

Shudder-

The deafening noise in his ears naturally messed with his balance and sense of distance.

Black Tongue lunged at the staggering Vikir, mouth mouth wide open all the way to the ears.

A smile filled with madness.

“Hathathathat- die, Night Hound!”

Vikir swung his sword at the maddened Black Tongue.

Jjeojeojeojeojeog!

The deafening slashes of the sword swung back and forth, left and right.

But none of them touched Black Tongue.

In fact, they flew in the wrong direction.

“Hathathat! You've made a complete fool of yourself!”

Black Tongue sneered at Vikir, who was swinging his sword at the wrong place.

...Kwang!

Black Tongue ferociously slashes at Vikir, his body more than twice as large as before due to his excitement.

The leeches covering his body were bubbling with his excitement.

Black Tongue slobbered and mocked atop Vikir's body.

“With all this commotion, it must be bad, maybe D'Ordume or Souaré will come. Heck, maybe the old man himself, Orca, will come to visit. How are you feeling, nervous, breaking out in a cold sweat, your eyes spinning?”

But.

“Uhm. That won't work.”

D'Ordume or Souaré might have been fine, but Orca is too much.

At the click of Black Tongue, Vikir replied briefly.

“I wanted leeches, so I invested some time, but I don't think I have time to play with you anymore.”

Vikir raised his left hand as Black Tongue gave him a questioning look.

“...!?”

Black Tongue's two eyes bulged.

The leather sack filled with the eggs of the new leeches was now in Vikir's hand.

“Goodbye, then.”

Vikir said a short farewell.

At the same time.

...Kwakwang!

The corridor shook.

The walls, floor, and ceiling of the corridor cracked, following the trajectory of Vikir's blows.

Jjeojeojeojeojeojeog!

An entire section of the corridor had been cut out. So was the flubber slime that coated the building's exterior walls.

“...?”

Black Tongue suddenly felt the floor he was on-or rather, the entire room-shift.

Like a slice of cake falling away, the entire space in which Black Tongue was standing was moving away from the corridor.

Nouvelle Vague is a castle in the depths of the sea. In the direction the piece was headed, of course, was the deepest depths of the sea, the seabed of the Great Deep.

Chwaaaaag-

The waters of the deep rushed in like crazy.

“Ugh!? Something like this! Just swim back!”

Black Tongue was very embarrassed at having suddenly fallen into the sea and was struggling with its limbs.

Then.

“...!”

Black Tongue looked up.

The hound preparing to leap at him, the seasoned veteran's gaze.

“That annoying guy....”

Vikir unleashed his reserved power at Black Tongue, who was pushed out to sea.

8th Baskerville Form. Black Sun.

Extremely concentrated aura forms a black sphere, sucking in everything in its path.

...Kuleuleuleuleuleug!

The approaching waters swirled in a vortex, and Black Tongue, trapped in the center, could barely squirm.

And then, with complete dominance, the hound delivered its final sentence.

“Get lost”

It was simple and clear.

Chapter 405

Jailbreaker (5)

◆

...Flash!

The slash fired by Vikir is launched toward the center of the vortex.

The black pillar created by the aura stretched vertically.

“Aaahhhhhh-!”

The scream of Black Tongue became a mere foam in the water.

...Rumble!

The black bricks crumble like sponge blocks.

The black tongue caught at the end of the powerful plasma wave flew straight into the deep sea.

A whole section of the corridor he was standing on was torn off like a piece of cake and floated out of Nouvelle Vague's nature.

There's no way he'd survive being exposed to 10,000 meters of water pressure.

Even Black Tongue in the realm of superhumans wouldn't have the strength to survive.

Slurp...

A transparent membrane began to descend before his eyes.

Brigadier Flubber's mucus coats the entirety of Nouvelle Vague's nature.

Whenever a hole is made in the castle, the mucus is spread out to prevent water from entering.

A coating of mucus has formed in the corridor that Vikir cut.

The water flow slowed significantly, and soon the floor was revealed.

Trickle, trickle, trickle...

The remaining seawater flowed down the slope of the corridor and down the spiral staircase.

Vikir stood on the wet stone floor and peered through the transparent membrane.

Just then.

“...!”

Vikir's crimson eyes, visible through his wet bangs, narrowed.

Something was approaching.

From beyond the darkness of the deep, something huge was coming toward him.

With insane speed!

[Gua-aaaaaah!]

Black tongue! No, what is 'supposed' to be Black Tongue!

It was no longer in human form.

It was an extremely elongated creature with countless leeches clinging to it, technically resembling a sea serpent or deep-sea eel.

It bared its razor-sharp teeth in front of a crushed, melted face.

It swam at a terrifying speed, rushing toward Nouvelle Vague, or more precisely, toward Vikir's area.

Upon closer inspection, Vikir realized it was not Black Tongue.

'Black Tongue is dead, and that must be Asmodeus in true form.'

Asmodeus the Magic Sword sucked all the blood from the dead Black Tongue, whose lungs burst under the pressure of the deep sea.

Using its desires and thoughts as nourishment, it regained its true form before it dried up.

[Gua-aaaaaahh!]

The sea serpent, a grotesque creature that could not be found anywhere else in the world, opened its mouth.

Gums and teeth sprouted haphazardly, left, right, and center, in full bloom.

Vikir clicked his tongue.

“This is how swords that eat their masters....”

Beelzebub resonated in his right hand.

Vikir stretched out a finger and snapped the hilt of Beelzebub's sword.

“Don't even dream.”

At the same time, Night Hound's eyes glow red.

Baskerville 8th Form. Black Sun.

Eight teeth circle the sphere, crushing everything in their path.

Asmodeus, sucked in, lets out a grotesque scream and twists and shudders, but cannot escape the fate of being dragged into the center of the black sun.

Ppageujag! Wagigigigig!

With a loud crash, the sound of something shattering was heard.

Vikir could tell by the sensation in his hands that he was controlling the Eight Teeth.

The magic sword Asmodeus had been completely shattered.

And then.

The Black Sun sank, and within it was the shattered remains of the sword, broken into nine pieces.

Silence. The frenzied rampage of a moment ago was nowhere to be seen.

They sink silently, wordlessly, row by row, toward the darkness of the deep, like the remains of a shooting star that has fallen into the sea and cooled.

“...The dog that bites its master is boiled.”

Vikir murmured coldly as he watched the sinking remains of the sword.

It was a truth Vikir knew all too well from his own experience.

In the end, one of the Seven Swords, Asmodeus, sank into the depths of the sea in nine pieces.

It had been lost forever.

The Seven Swords were now six, with one destroyed.

'But I can't say for sure. It's a sword with a strong life force, so it might still be alive.'

But is there a human who can pick it up and use it?

On this point, Vikir was skeptical.

It would be a waste, but it was impossible to handle more than two swords anyway.

Vikir shook off any lingering regrets about the sunken Asmodeus.

Instead, Vikir chose to focus on the actual harvest.

“More than that, I finally have it.”

Vikir lifted his left hand.

It was a thick leather hilt, quite heavy.

He opened the pouch and found it filled with dark eggs.

These are the egg sacs of sea leeches, black eggs that are commonly found on the carapace of snow crabs.

The tertiary egg membrane, which forms a sac within the strong foreskin until the leech larvae inside hatch, is hard and elastic and not easily broken.

'So this is a variant that Black Tongue put a lot of effort into?'

Vikir recalled the leech that had once attached itself to Kirko's stomach, gradually taking on Kirko's appearance.

Perhaps if it had been a little later, the leech would have grown to look exactly like Kirko.

“A secret weapon as good as the Blood Daylily.”

Vikir opened Andromalius's barrier and stored the leech eggs inside.

It would come in handy later.

'Now it is time to capture BDISSEM.'

The finale has entered the countdown.

Vikir left without hesitation.

To bring about the complete collapse of all of Nouvelle Vague's systems.

◆

Jjeoeoeoeoeog-

The symbol of Nouvelle Vague, the Gate of Good and Evil, opened.

...Kung! ...kung! ...kung! ...kung! ...kung! ...kung! ...kung!

A huge amount of seawater poured down like a waterfall from above, causing countless Iron Maidens to fall to the ground on the first floor.

And the gulper eels that had departed from the ground had just arrived through the deep sea dock on the 5th floor.

“Open the coffins!”

Lieutenant Colonel Bastille ordered, and the guards stepped forward and pulled the Iron Maidens open with a twist.

Inside, the prisoners were pulled out.

Prisoners who had traveled a journey through the depths of the sea.

Most of them lay in their coffins, dazed and drooling, or already dead.

Some prisoners were left in the form of a stew mixed with thick meat porridge and blood.

“Ugh, I guess this one will have to be fed to Brigadier General Flubber.”

“Oh, but he's alive, send him straight to the front lines! Ew, he just died.”

“Keep the bodies in one place. Send them to Brigadier General Flubber!”

“For crazy people, a whip is medicine! Bring them back to their senses!”

The sound of clubs and whips echoed around the room.

Then the surviving prisoners scrambled to their feet and made their way to the entrance.

This time, the number of new arrivals was quite large, so the guards were also busy.

Just then.

...Thud!

The last of the coffins fell.

The guards were about to approach it.

“Wait! Don't touch it!”

“We will escort it ourselves!”

A gravelly voice came from behind them.

All the guards, including Lt. Colonel Bastille, turned around in alarm.

There were Colonel D'Ordume and Colonel Souaré, who had just returned to Nouvelle Vague.

Colonel D'Ordume and Colonel Souaré grabbed the last Iron Maiden from either side and descended into the lower levels.

“She is an prisoner of Level 9 and will be transferred directly to Level 10 for her crimes.”

At those words, all the guards swallowed nervously.

There was no telling how dangerous this monster could be, and why the two wardens were so wary.

Meanwhile, Colonel D'Ordume spoke to Lieutenant Colonel Bastille.

“Warden Orca will be returning soon. Prepare a welcoming ceremony.”

“Yes!”

Lt. Colonel Bastille quickly turned his head.

At times like this, a good subordinate must be quick on his feet.

“Garam, where is Major Garam?”

Lt. Colonel Bastille searched for the bright young officer he had recently added to his entourage.

But Major Garam is nowhere to be seen.

There were too many new prisoners and the guards were too busy moving about to find him.

Then.

Lt. Colonel Bastille spotted a guard retreating backwards.

It was Captain Kirko Grimm, a young officer he'd heard of in his entourage.

“Hey! Captain Kirko!”

Kirko looked up at Bastille's call.

“Get Major Garam in here now! The Warden will be back soon, and we need to get ready for the welcome party, and while you're at it, make sure you have your eyes fixed on him!”

“Yes, I'll get him right away!”

Kirko nodded, knowing it was right.

It was just as well, since Garam had suddenly given her an order to go to the 5th floor and she was looking for an excuse to fulfill it.

She quickly broke away from the entrance and ran downstairs.

The road to the 5th floor. She had to pass through several corridors and bridges to get to the gulper eel kennel that Garam had told her about.

TICK-TICK-TICK

A dripping corridor.

As she passed through the empty corridors and over the arched bridge connecting spire to spire, she saw familiar faces.

She recognized them from her days as a junior guard.

“Aah! Captain Kirko! Salute!”

Old comrades saluting Kirko, who has now become their distant superior.

Then, one of the guards asked Kirko.

“Captain Kirko, are you also going to the 5th floor?”

“Um, what do you mean?”

“Well, Major Garam passed by here just now, too, and what did he say? He told me to hurry up and go near the kennels because I don't have to stand guard anymore....”

“...!”

For a moment, Kirko's expression hardened.

Something had really happened.

“Don't take the Major's word for it.”

With that, Kirko sprinted forward.

The two junior guards on guard duty quickly tried to stop Kirko.

“Now, wait a minute, Captain!”

“From here onwards is the area where people with the rank of major can enter autonomously...!”

But the guards didn't finish their sentence.

Kwakwang! Uleuleung-

A black corona rising out of the window in the distance.

A tremendous roar and shockwave shook the entire 5th floor.

Chapter 408

End game (2)

◆

Level 9. The prisoners imprisoned in the abyss of the 9th floor underground have been released.

When the BDISSEM restraints, the only means of controlling Level 9 beings, lost their power, they too ascended to the upper levels of Nouvelle Vague.

Each and every one of them was imprisoned here after serving more than a thousand consecutive life sentences while on land.

They are monsters whose very existence is a threat to the security of the Empire.

Not only do they possess great strength, but they also have diabolical brains.

When the prisoners of Level 9 joined the riot, the tide quickly turned.

“These guys are too strong!”

“Even the other prisoners are affected!”

“Damn it, those scums are in formation!”

“Don't get pushed back! If you get pushed back even once, it's over!”

“Focus on killing summoners and black mages!”

The guards gritted their teeth and fought back, but it was impossible to even hold their positions.

Aside from being strong, Level 9 also included many who were skilled in mercenary arts and military tactics, so the guards' siege was crumbling in real time.

Lt. Colonel Bastille shouted.

“Orca-nim! Where is Orca-nim!”

“He hasn't returned yet!”

At his subordinate's report, Lt. Colonel Bastille bit his lip so hard it bled.

His only hope at this point was with the two wardens, Colonel D'Ordume and Colonel Souaré.

Kwagigik-

D'Ordume, who had just killed a prisoner in front of him with the blade of his axe, strode forward, tearing up the battlefield.

“Don't be intimidated, they're nothing more than a bunch of weak and decaying cronies...!?”

But D'Ordume's words did not reach the end.

...Teog!

The axe blade that was slaughtering and crushing everything around it stopped spinning.

The face of the prisoner was visible, holding the scorching blade with his bare hands.

Seeing that face, D'Ordume also groaned softly.

“...Megidio. Level 9.”

The red-haired female prisoner smirked, fire blazing from her eyes.

As if she owed D'Ordume a favor.

Kwaang- hududug-

D'Ordume's face jerked to the side from the punch, spraying blood.

“Damn it. The troublesome bitches have escaped. What the hell happened to BDISSEM...!”

Taking a few steps backward, D'Ordume spat out a mouthful of blood and broken teeth and snarled.

Souaré, watching from the side, clicked her tongue.

“You're getting your ass kicked by a prisoner, you suck.”

But she couldn't bring herself to laugh at D'Ordume.

A girl with snow-white skin raised her fingernails and scratched at her cheeks fiercely.

“Oh, my- it's Snow White of the Killing Clan, yes, I knew you'd be the first to jump out. Of course, you'd be the first to come for me.”

Souaré lifted her bloodied face and gave a slow laugh.

A thick cigar burned brightly in her mouth, puffing out a thick cloud of smoke.

One by one, the prisoners of Level 9 gathered around the two wardens.

Each one was a villain who had gained a fearsome notoriety during their time on land.

Monsters who could have single-handedly destroyed a small country during the Warring States Period.

D'Ordume and Souaré's expressions grew more and more grim as they watched the scene unfold.

They stood with their backs to each other in the center of the encirclement and opened their mouths.

“...This is where I'm going to die.”

“It's not too bad. Nice weather. If only I could leave a nice corpse, and I did shave today.”

“Still, I'll die later than you. I'd like to see your ugly face crushed.”

“Hohoho – a moodless man. After nearly 30 years of fighting back and forth since we were junior guards as youths, this is the last thing you say to each other?”

“Hmph, did you expect a confession then?”

“I might have expected a little?”

“...?”

“Hohoho- joke~”

After finishing their conversation, D'Ordume and Souaré summoned all their strength.

Udeudeug! Udeudeug! Udeug!

D'Ordume's entire body was covered in dark iron scales.

Blade-like teeth hang beneath the elongated snout.

D'Ordume's already large size increases several times over, revealing his true form as a fierce saltwater crocodile.

Souaré, too, manifests both dwarven and elven blood coursing through her veins.

Her ears pricked up and her senses sharpened.

At the same time, her body temperature began to rise to a temperature that could melt metal.

Level 9's demons began to flee like fish out of water.

“Oooh, D'Ordume, I've been waiting for this day to kill you!”

“Souaré, I will cut off your legs for trampling on me!”

“Orca! Bring me Orca, you rascals!”

The guards desperately covered D'Ordume and Souaré, the key to winning or losing the battle.

“Support our two wardens!”

Lieutenant Colonel Bastille led the senior guards forward.

He wielded a large two-handed greatsword and herded the Level 9 prisoners into a circle.

“Well done, Bastille! Buy us a little time!”

D'Ordume exclaimed through gritted teeth, having just decapitated a prisoner from Level 9.

Covered in prisoners' blood, he was like one giant demon.

Kwakwakwakwakwakwang!

D'Ordume swung his tail, and the stalactites around him shattered.

Heavy chunks of stone flew in all directions, slamming into the prisoners.

“Ooooooooh!”

D'Ordume extended the axe blades on his forearms to their limits.

A black saltwater crocodile whose entire body is armed with an ax blade.

The hard, razor-sharp scales that covered its entire body tightened, transforming its appearance into something like an Evil God that had descended to earth to kill.

“Die, scum!”

With a thunderous roar, D'Ordume began to spin.

Death Roll.

A crocodile's signature hunting move.

A technique that involves biting down on an opponent and rotating their entire body to tear off chunks of flesh.

But when it was used by D'Ordume, its destructive power was extraordinary.

Kwa-kwakwakwakwakwakwakwang!

Scales sprouted from D'Ordume's entire body, along with six massive pairs of axe blades.

The aura that coated the tips of those blades also elongated, forming a guillotine-like shape.

A black vortex engulfed everything.

Everything sucked in was shattered and crushed.

The huge slashing whirlwind lay horizontally and swept the ground, swaying back and forth like a snake thrown onto a grill.

A glancing blow would dismember them, and a solid hit would kill them.

“Aaaahhhhh! Colonel D'Ordume has used a Death Roll!”

“Dodge! He can't even recognize his allies in that state!”

“Push the prisoners in! Just hold the line!”

“Stay in position and you won't be dragged!”

D'Ordume's special move was a threat not only to the prisoners, but also to the guards.

Even the vicious Level 9 prisoners ducked to the side to avoid the whirlwind of strikes that D'Ordume unleashed.

Kwa-deudeudeudeudeug!

The black vortex shears away and crushes any stalactites or boulders that stand in its way, turning them into a flat surface.

The stalactites that took the brunt of the aura storm are shattered and turned to sand, and the large, chunky boulders have gaping gouges in their sides.

All the prisoners stepped back and sideways at the sheer power of the blow, which altered the interior terrain so drastically.

...But.

Among the prisoners stampeding on both sides, there was a person standing still and alone.

A man in a tattered guard's uniform.

A silver Rose of Sharon, symbolizing Major, can be seen pinned to his chest.

The unidentified Major wears his hat brim deeply pressed down.

He stood still, unmoved by the Death Roll of D'Ordume coming straight at him.

“Hey! Are you out of your mind! Major, what the hell are you doing, get out of here!”

“Haha! You're killing your own guards, D'Ordume!”

The shouts of prisoners and guards rained down on him from the ebbing crowd.

But he stood still, his eyes fixed on the storm of charges that was closing in on him.

Ttang-geulang-

Eventually, a silver Rose of Sharon flower fell off and rolled on the floor.

He was about to rip off his chestplate.

...Screech!

From top to bottom. He brought his arm down vertically.

Kwa-kwang!

An arm that had only moved once. And a small blade sprouted from his wrist.

But it came down like a bolt of lightning, slicing through the body of D'Ordume, who had been flying straight at it.

Ujijijig!

D'Ordume's head, which had smashed into the ground, bounced off the ground once more.

Kung...

That was the end.

A single strike. With a single swipe, D'Ordume lay on the ground, covered in blood.

A moment of silence descended upon the abysmal Nouvelle Vague.

Ppodeug- ppodeug- ppodeug-

Amidst the eerily cold and eerie silence, the only sound that could be heard was the sound of the man wiping the blood from his sword with the lapel of his uniform.

Overwhelming.

The aura emanating from him seemed to consume everything on the battlefield.

Every living thing in Nouvelle Vague held its breath in horror at the sight of this crimson charisma, shaped like a large, monstrous dog.

With that, the man stepped forward with a military booted step and stomped on the head of the defeated D'Ordume.

“ ...I'm the kind of person who makes sure I pay my debts.”

And with that, Night Hound was once again in Nouvelle Vague.

Chapter 415

End game (9)

◆

...Grumble!

The clash between Vikir and Orca smashed and crumbled everything in its path.

Regardless of whether something was touched by human hands or not, it was an equal ending.

Mountains, hills, outer walls, watchtowers, shafts, piers... all collapsed.

And solitary confinement was one of them.

Kwaleuleuleuleuleuleuleug-

Numerous solitary confinement cells collapsed. Everything, nothing left.

Kwagig- peopeong!

Each time one of Souaré's strange structures, such as a cell or a mold, collapsed, skeletal mummies would emerge from within.

...Only one man survived: Marquis de Sade.

The one human being that even the harsh conditions of Level 9 could not contain.

In fact, his presence was so great that it was rumored that the Nouvelle Vague existed solely to imprison Marquis de Sade.

...Jeez!

Vikir took a step backwards at the creepy sensation that shot through his body.

It felt like countless snakes were licking his entire body.

He felt this even though they hadn't made eye contact and were just looking at him.

'...I should have known it when I heard the name Angajumang.'

As he had suspected, the identity of 'Old Man Angajumang' was none other than the Marquis de Sade.

The warmonger who had once incited 47 families to stage a coup, the madman who wanted to return to the days of war, when only the strongest could survive.

He was free again.

“Pushishishi- It's been a while since I've moved my body.”

Marquis de Sade moved his skinny arms back and forth.

Each twist of the joint made a dull noise, like something popping and breaking.

Then.

“...Grandfather.”

Professor Sadi, next to me, called out to Marquis de Sade.

Her voice trembling slightly, unlike her.

Sadi and Sade.

“Is that you, Sadi? Oh, dear. You've grown up so much since I last saw you.”

“Hohoho- I went to great effort to save my grandfather, but you'll still be nice to me, won't you?”

“No matter how, come here and hug this old man.”

Sadi staggered to her feet, covered in blood, and hugged Marquis de Sade.

Marquis de Sade, too, smiled warmly and stroked Sadi's hair.

“Thank God you're alive, my dear.”

“I'm glad my grandfather is safe.”

“I thought our family line was dead, but now there's a day of sunshine.”

“What? I'm not looking for a man.”

“I'm only saying that because I'm thinking of meeting a woman.”

Sadi and Marquis de Sade were laughing heartily and chatting.

The atmosphere was so peaceful and relaxed that, for a moment, one might mistake it for a café terrace in the middle of a quiet morning.

But the peacefulness was short-lived.

“You finally crawled out, Angajumang.”

Orca growled, his voice like boiling water.

Marquis de Sade turned his head, a bored expression on his face, and met Orca's gaze.

“Long time no see, old Orca. You live so long without dying.”

“That's not what I want to hear from you.”

Orca immediately picked up his club.

He swung it with all his might at the Marquis de Sade.

“Oh, you're going to persecute an old man, unarmed and empty-handed? That's really too much.”

Marquis de Sade smirked and picked up the whip from the floor.

“Granddaughter, I'll borrow your whip.”

And.

Peopeong- chalalalag!

He swung it back at Orca's flying club.

The heavy iron on the tip of Orca's club met the heavy iron on the tip of Marquis de Sade's whip.

...Kwakwang!

A loud explosion erupted, too loud to be believed to be metal on metal.

Sparks and shards of aura scattered in all directions, upsetting the already devastated landscape once more.

Kwakwang! Kwang! Ujijijijijig! Peopeong! Peong! Uleuleung...

With each stroke of the club and whip, the landscape cracked, rejoined, twisted, minced, and then cracked, crumbled, and shattered again.

Surprisingly, the power and spirit radiated by the Marquis de Sade was not at all inferior to that of Orca.

Who would have thought he'd spent the last few decades in solitary confinement on the 9th floor of the Nouvelle Vague?

“....”

Orca wrapped his trembling arms around himself and lowered his posture.

Marquis de Sade looked down at him, then opened his mouth.

“...Yes, I remember that day. It's been more than 40 years.”

'The 47 Man Riot'.

An unprecedented event that occurred when the Empire had just been unified.

It was led by 47 people, but each of them was the head of a single family, which is why it's also known as the 47 Families Rebellion.

They rebelled against the empire and stormed the Imperial Palace, coming close to beheading the emperor.

The official reason given was that they wanted the Imperial Throne, but...

“Actually, they didn't care about the throne at all. Pushishi-”

Marquis de Sade had rebelled for one reason only.

'Fun'.

Since the Empire had been united, there had been no more large-scale wars, no more hundreds of thousands dying a day, no more blood-and-guts fights with the strongest.

Power was no longer something to be wielded at will, and revenge was no longer something to be taken when wronged.

Everything was done according to laws and rules, and the emphasis was on getting things done as peacefully and bloodlessly as possible.

Marquis de Sade hated this change bitterly.

The days of war, killing, plunder, revenge, and the struggle of strength against strength.

A time of endless blood and violence, when only the strongest could survive and prove their lives were worth living.

“I loved those days, those people, those times... pushishishi....”

Marquis de Sade, who had lived his entire life in such a state of warfare, could not adapt to the dull and boring era he was suddenly thrust into at the end of his life.

Or rather, he hadn't had the heart to adapt in the first place.

“Well, whatever. So I stirred things up. A riot. It was fun for a while, yeah. I'm sure the world hasn't been the same since. It's a boring place again, and I can tell by the state of the children who are admitted here. They've been bred for peace and laziness.”

Marquis de Sade shook his head as if he was disgusted.

“So I thought it might be better for me to spend some time in solitary confinement here at Nouvelle Vague, to clear my head and organize my thoughts.”

“ ...Why would someone who did that crawl back out now?”

Orca asked.

Marquis de Sade looked at Orca with a childlike gaze.

“Well, I hear things have gotten quite interesting on the surface lately.”

“....”

Orca's already stiff expression hardened even more.

This was one thing he didn't want to be found out about.

The current state of affairs on the surface of the world was something that Marquis de Sade must never know.

Orca had seen the world before returning here to Nouvelle Vague. He saw how it had changed.

And Marquis de Sade had seen it, too, in those eyes. He saw it.

There were things everywhere that Marquis de Sade would have loved to see, things that would have kept his interest piqued and insatiable.

War, killing, slaughter, blood, violence, a brute force world where only the strong survive.

The fiercest days of the Warring States Period.

The greatest, hottest, most violent times, when the great Black Mage Tzersi or the great Swordsman Ornati lived.

An era of great war comparable to the heyday of the Warring States Period is coming.

“Pushishishi! This was such a shameful thing in my later years that my blood got hot. It's been a while since I wanted to go outside? Can you help me, my dear?”

“Of course, Grandpa. I'll escort you to the ground.”

Marquis de Sade looked back at his granddaughter, Sadi, and spoke in a humorous tone.

It was clearly a friendly conversation between the grandchildren, but somehow a terrifying madness was felt in their smiles.

At that time.

...Kung!

Orca struck the ground once with his club.

“You'll never get out. You guys.”

Orca's eyes dripped with hatred as he turned to face the criminals.

“Social Evil. It is my responsibility to prevent the chaos and disorder created by your very existence and the anxiety of the common people. Even if I die, you can't leave this place.”

“Pushishishi- Come on, my friend. What do you think your life is worth?”

Major General Orca and Marquis de Sade began to face off once more.

“I'm not letting you go. Never. Ever.”

“Pushishishi – and you don't even have Winston to assist you this time.”

Orca raised his heavy club.

Marquis de Sade curled his whip as well, posturing as if he were about to perform a sword duel.

Jjeojeog- jjeojeojeojeog-

The air and ground around them shattered like glass as the two ferocious forces collided.

Meanwhile, just a few feet away from the center of the maelstrom, Aiyen asked Vikir.

“What do you think we should do, run away?”

“...No. In a way, this is good timing.”

Vikir shook his head.

Maybe he could take advantage of their fight.

'Timing. I have to get the timing right.'

The confrontation between Orca and Marquis de Sade was indeed frightening.

Simply glaring at each other and exuding momentum is enough to warp the terrain, but what happens when they unleash their full power?

...The results were starting to play out in real time right now.

Kwakwang!

Orca kicked the ground and rushed forward.

Marquis de Sade chuckled and took a step back.

Orca charging like an angry killer whale and Marquis de Sade flying like a pale ghost.

Both of them were holding strong power in their hands, as if they were trying to win the battle with one blow.

...Flash!

Orca channeled all of his aura into the tip of his club.

A tidal wave of energy washed over Marquis de Sade.

Kwakwakwakwakwakwa...

Marquis de Sade shortened his whip.

And he rotated the aura that was previously immobilized by the BDISSEM restraints.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsuts...

Combination. The explosive power and momentum of a punch, a technique that would settle the match in a single blow, was embodied in the whip.

Just then.

“Now!”

Vikir stepped between them.

Kuleuleuleuleug! Kwaleuleung!

8th Form of Baskerville. The Black Sun fell between Orca and Marquis de Sade.

“...!?”

“...!?”

Orca and Marquis de Sade were greatly disconcerted by the sudden turn of their one-on-one fight into a three-way battle, but they could not take back the blow that had already cost them their lives.

Then, a tidal wave of black from Orca's club, a serpent of strikes from Marquis de Sade's whip, and Vikir's Black Sun descended upon the same spot in unison.

And there was one who moved swiftly ahead of them.

“West, take it!”

It was Aiyen.

She stretched out her hands with all her might.

Toward the blue glowing orb in front of them, Poseidon!

Kwakwakwang!

A ferocious explosion occurred near the root, and the ground shook in the aftermath.

Ujijijig!

Poseidon was pulled out of the ground.

It dropped from the ground like an onion with roots sprouting out of it, and soon rolled tumbling down the slope.

Toward the very spot where Orca and Marquis de Sade were gathering for Vikir's blow!

At the same time.

...Flash!

A blinding light and a tremendous roar erupted.

Aiyen barely covered her ears.

Vikir felt his eardrums burst and blood flow.

“Kuhugh!?”

“Kuahh!?”

The explosion was so loud that even D'Ordume and Souaré, who were watching, fell to the ground clutching their ears.

And at the same time.

...! ...! ...! ...!

After being hit by three different types of shockwaves, Poseidon's state began to change.

Jjeojeog-

The sound of an eggshell cracking.

...It sounded like something was hatching.

Chapter 417

Goodbye Nouvelle Vague (1)

◆

...Kwakwang! Rumble!

The entire Nouvelle Vague prison shook violently.

Vikir and Aiyen raced down the spiral staircase on Bakira's back.

[Keong! Keong! Keong!]

Bakira's sprint was faster than it had been in his prime, significantly reducing the time it took to climb the floors.

Chwaaaag-

A huge tidal wave surged in front of them.

“Oh no, this must be a flooded corridor!”

“This is the shortcut. Break through!”

At Vikir's words, Aiyen nodded and loaded an arrow.

Peo-peong!

The arrow flew in a straight line, tearing a gaping hole in the waves.

Bakira leaped over the ring of water like a circus act, kicking the ground beneath the waves where the arrow had cut through and leaping again.

...Thud!

Through the flooded corridor and landing on a half-destroyed bridge pier, Bakira continued to run.

Off to the side, the blue pillar of fire continued to rise, burning away at the Gate of Good and Evil.

“We're on the 5th floor now!”

“Yep. There's an gulper eel kennel on this floor.”

“Do you think there are any eels left?”

“Last time I checked, there were quite a few of them. Even if they escaped first, they couldn't have used all of them.”

Vikir was right.

There were still a few gulper eels in the holding tank, with debris and water raining down from the ceiling.

There was chaos all around, as many of the prisoners and guards had already escaped.

There was blood everywhere and bodies floating around.

It was easy to see that there had been a terrible fight for the gulper eel.

'It's a good thing I sent those who would escape first to the fifth floor.'`

Vikir had ordered that as many people as possible who were worth saving were to wait on the fifth floor before entering.

He'd even gone so far as to forge the orders, so there must have been quite a few people on the fifth floor.

They were already on the fifth floor at the time of the rampage, so they had a good chance of getting out safely.

“It's a miracle there are any eels left.”

Aiyen picked up a fishing hook and rope and jumped into the fish tank himself, catching a large gulper eel.

Chua-ak.

She twisted the jumped eel's mouth open with a grimace and said.

“Husby. Are you ready for this?”

“I'm ready.”

Vikir nodded.

But nevertheless, Aiyen opened her mouth once more.

“The land has changed. It's not the world as my husby knows it anymore.”

“I know the general picture.”

“...?”

Aiyen tilted her head.

The world was different before and after Vikir's imprisonment in Nouvelle Vague.

How could Vikir know that?

A newspaper, a story told to him by a new prisoner, or an informant he'd kept to himself?

Aiyen looked back at Vikir with a puzzled expression, but Vikir didn't really have an answer.

Instead, Vikir was thinking about the world before he had returned.

Memories of that day always haunt his nightmares.

How could he forget that devastating season when 98% of humanity was wiped out?

The sky suddenly torn apart and the flames that flowed from the cracks.

The countless drops of fire that fell like snakes and showers.

The torrential rain that lasted for 150 days, the Rain of Fear.

A terrible weather event that turned the world's forests into deserts and its lakes into bottomless pits.

Even after the dead have closed their eyes, the sounds of the dead wandering the parched wastelands, howling, and the unborn gasping for their dying breath, will haunt their dreams.

A time when nothing could be promised or assured.

A long rainy season that sentenced humanity to destruction.

'...It is about to begin.'

Vikir could already see that the gates of destruction were about to open.

The changes on the earth now are but fresh blood, mere signs and omens.

They are merely the demons warming up before the real game begins.

So Vikir has arranged all of this in advance.

Slowly, patiently, and thoroughly.

Now it was time to give the demons a good kicking.

“The volcano is about to erupt.”

Poseidon has hatched, and it's time to begin its ascent to the heavens.

It was the beginning of the Great Nouvelle Vague Eruption.

“We must get out of here before then.”

“But why did you explode the Nouvelle Vague?”

“Showers of fire. To counter the rainy season of fear.”

“...?”

Aiyen scratched her head.

But Vikir had no answer for her this time.

He merely replayed in his mind over and over again the thought of the Gates of Destruction, a great rain of fire that would last for 150 days.

“Now that Poseidon has hatched, the climate will change dramatically. All that remains is to wait and see.”

With those words, Vikir reeled in the gulper eel.

Kwakwakwang! Uleuleuleung! ...cheolsseog!

Everywhere, earthquakes rumbled and collapses fell.

The rising tide flooded the castle hour after hour.

The roar and crash of the waves was faintly interrupted by the shouts of the prisoners and guards upstairs.

Aiyen stood in front of the faint remnants of the flubber doors, dragging an gulper eel with her.

“Let's get out!”

“....”

Vikir took a step forward.

...Just then.

“Wait.”

A voice stopped Vikir and Aiyen.

“...?”

“...!”

Aiyen wiggled one eyebrow.

Vikir's expression hardened slightly as well.

Captain Kirko Grimm. She was standing in the corner of the kennel.

Her uniform was torn to rags, revealing her scarred and bare body.

He noticed that her beloved sword, which she had always honed, was broken in half.

Red blood oozed from every part of her body, staining the waters around her red.

“....”

“....”

Vikir and Kirko stood facing each other.

It was the first time they had ever shown their bare faces.

There was a sharpness in Kirko's gaze.

She asked Vikir pointedly.

“Are you a prisoner?”

“....”

Vikir didn't answer.

Why she hasn't escaped yet is unknown.

But if she tries to escape, we'll have to take her down by force.

...However.

“If you ride any current, you'll die before you can escape. Go back out the door on the left and take current 3021.”

Kirko showed an unexpected reaction.

There are thousands of currents that can carry an gulper eel from the fifth floor.

Only one of them is a circulation current that connects to the surface.

All the rest were trap currents that would keep them at the bottom of the sea for hundreds of years.

Vikir asked.

“Why are you telling me this?”

“....”

Kirko spoke after a long silence.

“I saw you kill Black Tongue.”

“...!”

Kirko took off his guard's hat.

Then, in a dry, clear voice, Kirko asked.

“What happened to the real Garam?”

The question was cold and sharp, like a stab to the lungs.

Vikir answered in a flat tone.

“Dead.”

“...When.”

“Two years ago, during the riots in Sakkuth. Saving you when you were unconscious.”

“...Where's the body?”

“Buried.”

“....”

Kirko was still staring at Vikir, her eyes emotionless, her gaze unwavering.

Her lips curled again.

“Did he say any final words?”

For a moment, Vikir's mind flashes back to Garam's last words.

He had muttered these words before he died.

'I wanted to show that... girl... the outside world... and... her....'

That was Garam's last words.

Vikir complied.

“He wanted to show you the outside world.”

A moment.

“...!”

Kirko's pupils, which had not even moved until now, shook violently.

Vikir remembered Garam's long-burned diary.

At the end of her diary, Garam wrote that he always wanted to get out of here with Kirko.

Even though Garam was now forever unable to leave Nouvelle Vague.

And then.

Tag-

The sound of Kirko's footsteps broke Vikir's reverie.

She turned around.

And walking forward.

It was not in the direction of the escape route.

Kwakwang- uleuleung...

Dead land with huge piles of stones and waterfalls.

“Aren't we getting out?”

Vikir asked, and Kirko answered without looking back.

“I'm not leaving. This is where I was born and raised.”

She paused after she finished speaking.

Then, after a long silence, she turned her head slightly to the side and said in a whisper.

“...Goodbye.”

It was such a small sound that it was barely audible, drowned out by the roar of the tidal wave crashing next to her.

Unable to waste any more time, Vikir forced himself into the eel's mouth.

Aiyen cuts the rope, and the gulper eel is carried out of the castle by the current.

The gulper eel is quickly moving away from the ocean current.

With that, Vikir and Aiyen left Nouvelle Vague and headed for the surface.

“....”

The castle is crumbling and falling apart. Seawater rushing in from everywhere.

Kirko was the only one left.

She could see a man's face in her mind.

A man from the surface.

A man who looked and acted friendly.

But no matter how she looked at him, he was not fit to be a guard.

...And who seemed to think that one day he might return to the ground from which he came.

So she didn't want to stick around.

Such a weak guy.

But what is this?

The guy who seemed like he was going to return to the ground at any time ended up not being able to do so.

Tug-

She took it off and threw the hat in her hand onto the flooded floor.

And finally, she lowered her stinging gaze and spoke.

“.....Stupid Garam. You're such an idiot.”

That was the end of it.

Soon, a huge amount of sea water rushed in and completely filled the castle.

Kwakwakwakwang! Kkuleuleuleuleug...

And just like that, Nouvelle Vague was buried beneath the pitch black water.

Forever.

Chapter 418

Goodbye Nouvelle Vague (2)

◆

Kuleuleuleuleuleug...

The abyss. A vast void.

The blackened vision makes the passing of the mass of water bubbles only audible.

Vikir and Aiyen's gulper eel shook violently before emerging into the center of the deep sea.

Deudeudeudeudeu...

For a moment, they thought they were in the wrong current because of the violent currents churning in all directions, but this was actually the only one that was working.

Compared to the other currents, which are initially stable, this current 3021 is violently churning and unstable, but it eventually becomes the safest route.

Soon, the faint light from the gulper eel's skin began to illuminate the surroundings.

The pitch blackness brightened a bit, and through the transparent skin, they could see the outside of the deep sea.

Uleuleung...

Nouvelle Vague was completely submerged.

Shrouded in flames and steam from the volcano's interior, the Nouvelle Vague looks precariously close to exploding at any moment.

This is probably because the Gate of Good and Evil in the ceiling of Nouvelle Vague is preventing the volcano from erupting.

As a result, the Nouvelle Vague currently resembles a champagne bottle that has been shaken to the limit.

The moment the top cap, the Gate of Good and Evil, is destroyed, an enormous explosion and rising current will occur.

The explosion and the seawater that flows into the resulting cavity is heated by geothermal heat and expands, creating a primary pillar of fire and a secondary pillar of water on a massive scale.

It will start in the deepest strata of the sea floor, penetrate the seafloor, and rise up high, passing over the surface of the water and into the air, very high up.

“And it will be powerful enough to create extreme weather on the surface.”

Aiyen nodded at Vikir's words.

She was currently tugging at the fishing hook and rope hanging from the lip of the gulper eel, keeping it balanced.

In other words, it is the role of the coachman who drives the carriage.

Vikir was about to grab the line, too, when Aiyen, who had a good sense, felt something.

“I think there's something attached to the eel's tail.”

“...?”

Vikir looked back.

Sure enough, there was something dangling from the tip of the gulper eel's tail.

It was dark and the current was too strong to see exactly what it was.

...But even without looking too closely, the thing started to move closer and closer to Vikir.

Pulling on the eel's tail, the creature slowly approached towards him.

“...!”

Vikir's eyes widened.

It was Marquis de Sade holding the gulper eel's tail!

He even had a Sadi at his side.

Next, Marquis de Sade grabbed the gulper eel's body and crawled up to its mouth and crawled in.

“Puh-ha! The water pressure almost crushed my bones. Pushishishishi... But after being in solitary confinement for a long time, I'm starting to get used to it.”

“Greetings, Night Hound. It's shameless, but I'd like a free ride~”

Marquis de Sade laughed heartily.

Even Sadi, who has lost her mind, also lies down like a mollusk and laughs.

The gulper eel was already large enough to carry a dozen people, so adding Sadi and Sade wouldn't cause much trouble.

“I'll give you a ride if you behave.”

“Oh no. I feel sorry for the young fellow. I don't think I can stay quiet.”

At Vikir's words, Marquis de Sade shook his head with a sad expression.

It didn't take Vikir long to realize why he was saying this.

“...!”

Something was furiously chasing after the gulper eel as it slowly drifted along the current.

Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa-

A terrifying sound began to emanate from beyond the blackness.

At first glance, it sounded like a ship's bellows, but it was far too high-pitched for that.

Could this be the voice of the legendary Siren?

Even the eels that had been swimming around twisted in pain.

This unidentifiable sound filled the void of the sea floor.

Vikir sensed that the creator of the sound was near.

“I think it's Orca.”

Marquis de Sade smirked.

Then, beyond the transparent flesh of the eel's body, something massive emerged.

A body with a black luster, white spots clearly visible even through the darkness.

Muscles packed tightly throughout, powerful dorsal fins, forearms and legs bared beneath a tattered coat of fur.

Orca. He transformed into a strange body and once again blocked Vikir's path.

“ ...Are you a member of the Killer Whale (Orca) type Beastman?”

Vikir spoke to himself in a low voice.

Just as D'Ordume had transformed into the form of a saltwater crocodile earlier, Orca had a similar constitution.

He grasped the chain and club at the end of his long tail, which had slipped out of his coat, with a clawed hand.

“SADE! You're never going outside!”

Orca's hissing voice was clear even in these murky depths.

In the midst of this hopeless sea, Orca had met his match.

The worst of all fears had come true.

Marquis de Saad chuckled.

“On land, maybe, but underwater, it's suicide to take on that old man.”

“...What do you propose?”

“Well, shamelessly, I'd like to ask you what you think?”

Marquis de Sade was secretly indicating that he would follow Vikir's lead.

Vikir said plainly.

“You owe me a debt. How will you repay me?”

“Pushishishi....”

Marquis of Sade laughed wordlessly, then held up three fingers.

“The people of the Sade family will repay a favor threefold, and our enemies three thousandfold. You owe me one life, so I will repay you with three.”

“....”

“Give me three names of those you wish to kill. Whoever they are, I will kill them for you.”

Marquis de Sade narrowed one eye at the end, saying, 'If only we can get out safely to the ground.'

Vikir nodded silently.

Jilkkeun-

With that, Vikir tied Sadi's whip around his waist.

Then he tied the other around Marquis de Sade's waist.

“Hold on to these.”

Vikir placed the middle of the whip in Aiyen's hand.

Sadi, immobilized by the after-effects of the demonization, asked.

“Are you going to out?”

“There is no other way.”

Vikir said, looking into Aiyen's eyes.

Aiyen looked back at Vikir with uneasy eyes.

“I'd rather go out, Husby.”

“You drive the eels, it's safer that way.”

“I don't want to be separated again. How did we ever get back together....”

“It's important to hold the line.”

Vikir spoke in a serious tone, and Aiyen bowed her head deeply.

Then she looked up, biting her lip so hard it bled.

“Never. I will never let go.”

“That's enough.”

Vikir stood up.

Then, through the mouth of the gulper eel, he threw himself into the deep.

To cross the final gateway to the surface.

◆

The pressure of the water at 10,000 meters was beyond his imagination.

Even Vikir's stats, the protection of the River Styx, and his body, which had reached the Supreme Realm, could not withstand it.

'I can see why the demons didn't cross this place until late in the War of Destruction.

A pressure that would crush an entire body just by being present.

It's like hundreds of elephants on an egg.

'This is why the Marquis de Sade asked for help.

Vikir glanced sideways.

He could see Marquis de Sade, with a whip tied around his waist, gasping for air.

Just then.

Huuuuk-

An invisible pressure began to distort the front.

A tidal wave. On the surface of the water, it would have risen to enormous heights, but under the sea, it was completely invisible.

Kwakwakwang!

A vision swirling with a roar.

Orca in the shape of a killer whale passes in front of him.

Ssaeaeg- ppeoeog!

Suddenly, his vision blurred red.

Vikir squinted, but it didn't stop his face from being crushed.

His skull felt like a grain of sand, the impact shattering his nose, cheekbones, and front teeth.

It was like taking a full-swinging warhammer to the center of the face.

'...Is it a drop of water?'

Orca was scooping up water from the distance with a wide, raked hand and throwing it back.

It flew like a cannonball, aimed at Vikir and Marquis de Sade.

However.

Peoeong!

Vikir stretched out his sword and sliced the flying water droplet diagonally.

Additionally, the orca's location was detected based on the direction and angle of the water droplet flying.

...Flash!

Decarabia on the chest narrowed its eyes and shot out a red light.

For a moment, the surroundings were illuminated.

“Oh. You can do that?”

[You think so little of me.]

A radius of a dozen meters lit up with the haughty glare of Decarabia.

Then he could clearly see Orca's figure in front of him.

Dressed in a warden's uniform and coat, he held a club in his hand.

It looked like a half-and-half killer whale and a human.

“Get lost!”

Orca swung the club in his hand.

A massive tsunami erupted, crushing the space around them.

But Vikir was confident.

“If I know the direction, I can stop it.”

The mana ebbed away, revealing Decarabia's true form.

Red Inverted Pentagram. Wailing Wall.

Although it consumes a lot of mana, its defense is a solid shield.

It blocked all of Orca's ranged attacks.

Kugugugung!

If anything, Orca's attacks only made Aiyen's gulper eel go faster and faster.

Vikir and Marquis de Sade, connected by whip rope, also rose upwards faster and faster.

“...These bastards.”

Orca eventually changed his attack method.

Close combat. The most primitive and surest way to attack: lunging in with a club and beating them down.

And that's what Vikir and the Marquis de Sade wanted, too.

A monstrous whale, tearing through the turbulent currents.

Vikir drew his magic sword, Beelzebub, and Marquis de Sade raised a sword of unknown origin to meet Orca.

The powers of the three came together once more.

Vikir's black sun, Marquis de Sade's serpentine aura, and the tsunami of Orca's club all came together in a fierce collision.

Kwakwakwakwakwa!

A giant whirlpool formed in the sea.

The sword trajectories of Vikir and Marquis de Sade formed the upper layer of the vortex, and the tsunami of Orca's club formed the lower layer, meeting in the center.

...Kwakwang! Kkwaleuleung!

With a thunderous crack, the shockwave stretched out in all directions, tearing the surrounding sea to shreds.

As the water and air reentered the empty space created by the ripping of the waves, violent currents formed, building up the space around them.

The pressure, raging in all directions, crushed and shattered everything, cliffs and rocks alike.

“...!”

A thick line of blood sprouted on Vikir's forehead.

His instincts, sharpened by having crossed so many lines of fire, were giving him a cold assessment of the current situation.

'Die.'

Never win.

As long as Orca is under the sea, it is no different from a god.

He can still breathe underwater, and he moves much faster with ever more powerful muscles.

He could shoot out sound waves to see everything for miles around, and he could unleash a tsunami without moving to take out his enemies at great distances.

Moreover, on this harsh sea floor, in an environment where everything was unstable, to stand against him was like a worm against a beast.

Marquis de Sade sensed it, too, and smirked.

'Is this going to kill me?'

'....'

Even before Vikir's regression, Marquis de Sade attempted to break out of Nouvelle Vague, only to be stopped and killed by Orca.

Even with Vikir by his side now, it seemed unlikely that fate could be reversed.

The wheels of causality were turning.

Vikir was just a mere mere mole standing in its way.

The moment.

“....”

“....”

Vikir and Marquis de Sade's gazes locked together.

As if in a pact, they both moved their hands to snap the whip at their waist.

“No!”

In the distance, Aiyen, who was driving the gulper eel, shouted, but it was too late.

The current rushed even more violently, pushing the gulper eel upward.

Those who must go must go, and those who must stay must stay.

At the same time.

“...!”

Orca felt something.

Two men who had chosen to remain in the depths of the sea.

The momentum of Vikir and Marquis de Sade had completely shifted.

It was sharp enough to make even the mighty Orca break out in a cold sweat.

...At that very moment.

“!?”

The balance between the three warriors in the darkness of the deep sea was shattered.

A strange thing that was difficult to explain rationally.

...It was, what can only be described as, luck.

Vikir, who had never been blessed with much luck in his entire life, could not help but feel somewhat bewildered.

...To properly explain this phenomenon, we need to go back a few seconds.

Kuleuleuleuleug! Kudeudeudeudeug!

A pillar of fire erupted when Poseidon was activated.

It was like a residual eruption from the condensation of volcanic power.

The intense heat surged as if it were going to explode, but it was blocked by the 'Gate of Good and Evil', the final gateway to the Nouvelle Vague, and was trapped and unable to escape until now.

But now.

One by one, the chains and pulleys securing the gate broke and destroyed, causing the Gate of Good and Evil to heat up to its limit.

...Ting! ...Ta-aang! ...Tuung!

All the chains connected to the Nouvelle Vague were broken.

Kabooom!

The Gate of Good and Evil was thrown up into the air like the cap of a champagne bottle that had been shaken to its limit.

The Gate of Good and Evil was blasted open by the immense pressure.

70 meters in diameter, 5 meters thick and weight 6535 tons. Made of a mythril and adamantium alloy, it flew like a bottle cap at the end of an exploding champagne stem.

And this huge and heavy lump of alloy, which had randomly and accidentally bounced away, ended up heading towards Orca, who was confronting him while turning his back on the true nature of Nouvelle Vague.

The direction of the wheel of fate is unpredictable.

...Peoeog!

Orca fell forward as this huge object passed by his head out of nowhere.

Red blood spurted out.

The monster whale was struck in the head by a sudden impact, and was quickly caught in the current and sank like a piece of trash.

“...?”

Marquis de Sade's mouth dropped open in disbelief.

But that was not the reaction he saw in Orca.

...Kwakwang!

The Gate of Good and Evil flew off into the distance, smashing into a corner of the cliff before rolling back down.

Kudeudeudeudeudeudeudeudeudeu-

With the Gate of Good and Evil broken through, Nouvelle Vague's downfall began in earnest.

A castle submerged in water.

The space between the black bricks began to glow red.

In the beginning, Nouvelle Vague was built by digging into the interior of an extinct volcano, and now that the volcano is active again, everything is over.

The Iron Fortress, a castle with a long history that has never shown any flaws, has now become like a cork blocking a bottle of champagne that is about to burst.

Its body is corroded and crumbling.

The great pillar of fire that broke through the Gate of Good and Evil was only the beginning.

The crackling pillar of fire soon turned blue at the base, and then expanded greatly in the second and third waves, instantly expanding in size.

...! ...! ...! ...! ...!

The explosion was so loud, far beyond the range of human hearing, that it seemed as if the entire ocean had been blown away.

It was the beginning of a great eruption that would easily surpass 10,000 meters deep and extend dozens of kilometers into the sky.

Chapter 421

How to Live as a Wandering Knight (2)

◆

Tuuuuuu-!

The sound of a horn rang out, announcing a monster invasion.

The entire town was in a panic.

It wasn't just a horde of bandits or a wildfire.

The enemy is monsters, not humans, and it's not a matter of stealing money, food, or shelter, but of immediate danger to their lives.

Moreover, the type of monster that is crossing the fence this time is a gnoll, a canine monster known for its large population and ferocity.

Grrrr...

Soon, bizarre things begin to flood into the town.

A voice that sounds like oil slowly boiling from a low temperature.

The sound of scratching in the parched earth.

Stooped back, vaguely bipedal walking, sharp teeth and claws, and hideously shiny eyes

A horde of gnolls, the most damaging species to humankind, has invaded the town.

The gnolls were also severely malnourished, their fur dry and lacking in shine.

Their eyes were bloodshot, and the saliva that dripped from their mouths reeked of greed.

The monsters are tired and weary of the Great Famine.

The ongoing drought has left them with nothing to eat or drink, and the wildfires that have raged across the empire have drastically reduced their living space.

The lesser monsters, unable to compete with the other monsters for food, have been forced to descend upon the human population in record numbers.

This group of gnolls here were swept away by the tide of fate.

Kyaaak-!

A gnoll began to ransack the house.

Cloth was torn, wood was broken. Everything that had been touched by human hands was being ravaged.

It stretched its long nose and tracked the freshest of the smells to the floor.

At that time.

...Kwang!

The closet door shattered, and a man burst out from inside.

“Hey, get away from me!”

The man raised a pitchfork and brought it down on Gnoll's head.

Kkig-

Gnoll was dead on the spot, with a shattered skull.

The problem was, it was followed by two, three, four, five, six... so many gnolls that it was pointless to count.

“Honey, run out the back door, go to the basement shed in the backyard!”

Before the man could finish his shout, the side door opened and a woman came running out with three children.

The man quickly caught up to her and ran after her.

Threatening the gnolls, who were excited by the smell of blood, with a pitchfork.

Backyard. A shed door to the basement is visible.

The man quickly opened the door and went inside with the woman.

Then.

“Uaaahhh- Mom!”

A scream erupted from behind them.

Before the man and woman could turn around, they realized who the scream belonged to.

Two children had entered the basement bunker, and where they all turned, there was a little girl who was just getting up after falling to the ground.

Her clothes were torn at the sides, and the blood was clearly visible staining them red.

“The youngest!”

The man shouted, but it was too late.

If they leave now, everyone will die. Closing this door as soon as possible is the only way to save his wife and the two remaining children.

What must it be like for a parent to give up their child right before their eyes?

“....”

The man and woman hesitated. Chewing on his lips, unaware that he was bleeding, he made a decision in that brief moment that he would regret no matter how many times he turned around in his life.

...BANG!

The door slammed shut. Reality is always unavoidable. And so it was with this closed door.

The girl cried out and fell to her knees, scratching at the door. So desperately that her fingernails were peeling off.

As her father had always nagged her, she should have put the nail sticking out of the side of the front door back in properly.

If only she had, she wouldn't have fumbled with her clothes on the nail just a moment ago.

But regret is always too late.

The girl cried out at the top of her lungs.

“Mom! Dad! Open up! I'll listen to you from now on! I won't cry, I'll eat less, I'll clean up after myself, and I won't fight with my sisters and brothers...!”

Unfortunately, it wasn't her parents and siblings who answered her plea, but the swarm of gnolls behind her.

Keuaaag-

They lunged at the girl in the lead.

Just as she was about to scream.

Peoeog-

A pitchfork stuck in the gnoll's mouth.

“Youngest, hurry!”

The man who had just opened the door fought off the gnolls.

The woman also came out carrying an armful of bricks from the walls of the warehouse and was glaring at the gnolls.

The father is strong. Of course, the mother too.

“Dad! Mom!”

The little girl ran backward, tears streaming down her face.

The father raised his pitchfork to face the gnolls.

But no matter how strong parents are, they are not stronger than the world around them.

Soon, the gnolls lunged at them, teeth and claws bared.

Buuk-!

Blood splattered as thick leather pants ripped open.

It was the beginning of a family's downfall.

...Just then.

Peoeog-

The father's feet grew lighter.

Gnoll's head, hanging from his pants, shattered like a watermelon.

“...Uh?”

The place where the father's blank gaze was directed was towards the front.

Flutter-

A ragged blood-red robe fluttered in the dry wind.

The matte black plate armor was making an unpleasant metallic sound.

The Wandering Knight. He appears out of nowhere, standing tall above the ground, facing the gnolls.

“...There, there. Who are you?”

The father asked, but the Wandering Knight did not answer.

Instead.

Kwag-

The long stick he was carrying on his back shifted in his hand.

Peoeong! Ppagag!

The heads of the gnolls around him exploded.

A blue spear blade was revealed within a piece of bandage that was torn with red blood.

The liquid aura that symbolized the Graduator was sticky, drawing a complex trajectory in the air.

Puff-puff-puff!

A movement without waste.

A skilled path forged by extreme battle experience.

It was the skill of a seasoned warrior who had seen countless battlefields.

The hood was lifted, revealing the face of the Wandering Knight.

Although he had a young face, he had a sense of authority and an appearance that was an appropriate mix of two things that are usually difficult to coexist.

His shoulders are broad like a bear's and his waist is lean like a wolf's.

His body was optimized for battle, except for the absence of his left arm.

Even with his one arm, he boasted ghostly spear skills.

A single swing of his spear killed at least one enemy and crippled more than one.

Peoeog! Peog! Udeudeug! Peo-eog!

The sound of mincing meat and bones all at once. In no time, the backyard was covered in blood.

But the gnolls' messy groans were no longer audible.

The one-armed Wandering Knight, who had neatly cleared away the group of monsters, brushed the blood off his spear.

At that time. There was a hand pulling open the door to the basement.

It was the girl who had almost never made it inside a moment ago.

She called out to the Wandering Knight.

“Mister! Who are you?”

“....”

“My name is Shammua, and I was wondering if you could tell me who my benefactor is?”

The Wandering Knight turned his head and looked back at the girl.

Whether it was fearlessness or gratitude, the girl's tears had been wiped away and she was looking at him with longing and curiosity.

The Wandering Knight was just about to open his mouth to say something.

Kyaaaaahhh-!

Grrrrr!

Kaung! Kaung!

The sound of gnolls screaming outside the fence.

Obviously, things aren't over yet.

The Wandering Knight took a short break and stood facing forward again.

And then.

A splatter!

The wooden fence shattered, and something huge burst into the backyard.

It was three times the size of a normal gnoll, its fur standing on end all over its body, stained an unusual black-green color.

Oil-like fluids were dripping from its bloodshot eyes, and a sickening stench wafted through the air.

<Poison Gnoll>

Danger Rating: A

Size: 3 meters

Found in: All continents

-Also known as 'Poison Gnoll' or 'Deadly Poison Gnoll'

This is an example of an abnormally evolved digestive system among gnolls.

Most gnolls feed on carcasses, but the poison gnoll has evolved the ability to accumulate poison in its skin and saliva from the rotting flesh of its prey in its stomach.

There is one gnoll in a colony of more than 300 individuals, and most seem to fulfill the role of leader.

Poison Gnoll. A variant of the gnoll swarm. They possess a strength and ferocity that no normal gnoll can match.

The family, thinking they were safe, cowered to the ground in fear at the sight of the Poison Gnoll's fearsome form.

However.

The one-armed Wandering Knight merely laughed dryly.

“...Poison Gnoll. Long time no see.”

His voice was dry and short.

He radiated a blue aura that wavered like a tidal wave with his only arm.

The spear he held tightly rolled up did not budge.

Just before the girl behind him closed the door, drawn by her mother's torch, the Wandering Knight spoke.

“I belong to a vigilante group called Night Walkers. My nickname is a bit cringe, but it's 'Knight of the Night'.”

“...!”

The girl's ears perked up.

The other side was a member of 'Night Walkers', a vigilante group rumored among the people these days.

One of the beings of urban legend who were said to lead the weary to a land of salvation, a paradise called the 'Ark'.

The one-armed Wandering Knight, or 'Knight of the Night' as he was known, smiled at the girl with a mischievous smile and narrowed one eye.

“Name's Tudor.”

And when he turned his head back to the front, his expression was extremely cold and chilly.

“No last name.”

Chapter 422

How to Live as a Wandering Knight (3)

◆

...Pow!

The hard skeleton shattered and all the hot stuff inside spilled out onto the ground.

The Poison Gnoll fell to the ground, spraying poisonous brain fluid, and after shaking its body for a while, it cooled down.

The gnolls that had followed the Poison Gnoll into human territory also fell to the ground, all of them dead.

Initially a single clean hole in the head or heart, the gnoll corpses piled up, their entrails and heads bursting open in a gruesome, messy mound that testified to the fierceness of the battle.

Knight of the Night. Tudor, a wandering knight in black plate armor, sat atop the corpses of the gnolls, breathing heavily.

“...It's hard to get used to having one arm.”

The expression on his face has worn away as he continues to march, constantly exhausted and tired from the lack of sleep.

Muttering to himself in a dry voice, Tudor suddenly realizes that his tone and manner of speaking reminds him of someone he remembers, then smiled.

“Perhaps that's how he's always lived his life, and that's why he's so cold and dull in personality....”

Vikir. The Night Hound.

It had been quite some time, but his face and voice were still fresh in his memory.

Tudor remembered his old friend, expelled from the Academy long ago, now imprisoned in a prison in a faraway place.

Throbbing-

And every time he did, pain shot through his severed left arm.

Donquixote's eldest son, the next in line to become head of the family, had abandoned the family name and turned his back on his family.

He left his severed left arm at home.

“....”

Tudor recalled a story he'd heard in a tavern before the fight with the gnolls.

'I also hear that Donquixote and the Ushers are the subject of much gossip in town, and that the current patriarch is laid up with an illness, a very serious one, I hear. See you today and tomorrow.'

'They're superhumans! They're masters! They are not the kind of people who will succumb to disease or something like that!'

'They've been out of active service for years now. From what I've heard, Donquixote's younger brother is the regent, and Usher's younger sister is the regent.'

'Hmm, I've heard that, but I've also heard that Donquixote and Usher didn't have many members of their own families, so they relied on people from the outside world to help them. Is that why?'

The sound of teeth grinding came out of Tudor's mouth as he recalled the memory of that time.

Grrrttt!

Anger surges through him. A throbbing sensation in his missing left arm.

Tudor remembered that night, the night of his escape from the family home, clearly.

...Uncle Passamonte, who had been involved in escorting Vikir to Nouvelle Vague.

He had also vehemently advocated for the Nakajaniye Court of the Imperial Capital to sentence Vikir to death.

After the trial, Tudor had visited Passamonte several times to discuss the demon controversy and Vikir's punishment.

Even then, he had doubts.

Could his uncle, who had been so kind to him since he was a child, really be involved with the demon?

The uncle who had taught him what chivalry, romance, and ambition meant?

Es la misión del verdadero caballero. Su deber. ?No! Su deber no. Su privilegio.

-It is the task and duty of a true knight. No! Not your duty, but your privilege.

So?ar lo imposible so?ar.

-To dream the impossible dream.

Vencer al invicto rival,

-To defeat an invincible opponent,

Sufrir el dolor insufrible,

-To endure unbearable pain,

Morir por un noble ideal.

-To die for a noble ideal.

Saber enmendar el error,

-To know how to fix a wrong,

Amar con pureza y bondad.

-To love with purity and good will.

Querer, en un sue?o imposible,

-To fall in love in an impossible dream,

Con fe, una estrella alcanzar.

-To have faith, to reach for the stars.

When he closed his eyes, he could still hear his uncle's voice in his ear as he recited verses from the epic poem.

...But that didn't make him doubt Vikir.

As far as Tudor knew, Vikir had never told a bluff.

That was the kind of man he was.

A friend who was close to his age, but like an older brother, sometimes even an elder brother, a trusted and reliable friend.

He could never imagine that Vikir would ever claim anything false.

And then there was Professor Banshee Morgue, a familiar face at Colosseo Academy.

He may be a bit of a jerk and a pompous prick, but he's a fierce principled man and never speaks up when he's not sure about something.

Tudor, a former student at the Academy, knew this well.

So, the idea was to meet Passamonte face to face and investigate the facts.

...However, Tudor has not been able to even see Passamonte's face properly in recent years.

Passamonte, who had succeeded his father as regent after his sudden illness, kept Tudor out of his life.

Power struggles are a common occurrence in high-ranking families with complex family histories.

It's a common, clichéd trope that's always been part of fairy tales and legends.

But when it comes to his family, it's a different story.

During the vacation before Tudor graduation from the Academy, a secret civil war raged within the Donquixote family.

His uncle's rebellion for control over the province.

Tudor is forced to flee the family home to escape a wave of assassins.

It wasn't until a sword was drawn to his throat that Tudor knew for sure.

Donquixote's family had already been eaten by the Pasamonte.

That the sudden illness of his father, who was called the King of Spears, had been caused by a terrible conspiracy.

...And that in the end, Vikir, the old friend was right.

Tudor fled through tears. Through the pain and humiliation of having his arm cut off on the way.

As Tudor fled by boat, he remembered the words of Passamonte, who was at the head of the pursuing party, as he scowled at him.

“Do you mean to abandon your father and run away, and yet you are the son of the Lion King?”

Enraged, Tudor plunged into a final, life-threatening battle.

...It would have definitely been like that if it hadn't been for Bianca who appeared at the right time.

To Tudor's stubborn insistence that he could not leave his father behind, Bianca calmly replied.

'Retreating is not running away, and it is not wise to simply wait when danger outweighs hope. A wise man does not risk everything in one day, knowing to save today for tomorrow.'

These were Vikir's last words on the court of Nakajaniye in the center of the Imperial Capital.

Tudor left the family, following in the footsteps of Bianca, who had turned her back on her family in the same situation.

The heads of the Donquixote family and the Usher family, who had tried to declare neutrality in the face of signs of civil war, have since disappeared from the world.

The actual patriarch of Donquixote and Usher family became Donquixote La Mancha Passamonte and Usher Poe Madeline.

They searched the entire continent under the pretext of finding missing young patriarchs, and Tudor and Bianca had to go on an arduous escape.

The journey was arduous and dangerous, requiring them to penetrate several layers of vast siege networks and overcome countless guard posts.

And the people who helped and accepted Tudor and Bianca are the 'Nightwalkers', a group of followers and vigilantes who continue the legacy of the 'Night Hound'.

“....”

And now.

Tudor, who had followed in the footsteps of the Night Hound and become a Knight of the Night, looked down on the town from above the corpses of the gnolls.

The world had changed a lot.

Famines, long droughts, giant wildfires raging across the empire, and hordes of monsters.

The lives of humans had been squeezed to the bone, and it wasn't something anyone learned about in textbooks.

A large man shoves a slender girl and rips a chunk of meat from a gnoll corpse.

The strong extorted and robbed the weak, and treated them as if they were not human.

-The truly strong are strong to the strong and weak to the weak.

-The strong do not bully others because they can afford it, but the weak bully others to hide the fact that they are weak.

A quote from the autobiography of 'Donquixote La Mancha Alonso Quijano', a man from the distant past, a true ancestor of Donquixote the Spearman.

But the romance of chivalric literature and the reality of life were diametrically opposed.

The stronger you are, the more you bully others, and the weaker you are, the more unfair things you experience.

However, the weak were not necessarily good and kind.

The reality was much different than what they were taught in the Academy and within their families.

It was not the strong who survived, but the strong who survived.

Such was the world.

Tudor had seen this kind of humanity many times before, and he could feel his own personality becoming duller and more calloused as the battle raged on.

It was a process of going from an aspiring hero to a battlefield veteran.

And why?

The more Tudor's personality, speaking style, and voice become more and more similar to Vikir's.

“Hahaha- I shouldn't even take on his way of speaking, that's too stiff.”

Tudor smiled mischievously and then stood up.

Just then.

“...So, there.”

Someone shuffled to the side.

Where Tudor turned his head, a girl stood.

The same girl who had just escaped the gnoll attack.

“Drink this!”

The girl held out a large bowl of clear water and toasted bread sprinkled with herbs.

Water and herbs in this time of need. Tudor felt his throat instantly tighten.

“Can I accept something so precious?”

“...Of course!”

The girl, who had been worried that her gift might not be accepted, replied with a wide smile.

Tudor ate the bread and drink the water.

He would have to travel a long way to get back to the Night Walkers' hideout.

When Tudor finished eating, he stood up and saw that quite a few people had gathered around him.

“Knight, Knight of the Night, please take us with you!”

“We have heard that following the Night Walkers will lead us to a place where there is water, food, and God's blessings!”

“Please have mercy on us....”

The people gathered are those who no longer have a place to live due to gnoll raids, famine, and wildfires.

At first glance, the crowd looked to be about 10% of the town's population.

And Tudor nodded to them.

“Follow me.”

This is why the Knight of the Night had come all this way in the first place.

A secret but not so secret place where the Night Walkers gathered.

'Only there will fire and water escape, and only there will true salvation be found.'

That is where the land of salvation in the new Book of Revelation exists.

The mission was to move as many people as possible to the ark built by the 'Saint of the Night'.

Chapter 423

The Night Walkers (1)

◆

Tochka.

A citadel located on a high plateau in the Rocks Mountains of the Northern Continent.

Its high, solid walls, deep moat, and towering cliffs surrounding it made it a natural fortress.

However.

This fortress, which was said to be able to fend off a hundred soldiers by one girl, was now a deserted, ownerless mountain.

No wonder, another name for Tochka, the strongest fortress, is , the 'Crying Castle'.

The name, which means “beheaded while crying” comes from an ancient story of a general in the Warring States Period who was defeated by the enemy army while sitting-in in the fortress here.

The young and talented general, trusting only in his own skills and military theories, waged a siege in this natural fortress, but the result was a disastrous defeat.

Fortress Tochka was a massive fortress with impregnable defenses, but it had only one drawback: it was located on a plateau filled with rocks in the dry climate of the northern highlands, and there was no water nearby for drinking.

Because of the general who suffered from hunger due to lack of water and opened the gate and escaped, the country eventually entered the path of destruction.

Therefore, the king had no choice but to behead his favorite general according to military law, and the nickname 'Crying Castle' was given because the king swung his sword with tears in his eyes.

The ominous legend of Crying Castle, a harsh environment where there is hardly any drinking water.

As a result, this magnificent and sturdy fortress has become an unremarkable place that is slowly being forgotten as the years go by.

...However.

There is a group of people who operate out of this abandoned fortress that no one takes notice of.

Night Walkers. They were 'those who walk the night'.

Ungseong-ungseong-

The Tochka, which not long ago had been nothing more than a desolate highland fortress, was now bustling with people.

Additions and renovations are everywhere.

Pillars and watchtowers were being raised, and holes in the walls were being filled.

Countless goats pulled carts loaded with food and water.

Where the tents were pitched, refugees from all over the continent had gathered.

They had all followed the Night Walkers to this 'Ark'.

Famine, drought, wildfires, and monster outbreaks have displaced them from their original homes.

The sick are healed and the hungry are fed.

Not enough to fill them to overflowing, but enough so that they no longer had to watch their children clutch at their empty bellies.

The refugees who settled here all looked tired and exhausted, but there was a glimmer of hope in their eyes.

They had come from a place where they had left the unbelievers behind.

They had traveled a long way, risking ridicule, mockery, and scorn, to follow a gleam of faith, and the outcome was bright.

At least here, they were blessed by priests and rationed food and water.

It was a paradise compared to their old home, where they had to worry about food shortages, robberies, and monster attacks every day.

Meanwhile.

In the tents where the wounded and sick lay, dozens of priests bustled about.

One priest was tending to a refugee who had been crushed by a boulder while helping to repair the city walls.

She took a deep breath and muttered.

“Calm down, Lolita. This is just a simple recovery baptism, nothing to be afraid of, so don't tremble.”

“Sister. My name is not Lolita.”

“I know. Lolita is my name.”

“...?”

When a young nun, who doesn't look like she has much experience, asks for God's help with trembling hands.

Swoosh-

A hand gently grasped her hand from behind.

“Our Lord Lun is willing to extend his hand to the lamb that groans in pain before his eyes.”

Sister Lolita turned her head in surprise at the experienced and compassionate voice.

There stood Dolores, the 'Saint of the Night', leader of the 'Night Walkers', smiling.

'...It's dazzling!'

Lolita, the novice nun, was momentarily intimidated by the solemn, compassionate, reverent, and beautiful figure.

Then Dolores' expression changed into a mischievous one for an instant.

She whispered in a low voice that no one else could hear, only Lolita.

“Don't be afraid to draw on the divine power, draw on it as much as you can, and He will pay you back. In a time of crisis like this, the interest is cheap.”

The Old Testament priests taught her a good lesson.

Lolita's eyes narrowed at the familiarity in Dolores' tone.

“D-do you think a saint could say something like that?”

“Of course.”

Dolores smiled and raised her two fists in encouragement, and Sister Lolita's expression brightened.

As if emboldened, she began to pray. She had done an excellent job of healing the patient.

Dolores smiled as she watched the young sisters who had trusted her with their lives in the Quovadis family grow into young women.

As it turns out, the flower of faith blooms most beautifully in the fiercest places on the front lines.

Then.

A voice called to Dolores.

“'Saint of the Night', it's been a long time!”

A man can be seen beyond a herd of goats grazing on the highlands in the distance.

A man of impeccable height and manly handsomeness.

Black armor and blonde hair flowing in the wind, he was the epitome of the ideal wandering knight.

He looked like a painting in a canvas, but his severed left arm was a reminder of the harsh reality.

“'Knight of the Night'!”

Dolores grinned at her comrade in the distance.

Tudor had returned.

They had been senior and junior at the Colosseo Academy, and they had gotten along well within the Night Walkers.

“I've brought a lot of new people with me.”

“We've graduated, just let it go.”

“Once a senior, always a senior.”

Dolores and Tudor were both early graduates of the Academy.

As a result, their time together was fairly short, but Dolores still remembers Tudor's school days vividly.

After Vikir's imprisonment at Nouvelle Vague, Tudor had become noticeably less talkative.

The once cheerful, leadership, and romantic Tudor had become a quiet, sincere student who devoted himself only to training and studies.

Something terrible happened to his family afterward that shaped him into the man he is today.

Sancho the Warrior of the Night, Pigi the Gatekeeper of the Night, Bianca the Sniper of the Night, and the rest of his fellow academy classmates, their cheerful smiles hiding an unimaginable amount of sadness and pain.

'Maybe, if I hadn't met Vikir earlier, I would have been in the same situation as Tudor.'

Dolores sympathized deeply with Tudor's pain and grief, but she was also deeply grateful to Vikir for his early help in chipping away at the darkness of the Quovadis.

No, the civil war would have been much more chaotic if Quilt and Humbert had lived,

'No, there would have been no civil war in the first place.'

Seth, or rather Andromalius, lurking in Baskerville, the Ironblood Swordman.

Seere, hiding in Morgue, the Mage Sect.

Bartolomeo, no, Belial, who was lurking in hiding among the wealthy Bourgeois.

If each of them had seized control of their families and joined the civil war, the human world would have been turned into a horrible hell by now.

Dolores felt a newfound reverence and pity for the weight of Vikir's burden and the length of the thorny path he had been carrying.

'In times like these, we must be even more resolute in our support of his will.'

This must take precedence over helping him escape from his imprisonment in Nouvelle Vague.

Any hasty movements would only hinder Vikir, so they must complete the task at hand.

Then.

“Hey, Knight of the Night!”

Two more men appeared in the distance, beyond a cart full of drinking water.

It was Sancho and Pigi.

“Long time no see, boys!”

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi hugged each other, celebrating their first reunion in months.

The Night Walkers had been traveling across the continent like this, sharing the story of the Ark with refugees and bringing them to Tochka.

'Only here will fire and water be spared, only here will true salvation be found.'

All of this was based on a message left behind by Night Hound.

Sancho, standing beside Tudor, looked back at the now bustling fortress of Tochka.

“This place has become quite crowded. When we first took up residence here, it seemed like it was haunted.”

“Yeah. It's a good thing you guys have been so good about keeping up with us in this high, barren place.”

Pigi nodded.

But neither Tudor, Sancho, nor Pigi, who had led the refugees to this place, had resolved the fundamental question.

“But why did Vikir tell us to gather people here?”

It was a mystery that even Dolores, the leader of the Night Walkers, had yet to solve.

But the situation was too urgent for Vikir to explain much.

Besides, Vikir, as everyone knew, never told a lie.

“There must be a reason, because I've never lost anything by listening to him.”

“I know. There must be a reason why he insisted on gathering as many people as possible in such a desolate, remote fortress.”

“Exactly, so let's push on, it's all we can do until we find a way to rescue Vikir!”

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi once again look determined.

Dolores looked at them with trust in her eyes.

Just then.

“Hey, executives. I need you to assemble, we have a meeting to conduct.”

In the distance, the curtains of the barracks were lifted and a figure stepped out.

“...!”

“...!”

“...!”

“...!”

Dolores, Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi turned their heads in unison.

It was the Wealth of the Night, the sponsor who financed the Night Walkers.

Also known to a very few as 'rich friend'.

A wealthy individual who had taken Tochka from a mere abandoned fortress on the outskirts to a fully fortified fortress, stockpiling enough food and water to feed and shelter a large number of refugees.

A supernova in the business world, where once funds are mobilized, the wealth is comparable to that of the tycoon Bourgeois.

And an advisor to the Colosseo Academy's investment club, the Oracle.

'Messinadnaro Cindywendy'.

No, she was now Countess Cindywendy of Baskerville, and she was looking down in this direction.

“...It's urgent.”

With a rare look of seriousness.

Chapter 426

The Night Walkers (4)

◆

Sinclaire.

The most talented and brilliant of the 20 classes at Colosseo Academy, with the exception of Vikir.

In the original story, she disappeared from everyone's sight after graduating from Colosseo Academy, until she reappeared in front of her classmates.

“Stay back!”

Sinclaire shouted at Bianca, who was holding Tudor.

At the same time.

Jjeojeojeojeojeog! Ujijijig!

The ground is torn apart on a large scale, and the entire yellow gold vein beneath it is lifted out.

A stratum suddenly broke off and floated into the air.

Countless pieces of gold are melted by a hot magic field and then their form is recreated.

Then, an enormous number of golden hands appeared behind Sinclaire's back.

A thousand hands.

Each one glowing with a brilliant golden light.

Behind them, a large mana wheel spun, emitting a halo of light.

The hat atop Sinclaire's head began to unleash its power.

The so-called 'Money Hat', a mysterious artifact that increased the amount of mana one possessed based on the amount of gold one possessed.

It was a powerful artifact, especially with Sinclaire's overwhelming wealth as he became a recognized member of the Bourgeois family.

Sinclaire had even gotten quite high stats in the Hell Tree.

This had allowed her to double-cast a great deal of earth and gold magic.

Like right now.

Kwakwakwakwang!

Countless golden fists rained down, blocking Donquixote's invincible cavalry for a moment.

Horses stumbled and knights rolled on the ground.

The tightening siege was suddenly loosened.

Of course, Bianca, who had crossed so many lines of fire, would not miss this opportunity.

Pas-

Bianca moved as if she had made a pact with Sinclaire.

In one swift motion, she scooped Tudor up in her arms and leapt upward.

As Bianca and Tudor slipped back through the encirclement, Sinclaire flew through the air to cover them.

Kwakwakwakwang!

The spears flying toward Bianca were deflected by a golden fist.

Bianca, who had been running wordlessly, turned to Sinclaire.

“ ... What about the family?”

“I left them in the care of Uncle Damian, and I hope you don't mind me saying so now, but... I'm kind of worried about you guys.”

Sinclaire lowered his head and spoke in a low, hushed voice.

This is because Sinclaire and Bianca were, in a vulgar term, 'at loggerheads' with each other.

Sinclaire had originally planned to graduate with honors from the academy, prove herself, and then compete with her cousin Juliette for a place in the Bourgeois family.

However, Juliette's death and her growing attraction to Vikir, a former classmate at the same school, she gradually began to wander.

After much deliberation, she decided to drop out of Colosseo Academy to clear her mind and make a clear decision about her future.

She also decided to cut off all ties with her other friends, who were making her swayed by their personal feelings.

Suddenly, one day, without leaving a word, she disappeared from everyone and erased her traces.

But fate had a twist.

Sinclaire became trapped in the Hell Tree, and in the process, she began to reflect on her inner self.

A murderous battle among her friends.

A mission where only one of them would survive to reach the next level.

In the midst of these extreme trials.

'In a situation like this, I think it's only right to send the person most likely to survive, and you're the most genius among us, Sinclaire, so I think you should go.'

'...Hung. You know you've been a total jerk to me lately, you should really think about it. Reflect on the real thing. Where's such a good friend?'

Her friends embraced her and sacrificed for her, even though she was the first to turn away.

They didn't ask for anything, they didn't demand anything, they just gave her their full trust.

After weighing it all up, she was ashamed of herself for thinking it would be beneficial to fall out with her friends.

...And that's what Sinclaire had in mind, too.

'Decide for yourself. What to see, what to hear, what to believe.'

Vikir said this just before he was crushed by the Demonic Dragon's fist.

Those were the same words he'd used to kill her father, who had become the Demon's mastermind.

Afterward, Sinclaire, who had dropped out of the academy and become a Bourgeois family head, thought long and hard.

Was this the life she'd been seeking?

Was this what she really wanted, what she had hoped for?

[It wouldn't be a bad idea to weed out useless relationships at this point. As of this time, all plays have ended].

Her father, Bartolomeo, the only family member she ever wanted to be recognized and loved, had long since become a puppet of the demon.

By the time she realizes this, her goal of becoming the head of a Bourgeois family has already lost its meaning.

So what has she believed and what has she been pursuing?

And what should she believe in and pursue in the future?

She pondered for a while, and then her sharp mind came up with an answer.

And now, Sinclaire is standing here to fulfill her answer.

“I'm sorry, I've been wrong all these years. Please accept me as your friend again.”

Sinclaire said as she blocked Donquixote's Invincible Cavalry.

A voice that trembles lightly, unlike the golden iron wall that stands strong.

Her sincere apology reached Bianca, who was behind her, leaving Tudor in Dolores' care.

“....”

Bianca turned her head to look at Sinclaire.

Sinclaire was sweating profusely.

Blood trickled from the corners of her mouth, indicating the strain on her body.

“I would do anything if you could only forgive me....”

But she couldn't finish her sentence.

“Ah! How can you not forgive in a situation like this!?”

Bianca quickly rushed forward, grabbed Sinclaire by the scruff of the neck, and ran backwards.

...Kwakwang! Kudeudeudeudeudeudeug-

As Sinclaire was being tackled by Bianca, the golden wall collapsed and the Invincible Cavalry rushed in.

In the first place, just being able to block the charge of those monsters that could tear apart landslides for a few seconds was an incredible achievement.

Peopeopeong-

Several spears flew toward Sinclaire, but Bianca dodged them as she wrapped her arms around Sinclaire's waist.

The spears cut off a few strands of Bianca's long hair and send her flying.

Bianca dodged the spears and sprinted over the jutting rocks, turning to Sinclaire around her waist.

“Idiot, we were never friends in the first place.”

“Bianca....”

Tears formed in Sinclaire's eyes.

They'd been rooming together since their freshman year.

But they'd drifted apart at Colosseo Academy.

Hiding one's family origin or trying to cut off all contact after graduating from school would have been a great betrayal and immorality for the young girls.

But now, they have a much bigger cause to fight for.

Kwak!

The two women clasped hands.

When they met again, their hands were even more firmly interlocked than the first time.

“I'm sorry I'm late.”

“....”

“I'm also sorry for dropping out of the Academy without telling you.”

“....”

“I'm sorry I ignored your greeting on purpose, just to get away from you.”

“....”

“I'm sorry I hid my Bourgeois background from you.”

“....”

“At the Hell Tree again....”

“Ahhhh! I get it, I'm out of breath, I can't even answer!”

Bianca shouted, forgetting that her smug expression was crumbling.

Both Sinclaire and Bianca had tears and snot running down their faces.

Right then.

The Invincible Cavalry, which had come up right behind Bianca and Sinclaire, stopped.

“You bastards! How dare you take my friend!”

“I can't forgive you!”

“I'll pay you back twice over!”

Sancho, Pigi, and Tudor, who had fully recovered after receiving treatment from Dolores, joined them.

“Bianca!”

“Tudor!”

Tudor and Bianca leapt to their feet, clasping each other's hands, and within moments, they were each delivering a stinging blow to the knights who had been on their backs.

“Here comes the Tycoon of the Night!”

“Isn't it better to be the Golden King of the Night than the Tycoon of the Night?”

As Sancho and Pigi casually smile at Sinclaire, whom they haven't seen in a long time, Sinclaire smiles back with tears of relief.

It's good to be together. That's what motivation is all about.

“ ... It's a shame we're missing one.”

Pigi mumbles to himself, and everyone flinches.

But it was only for a moment.

“Don't worry. He'll be back.”

“I can't imagine him dying.”

“ ... I guess so too, right?”

“Maybe he's healthier than we are.”

“We're going to get him back.”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire turned their heads, their faces determined.

And before them stood Dolores, their most trusted senior and ally.

“Ready, the prayer is complete!”

Dolores clasped her hands together and began to radiate holy power.

Paas-

A dome of pure white flame began to expand outward.

The entirety of Donquixote's knights flinched as they were touched by Dolores' holy power.

Their eyes glazed over and their movements slowed noticeably.

“That's it! It's working!”

Tudor exclaimed uncontrollably.

But Dolores's complexion was not so bright.

“Wrong, the brainwashing is too strong. It must be the power of a demon of the 10 Corpses.”

And the one who was indirectly controlling the knights with that power, the cause of the battle, stood before Dolores.

“Kahahahaha! His influence will remain strong as long as I am here!”

Pedro, who was sprinting toward Dolores with a burst of magic.

As he approached, the eyes of the knights around him became cloudy again, and their actions became sharper.

Finally, Dolores bit her lip and drew her secret weapon.

“...I can't help it.”

It was the last thing she wanted to do.

Dolores clasped her hands together and began to pray.

...Paas!

Another bright light swirled around her.

It was like the warmth of sunshine, bringing a cool breeze to the battlefield.

Pedro sneered at Dolores.

“Prayers and holy incantations are laughable! Light is only as warm as the sun you bathe in....”

But. He didn't finish his sentence.

He was interrupted by a large shadow suddenly cast across his face.

“What ...?”

Pedro's face went blank for a moment.

It was because of the object Dolores suddenly pulled out from behind her back as she prayed.

A mace. A large, beautiful, powerful hunk of iron.

It was Nabokov I's favorite weapon, which was closer to physical power than divine power, was right there.

Chapter 428

The Lion King (1)

◆

A castle on the northern coast.

The castle rises high above the beach and coastal cliffs, with blue sea water flowing below.

A few fishermen can be seen fishing on the lower beach.

Hwiiiing-

Somehow, a warm wind was blowing from far out on the sea.

Bubbling

White foam rises from the reef forest.

This is a phenomenon that occurs when schools of warm fish gather together.

“Hey, where are all the other fish, and these are the only ones being caught?”

One of the fishermen said, puzzled.

The sea had gotten unusually warm, and there were a lot of warm fish that only come out when the water temperature is high.

Grumbling-

By the way, the sky has been dark for days.

The sun was covered by several layers of dark clouds, making it impossible to distinguish between day and night.

The fishermen clicked their tongues.

“It's an ominous sign. An ominous sign.”

“Is there a volcano offshore somewhere? Why is the water so warm?”

“There was a big earthquake the other day, so that must be it.”

“When schools of large fish come out, the sea turns dark red... Other fish will die in droves.”

“Looking at my sore skin, it looks like a heavy rain will come soon. Let's pack up quickly.”

The fishermen hurriedly reeled in their nets and returned to shore.

There were wooden stalls lined up on the beach, and the caught fish were drying out on them.

It was a relief to catch so many fish, especially since there was nothing to eat in the famine.

If they were dried well, they would last for a couple of months.

Then.

The fishermen shook their heads in unison.

“Oh no! There are knights coming!”

“Let's get down quickly, and if we make eye contact with them, they'll be offended.”

“They never used to be like that... but nowadays they're all acting a little strange.”

“Come on, let's get into the hut.”

Over the horizon, where the fishermen stared, came a group of knights.

Donquixote's Invincible Cavalry, who had been sent to the civil war.

Some of them were returning to their families.

Donquixote's knights were good-natured, greeting the common people and occasionally lending a hand, but that began to change when their patriarch, Cervantes, fell ill.

The knights became stiff and cold because of the orders of Pasamonte that dignity and authority were important.

They wouldn't even accept a greeting, let alone return it, and there was no conversation or interaction.

Not only that, but they also showed their inhumanity by riding past a child playing on the side of the road and crushing it, so the people were now very afraid of Donquixote's knights.

And the fearful gaze of the common people was being felt by the men at the forefront of the cavalry.

Tudor. Disguised in his armor, he was heartbroken to see the eyes of the commoners on him.

There were no more old men waving their hats cheerfully, no more young men offering him ale or grilled fish, no more little children coming up to play.

“...Pasamonte, no, Cimeries, I can never forgive you. I'll never forgive you for making Donquixote's territory so sick.”

“Hold on, Tudor, keep up the momentum.”

Bianca, riding beside him, said to Tudor.

The Night Walkers were returning to the family home, all wearing Donquixote's armor, blending in among the knights.

The knights, now somewhat removed from their brainwashing, are deeply ashamed of what they have done and willingly cooperate with the strategy.

The family's true nature is now at hand.

Beyond this point, the Night Walkers would fall to one side, and Tudor guidance would lead them to a secret passage.

Hwiiiing-

An unpleasantly warm sea breeze pierces through the helmets. The breeze carried with it a musty smell.

“Ugh- what is this smell?”

Bianca was the first to frown, always sensitive to smells.

Sancho wrinkled his nose.

“It's the smell of dried fish. The whole fish has a particularly strong smell.”

“That's a pretty stinky smell.”

Pigi threw his hands up in the air.

The smell of drying fish filled the air as they walked along the beach, until they came upon the tall gates of Donquixote, a castle of spears perched on a cliff.

Kkigigigigig-

The gates opened of their own accord as the banner of the Invincible Cavalry was raised.

They had finally succeeded in infiltrating the enemy camp.

“....”

The Night Walkers slipped from the ranks of the knights as they crossed the field of smoke.

“This way.”

Tudor moved toward the bush, keeping close to the outer wall.

It was a passageway for servants, but there was a secret door beneath the wall that led inside.

Donquixote's knights entered, their faces still grim, as if caught in a hint.

To avoid arousing the demon's suspicions.

Now, on cue, they will move swiftly and take control of the empty castle.

And then they would swoop in at the crucial moment to catch Passamonte off guard.

“For that to happen, we must find him first and lure him out of the castle.”

Dolores's words had everyone nodding in agreement.

Then the Night Walkers, led by Tudor, took the back roads and headed for the main castle.

“Here we go.”

Tudor loaded his fingers with mana and pushed a brick in the wall.

Grrrrr.

An underground tunnel opened up.

The Night Walkers all crawled into the crypt.

...Gurgling!

On the end of a wooden pole was an old solid fuel.

It was dried whale fat.

A match was struck against the blackened mass and a few torches were produced.

“Thank God. I thought it was old and wouldn't stick.”

“I could have used light magic.”

“No. Let's try to avoid using mana as much as possible, in case the demons notice.”

Tudor said, handing Sinclaire a torch.

Then. The six assassins -Dolores, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire- swung into action.

This was the way of the demon hunter to hunt demons, and the way of the eldest son, who had been kicked out of the family, to regain his rights.

Seeing Tudor's body trembling slightly, Bianca reached out and slapped him once on the back.

“Don't be nervous. The head of the family is naturally inherited by the eldest son. Why are you dropping this when the cause is right here?”

“...You're right, it's weird to be nervous when I'm going to reclaim what's mine.”

Tudor took a deep breath and puffed out his chest.

Bianca looked sadly at Tudor's empty left arm, then pursed her lips and curled her bow tightly.

It dawned on her that she was neither in a position to pity anyone, nor could she afford to.

◆

After passing through several underground passageways and double doors, they finally reached the depths of the castle's interior.

Tudor threw off the iron mask and helmet that covered his face.

His one remaining arm twitched with strength.

He felt a new appreciation for the years that had passed.

To have to walk through the corridors, fully armed and breathless, where he once roamed freely in nothing but a robe after a shower.

Then. A few passing maids appeared from around the corner.

“Oh? Young master?”

Unexpectedly, the maids were not at all surprised to see Tudor.

“What are you doing here, at this hour?”

“....”

Tudor felt his hands sweat as he gripped the spear.

It seemed that the maids were unaware of the treatment Tudor received within the family.

“It's no big deal. It's been a while since I came home.”

“What? You've been out? I haven't seen you around lately... did something happen to the estate?”

The maids look at Tudor with pity.

Tudor smoothed out the hem of his black cloak that covered his left arm.

Then he smiled and said.

“Well, so be it. How is my father?”

“I don't know, I haven't seen him lately. I can only speak to him through the Viscount Passamonte.”

“ ...Only through my uncle?”

“Yes, my lord, he is very ill. Though it is a relief to know that Mr. Passamonte is always at his side to take care of him. How very dutiful he is.”

Just then, one of the maids spoke up.

“But there's something a little odd, whenever I go near my lord's chambers, there's always some sort of...”

Tudor raised an eyebrow, and the other maid interrupted her with a squeak of surprise.

“My dear, what nonsense are you talking about?”

“Well, it's not that...”

“I told you it was your nose that was the problem! Ugh, you're being unnecessarily sensitive.”

The maids hurriedly broke off their conversation and bowed to Tudor.

“Then the head maid called us and we have to help take care of the knights of the Invincible Cavalry who returned to the main house just now.”

“Uhm. Well, yes.”

Tudor let the maids go.

When they were gone, his companions, who had been stuck between the ceiling and the pillars, descended to the floor.

“What did the maids say? A little while ago, one of the kids was acting a little strange.”

“I don't know, I didn't hear the end.”

“Oh, you stifle! We need to capture them and interrogate them!”

“They don't know anything, they've only ever been in their own world. What do they know about what's going on outside? Right now, the most important thing is to get through this place quickly.”

Tudor has a point.

Having infiltrated this far, there was no time to fool around with unknowing maids.

The Night Walkers moved quickly through the darkened corridors to the spiral staircase.

Soon, beyond the darkened corridors, they could see the patriarch himself.

A room where Cervantes the Spear King is lying sick.

Two knights stood guard before him.

“Who are you?”

“My lord, who currently not allowing anyone to see him... huh!?”

The knights gulped as soon as they saw Tudor.

But only for a moment, and then their eyes turned bloodshot.

Their mouths were torn open from ear to ear, and their tongues stuck out in two pieces.

[How did you get here?]

[Anyway, welcome!]

The knights turned into demons as soon as they saw Tudor's face, and it wasn't just the effects of brainwashing.

Bianca's arrows were able to fly without any hesitation.

...Peog-peog!

It was at least two shots faster than the knights' mana manifestation.

Tudor's spears pierced the throats and hearts of the two demons, who stopped dead with arrows lodged in their foreheads.

“I've used up my mana, what can I do?”

“They're covered by the demons' auras, so they'll be fine, but let's get through them as fast as we can, just in case.”

Tudor and Bianca turned their heads.

Dolores closed her eyes and scanned the mana flow around her, then nodded.

So far, there hadn't been much of a commotion, so it didn't seem like they'd been spotted.

Stepping over the bodies of the demonized knights, the Night Walkers advanced further.

“Will my father be all right?”

“Of course he will. He's the King of the Spears, and even if he is, he'll be fine as soon as he's away from the demons, and there's Dolores.”

Tudor and Bianca walked ahead.

Then.

“...!”

Everyone felt it.

Hwiiiing-

A warm sea breeze in the window, and a tantalizing smell carried on the breeze.

“Ugh, the smell of drying fish.”

Bianca said, wrinkling her nose.

But Tudor's complexion was stiffening.

This was not the smell from the coast.

A stench far worse than drying fish in captivity was wafting through the gap in the doorway of Cervantes the Spear King room.

Ujijig!

Breaking the locked doorknob with the force of his hand, Tudor pushed the door open and stepped inside.

“...!?”

Soon, Tudor and everyone else realized.

Why the maids had reacted the way they had earlier.

Chapter 430

The Lion King (3)

◆

-It is the task and duty of a true knight. No! Not a duty, but a privilege.

To dream the impossible dream.

To defeat an invincible opponent, To endure unbearable pain, To die for a noble ideal.

To know how to fix a wrong, love with purity and good will.

To fall in love in an impossible dream, To have faith, to reach for the stars.

A romantic poem that would only appear in chivalric literature.

Its author was a nobleman with beautiful blond hair and blue eyes.

Donquixote La Mancha Passamonte.

He raised his white face and looked at his nephew, Tudor, in front of him.

“Who taught you this favorite poem?”

“....”

Tudor's mouth fell open.

Dolores, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire knew.

Ever since they'd met as freshmen at Colosseo Academy, Tudor had loved chivalric literature and heroic epics and recited them often.

That passage in particular was his favorite.

Passamonte opened his mouth with a hint of sadness.

“Half of your chivalry was learned from this uncle, and what a tragedy. To stab in the back of an uncle who has given you all his love. What kind of immoral act is this?”

“....”

Tudor did not speak this time.

Passamonte continued.

“Bring me that Gungnir. It is too dangerous an object for you to handle when you are so young. I, your guardian and uncle, will keep it for you until you are old enough to be a knight. Here-”

A white palm stretched out before him.

Only then did Tudor speak.

“You have never been able to remove Gungnir from my father's body.”

“....”

“Because it is a family heirloom that only responds to those who are worthy of being a Donquixote.”

Tudor lifted the new Gungnir and tapped it lightly on the floor.

It's heavy, but it's just as reliable.

The blade of Gungnir was as sharply honed as Tudor's resolve.

Then, with a crackle of lightning, Gungnir pointed it at Passamonte.

“Did you intend to capture me alive and make me draw Gungnir?”

Gungnir would not have responded to anyone but Tudor himself.

So did Passamonte need Tudor to get his hands on the spear, a symbol and token of the family head?

At Tudor's rambling words, Passamonte raised an eyebrow at Tudor.

“It's similar to my intention. Just about half. Well, there was that purpose as well.”

Then he added, in a tone of amusement.

“To be honest, ... I haven't been in a very good mood lately, nephew.”

“Don't call me nephew. You disgusting demon.”

“Oh- you won't let me call my nephew my 'nephew', what a immoral person. I see, what shall I call you then, mmmm~ Mr. Tudor?”

Passamonte retracted his outstretched hand toward Gungnir and smiled broadly.

But despite the smile on his lips, the voice that escaped his lips held a deep note of regret.

“The reason I'm in a bad mood... is because I lost the body I've been preparing for over a decade to change into in vain at the end.”

“...!”

Everyone's eyes widened.

It was obvious what Pasamonte was talking about.

Cervantes Donquixote, the Spear King.

The demon was planning to abandon Pasamonte's frail body and take on Cervantes' stronger one.

But Cervantes' superhuman mental strength allowed him to destroy his own body before the demon could take it.

His body was completely shattered, and the Divine Spear Gungnir, which had penetrated it, was sealed tightly.

As a last stand, Cervantes made sure the demon took nothing from him.

“I borrowed poison from the Leviathan, and at the last moment, when I looked away for a moment, he committed suicide. It was a moment for which the expression 'One thousand thoughts and one mistake' is perfect.”

Passamonte said with a grim look and gesture.

“Cervantes, in the end I got nothing of his soul or body, which is a tragedy, ... but!”

At this, his blue eyes turn black.

The overly enlarged pupils were like holes into a deep abyss.

Just looking into his eyes is like being pulled into a dark abyss.

The dizziness and nausea that followed caused all the Night Walkers to sway.

All the light of the stars, moonlight, and the twinkling of human emotions is sucked away into the darkness beyond.

Into the nothingness, into that infernal void, where no one knows what lurks.

Passamonte looked at Tudor with those eyes and grinned so wide that the corners of his mouth touched his earlobes.

“...But it's all right! For here is a body younger, fresher, and with better qualities than Cervantes's; but a body not yet perfected, and with much to improve!”

Only then did the Night Walkers realize what Passamonte was really after.

A body with the highest qualities, comparable to that of Cervantes the Spear King, but much younger, with a vast future ahead of him, and infinite potential for improvement.

And a much more immature and fragile mind, easy to devour.

That's right.

Having failed to take Cervantes' body, Passamonte now set his sights on Tudor's.

-'Why do you want to take me and Tudor alive? If you're after static elimination, why not just take our heads? Isn't that much easier?'-

-[Mo, I don't know! I'm serious! He didn't tell me!]-

There was a reason Pedro had been so evasive in answering Bianca's question.

Whether he knew it or not, it is impossible to tell.

'...It was a trap!'

Dolores bit her lip.

The cavalry of the Donquixote family that only attacked a few people. The brainwashing was somehow sloppy. Loose boundaries. A darkness that reveals itself so easily.

All of these were Passamonte's enticements to lure Tudor into the heart of the castle.

'If it were you, Vikir, we would not have fallen for this.'

Dolores blamed herself, but that didn't change the situation.

'Regardless, you have to do the best you can. The odds were stacked against him from the start, and there was nothing he could do to change that.

'Let's just get out into the open. There are unbrainwashed knights outside of the castle, and if we can combine forces, we have a good chance of winning....'

Dolores's thoughts were interrupted, however.

“Yaaaaaah!”

Tudor suddenly raised his Gungnir and charged toward Passamonte.

Boom-!

Speed ??like lightning, heaviness like a tsunami.

Tudor's strike shot out, aiming for Passamonte's heart.

“Ouch. Better than I imagined. Bone solid, muscle tight, entrails fresh. Such good body.”

Passamonte twisted to the side at the waist, dodging Tudor's spear.

Just then.

Peog-peog-peong!

Bianca's arrows flew and struck the wall.

“Haas!”

Bianca was firing just as hard as Tudor.

Strangely, it wasn't just Tudor and Bianca, but Sancho, Pigi, and Sinclaire as well.

“Eh, eh, my body's going out of control!”

“Something! I feel like I can do something! Although there is no basis...!”

“I feel an inexplicable sense of elation. There's something wrong with this.”

Listening to her colleagues, Dolores realized that she had been thinking wrongly, too.

'Now that I think about it, I've been thinking that it might be worth sticking around. No way!?'

Dolores looked up in surprise and stared at Passamonte.

Then she saw the smile on Passamonte's face.

“Have you noticed? I have the ability to make others reckless.”

Reckless, like a frog trying to match the size of a bull.

It was this brainwashing ability to make others do whatever he pleased that allowed Pasamonte to possess Donquixote.

The demon's cunning ability to manipulate others was first manifested when Pedro discovered the fortress of the Night Walkers.

As if possessed by something, the Night Walkers found Donquixote's castle of their own accord, and now they surrendered everything to the fearsome demon.

'Alas, Vikir was right in his warning!'

Dolores cursed herself deeply.

Vikir had given her a brief explanation of the powers of the Ten Corpses before he left for Nouvelle Vague.

But the powers of demons are so mysterious and strange that even those who experience them firsthand often fail to realize they are real.

The Night Walkers were confused, unsure of how they had been drawn into Passamonte's scheme.

Perhaps their very presence here was a trick of the demon? The thought occurred to them, and from then on, things spiraled out of control.

And demons never miss the moment when a human loses insight and falls into confusion.

“Okay, now that you're properly confused, let's get down to business, shall we?”

To take over the body, the mind must first be shaken. It's the basics of the basics.

Tsutsutsutsutsu...

Passamonte spreads his arms wide.

The floor cracks, and then a thick, deep crack opens up and the floor collapses.

Ujijig! Rumbling!

Something began to surge up through the inky darkness beneath the floor.

It's a terrible malice, rising to destroy human hearts and minds.

“...!?”

The faces of Dolores, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire instantly turned blue as they saw what lurked below.

The abyss beneath the floor of the room.

Beneath them lay a landscape that would traumatize any student who had ever been a part of Colosseo Academy.

Chapter 434

The Returned Hound (3)

◆

'Black Tongue Leeches'.

Vikir's secret weapon from Nouvelle Vague.

Hunger. A small vampire driven by an insatiable appetite.

They began to swell after drinking the blood flowing from the ground, and soon began to need more and more blood.

Specialized species bred by Black Tongue to seek only the blood of Vikir.

Their voracious appetite was too much for even the super-regenerative Vikir to handle.

But then a replacement appeared, one whose blood had the exact same composition as Vikir's own, and this was the perfect opportunity to grow the leeches.

“Eat a lot.”

Vikir said cheerfully.

And the leeches moved as if they understood him.

The leeches gorging themselves among the torn flesh, exposed bones, tattered tendons, and lumps of fat.

Even Death Knight Vikir of the 9th Form is powerless against their insatiable appetite.

[Demon... kills... dies...]

Even the Death Knights of the world have no business against the countless swarms of vampires.

At the same time, the appearance of the leeches attached to the body of Death Knight Vikir began to change.

Udeudeug- udeug- ppudeug!

The leeches grew from the size of a pea to the size of a finger.

But they didn't just get bigger.

Weng-al-weng-al-

kkyaleuleuleug-

kigkigkig-

The leeches grew heads, bodies, and limbs, and their facial features began to resemble those of Vikir.

It still looked like a crude doll a child made in craft class, but the more blood it sucked, the more it resembled Vikir.

“...It's cute. You look just like my brother.”

Sinclaire reached for one of the leeches that had lost the feeding competition.

Kyaag!

The leech's eyes widened and its teeth sank in, and Sinclaire was horrified.

“What the hell, I was just trying to take care of the poor thing.”

Sinclaire grumbled a little as the leeches trotted off to suck blood again.

At least they didn't seem interested in anything other than Vikir's blood, right?

Meanwhile.

[Demon... die.]

Death Knight was slowly crumbling.

Not only was the 9th Form, which used up all of the mana, destroyed, but the 8th Form was allowed to hit the body twice in succession.

Combine that with the devastating trauma, the massive internal injuries caused by the mana surge, and the specialized creatures that Black Tongue had developed to capture Vikir, and it was clear that even the Death Knight who can use the 9th Form of Baskerville would not have the stamina to survive.

In the end, Vikir's residual thoughts, the ghosts of the old world, crumbled.

[Demons Kill... Demons Kill...]

Vikir tries to stand up despite his collapsing ego and crumbling body.

Vikir stared down at himself.

And then.

“Don't worry.”

He reached out and covered the eyes of the remnant of consciousness that had fallen to the ground.

“The age of destruction will never come again.”

And then something incredible happened.

The ghost's expression, stained with black blood and an even blacker shade under its eyes, relaxed slightly.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsuts...

In an instant, Vikir's body turned to blackened ash and scattered to the ground.

The wind blew it around a few times, and soon there was nothing left.

“....”

Vikir stared dryly into the direction of the wind.

The Age of Destruction.

Even an old man who has lived many lifetimes of hatred and anger does not know where the end of the road lies.

Then.

Creeping...

The sensation of something small crawling up the back of his foot.

When Vikir looked away, he saw leeches wandering around on the floor, panicked because there was nothing to eat.

The leeches, which had grown as big as fingers, were now mini-mes modeled after Vikir.

“Come on. Come back.”

Vikir dropped a drop of his own blood into the leather sack and shook it on the floor.

The leeches, smelling his blood, leaped into the sack, their mouths watering.

Vikir watched the leeches wriggle in the sack and nodded.

“Hatred for Demons... and a copy of the main body with some of its appearance and strength. Could be very useful strategically, if I can control their appetites....”

The emotions of the remnant of the previous encounter had long since dried up.

A normal person would have been overcome with sentimentality for a long time after meeting with his past self, but Vikir doesn't consider such things a luxury.

Rather, he uses the painful scars of his past and the burden of his mission to fulfill it.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca are left speechless by his nonchalant demeanor.

“If it were like before, I would have just thought of him as a boring and dull guy.”

“But after seeing that mountain of emotions....”

“I feel sorry for Vikir, he's carrying so much on his shoulders alone.”

“I don't even dare tell him to rely on us.”

They were right.

Dolores and Sinclaire could only stare at the back of Vikir's head, unable to say anything.

Finally, Vikir turned back to them and said.

“Okay. You asked me something earlier, didn't you?”

“Huh? Ah, ugh!”

Tudor nodded.

His friends were wondering how Vikir had gotten here.

“You see, I was imprisoned in Nouvelle Vague about four years ago. I escaped.”

“...No, is that that easy?”

“Well, it took a lot of work. I almost died once.”

Vikir gave a brief explanation of what had happened.

The labor at Nouvelle Vague, the solitary confinement, and then the volcano eruption.

An unbelievable tale of being shot up to the surface in a pillar of fire from the volcano.

If the speaker had not been Vikir, everyone would have thought it was an empty boast.

“When I went up, I thought I was going to die. But when I came down, I thought I was really dead. After I fell, I lost my memory for a while, so I wandered off. I worked in a fishing village catching warm fish and drying dried fish.......”

Vikir frowned.

“I was fortunate that my two colleagues who escaped with me found me. When I saw familiar faces, the memories quickly came back. That's why they immediately moved to assassinate Passamonte. But he was so focused on you guys that his guard was down.”

“Ugh! That's too much, you should warn us!”

“I didn't tell you on purpose, because I think you're already somewhat imbued with the demon's brainwashing. Sometimes you have to deceive your own allies before you can deceive your enemies.”

Everyone nodded at Vikir's words.

Clearly, at some point, they had fallen for Passamonte's scheme.

“...Damn. He has some sort of hypnotic ability to make his opponents reckless. I've seen it firsthand, and it's dangerous.”

Vikir nodded as if he already knew.

Just then, Bianca, who had seen the conversation between Tudor and Vikir, burst out laughing.

“You two have become quite similar in personality, haven't you?”

The comment wasn't limited to Tudor.

Over the past four years, every single one of the Night Walkers had become more and more like Vikir.

The tone, the way they spoke, even their personalities.

It wasn't just because Vikir's presence loomed large in their minds.

It was a change in personality that was inherent in living through such fierce and harsh times, and everyone was slowly going through it.

“I suppose most people's personalities change similarly as the destruction approaches.”

“The real thing hasn't even started yet.”

“So, in a few years from now I'll be talking like that too?”

Vikir smiled faintly at Tudor's playful comment.

Certainly, most of his former comrades-in-arms before the regression had similar personalities.

In extreme situations, the unique characteristics of an individual, such as personality or qualities, may gradually wear out and become more consistent with the overall average.

Then. Sinclaire asked, as if out of the blue.

“So, what was my brother's personality like before all those traumatic experiences?”

All eyes turned to Vikir.

They didn't say anything, but they all looked very curious.

It wasn't a difficult question, so Vikir opened his mouth to answer.

“According to my nanny, who raised me as a child, ... I was shy and introverted. My favorite hobbies were playing with dolls and flower arranging. Of course, they were soon forbidden by the family tradition.”

“Ooh... really doesn't suit you?”

Everyone could only nod slowly at Tudor's words.

Finally, Vikir had everyone's attention.

“It's time to get out of here.”

“But how do we get out?”

“We'll have to use the same trick we used to get out of theHell Tree once more.”

Vikir turned his head to look at Pigi.

Pigi's blood has mysterious powers.

It acts as a deadly poison to demons, distorting the space they create and causing it to close.

Vikir's gaze met him.

'...He's a good person.'

A strange voice flashed through Pigi's head for a moment.

“Huh?”

Pigi's head jerked from side to side in surprise, but no one was speaking to him except for Vikir.

'...What was that?'

It was a tinnitus he often heard, but it had never been as clear as it was now, so Pigi looked a bit puzzled.

'Come to think of it, I think I used to have these visions when I was at the Academy.'

As Pigi pondered this, Vikir spoke up.

“Pigi. Do you think I could borrow some of your blood?”

“Of course, if I can be of any help!”

Vikir quickly obtained a few drops of blood from Pigi.

With Pigi's blood on him, Beelzebub shoots a long line of blood into the air.

Crackle-!

The space within the Hell Tree began to twist and tear.

It was the same phenomenon as before.

“We'll ambush the demon as soon as we get out. He won't be expecting us.”

Everyone's faces hardened with tension.

This is the second time they're striking first against an opponent they've already lost to once, so the pressure is on.

But unlike the first time, everyone's faces are much brighter.

This time, they had an ally they didn't have in their first attempt.

Vikir ended his speech with a short sentence.

“...Let's go out and give him a blow.”

His voice sounded just as reliable as it had four years ago.

Chapter 435

Dreaming the Impossible Dream (1)

◆

Crackle-!

The sudden crack in the air was enough to scare Passamonte.

“What's this!?”

What happens inside the Hell Tree is unknown to anyone but its master, Amdusias himself.

Passamonte was horrified to see the blazing portal and the sword protruding from it.

Suddenly, a thick fog formed in front of his eyes, and he began to hear and see strange things.

'...He's a good person.'

A voice as weak and unsteady as the last breath of a dying animal, unknown in source and identity.

Passamonte's ears flicked back, and a strange vision began to form before his eyes.

Swamps of blood and flesh, mountains of bones, an atmosphere drained of all mana, and giant mushroom clouds rising over the distant horizon.

...And an endless, barren desert.

...A massive tower stands tall in the middle of the desert.

...An old man in black walking lonely and alone toward the Tower.

Each vision pierces his mind in fragmented pieces.

“What, these are Amdusias's memories, what did that bastard see before he died?”

Passamonte rubbed his temples as if he was dumbfounded.

An undiscovered substance that twisted the laws of causality. Something with the power to close spaces opened by demons.

It probably has something to do with that sword that's creating the cracks before his eyes.

...Then, it tore open the gate to the Hell Tree, revealing Vikir within.

Passamonte asked in disbelief.

“What did you tear open the Hell Tree with? It doesn't seem to be the sword's inherent power.”

“Blood.”

“Whose?”

Passamonte repeated his puzzlement at Vikir's short answer.

But he was under no obligation to answer the question.

Vikir drew his blade out at length.

“Find out for yourself.”

At the same time, the fastest and most efficient swordsmanship, the 4th Baskerville Form, unfolded.

Passamonte grunted and jumped to his feet as Vikir's killing blow stretched out as naturally as breathing.

...Kwakwang!

The stone pillar shattered into pieces, raising a cloud of dust.

Behind Vikir stood Dolores, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire, all of whom also wore grim expressions.

And as the dust cleared, the true enemy hiding in the Donquixote family appeared before them.

Black armor, black skin underneath, and an all-encompassing blackness that obscured his eyes and nose, but revealed his white, sharp teeth.

He held a large spear in his hand, and his lower body was fused with the body of a black horse, with only the horse's head remaining as a skeleton.

With a searing aura covering his entire body like a mane, the black knight was no longer named Donquixote La Mancha Passamonte.

<Cimeries the 4th Corpse>

Danger Rating : S+

Size: ?

Found in: 'Serpent's Womb', deep within the Gate of Destruction

-Also known as '4th Corpse'.

One of the Ten Plagues, natural enemies of mankind, incomprehensible and unkillable.

“A swarm of reckless frogs shall arise.”

– The Ten Commandments 10: Top –

'Reckless Knight' Cimeries.

It was the appearance of the sixth mastermind of the Age of Destruction.

Vikir gave a brief warning to his comrades behind him.

“His breath will give you an unfounded sense of confidence and exaltation that will cloud your judgment. Avoid breathing as much as possible in close combat.”

Like a frog that puffs up its belly to match its size with a bull, only to have its skin burst and die, Cimeries has a strange ability to make its enemies reckless.

Combine this with the power of Dantalian and Belial, both skilled in military strategy and tactics, and the results can be devastating.

It's one of the main reasons the Alliance has lost so many battles in a row.

Even before Vikir's regression, Donquixote's Invincible Cavalry, brainwashed by Cimeries, charged the windmill with their horses, only to be annihilated in vain.

'We must get rid of him now, before the cataclysm. And Donquixote must be restored.'

Vikir took a step forward, his resolve unwavering.

“Vikir, I'll support you!”

Dolores stood beside him and offered her support.

Their souls, now in perfect resonance with each other, generated a great amplitude and manifested it in the form of an aura.

Kwakwakwang!

Vikir's sword and Cimeries's spear clashed.

The result was a whistle.

Neither Vikir nor Cimeries took a step back from each other as they continued with the next move.

Kwaang! Kkang- ujijijijig!

The black storm created as the spear rotates twists and turns to take the shape of a huge snake.

The tooth-shaped traces created by the sword gathered in one place and became the shape of a large sphere.

Like a snake with its jaws open, about to swallow the sun.

In the midst of the fierce battle, Vikir and Cimeries continue to clash, with their bodies supporting the pressure that threatens to burst.

Boom-!

Once the spear was extended, a hole was created in the several-layered castle wall.

...Boom!

With a single swing of the sword, everything behind him was sliced away, revealing a clear view of the outside of the castle.

[Incredible. How could a human possess such power...]

While Cimeries was muttering in disbelief, Vikir was also having thoughts of his own.

'The power of Cimeries is much the same as it was before the regression. The demons have gotten impatient and are building up their power in a hurry, and it will be dangerous if I take any more time.'

It's not just the Fourth, it's the Third, the Second, and the First.

Vikir decided to hurry things up a bit more.

“Let's do it.”

Normally, he would have handled whatever was going on on his own, but... this was different.

Dolores, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire's faces lit up at Vikir's request for help.

“Let me help!”

“Trust me, my friend!”

“I've been training hard, and I'm more than capable of holding my own!”

“Take my blood!”

“Just look at the gap, boys!”

“Brother, fight from a little distance, I'll cover you with magic!”

Dolores's holy shield, Tudor's spear, Sancho's axe, Pigi's sword, Bianca's arrow, and Sinclaire's magic formed a colorful aura and flew out to intercept Cimeries.

[Keughh! These annoying things...!?]

Cimeries spun his spear around and launched a blow toward the back.

[Long time no see, Cimeries].

The red-hot inverted pentagram created by Decarabia was blocking Cimeries' blow.

Before Cimeries could even shout something.

...Puug!

Night Hound sank its teeth into the nape of its prey's neck.

The teeth, now much larger and sharper due to the saintess's blessing, sank into the demon's flesh with ease.

[Keughhhh!]

Bubbling froth began to rise from Cimeries's mouth.

Ppudeudeug!

Cimeries stepped back, risking the flesh of his neck being ripped off in chunks.

Then, out of the horse's chest cavity, Pasamonte's face emerged.

He began to open his mouth, dripping with tears.

[Yes. I will admit that you guys are annoying enemies.]

He spoke with a hint of reserve, which was to be expected.

This was the lair that Cimeries had spent so much time working on.

It is he who now holds the reins of power in Donquixote.

[Then I will respond with all my might].

With that, Cimeries pulled out a blue whistle and placed it in Pasamonte's mouth.

Tudor was the first to recognize what it was.

“That's the horn of the Invincible Cavalry!”

Cimeries had already summoned the cavalry, which was already out on the field of battle, back to the main house.

And soon, the results began to show.

Ttuuuuu-

A whistle sounded, and the floor began to vibrate slightly.

Dudeudeudeudeudeudeu...

Tiny pieces of stone bounced and danced across the floor.

Dolores and Sinclaire's faces hardened.

“This sound is....”

“It's the sound of horses running!”

The sound of countless horses galloping from far away.

Donquixote, who heard the summons order from the head of the family, was returning with the strongest power of the Invincible Cavalry!

The two pillars that symbolize Donquixote, the 'Invincible Cavalry' and the 'Invincible Armada'. And those who were now gathering were the full force of the Invincible Cavalry.

Tudor shouted.

“Vikir, Donquixote's Invincible Cavalry is as powerful as the Seven Counts of Baskerville, and if they join the battle, we have no chance of winning!”

It was fortunate that the sea level had dropped too low for the Invincible Armada to reach these shores.

If it had been accompanied by a fleet bombardment, there would have been no answer.

Vikir parried a flying spear and opened his mouth.

“The Invincible Cavalry, I know their power.”

Even they would have been rendered reckless by the power of Cimeries.

No matter how strong Vikir was, he would be no match for all the knights of the Invincible Cavalry who would blindly charge at him.

...However.

In the face of all these odds, Vikir remained calm.

“But there is no need to worry. I have a plan for the Invincible Cavalry.”

Suddenly, beyond the tattered wall, the form of the Invincible Cavalry came into view.

Donquixote's Invincible Cavalry, charging over the long horizon, was indeed overwhelming from afar.

...However.

Kung!

A strange thing began to happen.

One of the knights who was running furiously at the forefront fell from his horse and rolled on the ground.

The horse tripped on something and fell.

Kwakwakwang! Ujijijig!

The same thing began to happen one after another.

The cavalry, which had been charging at a terrifying pace, was thrown to the ground along with their horses.

It was caused by a hook sprouting from the ground.

The ground was littered with tiny traps, just the right size to catch a foot in, that looked like tiny iron skewers bent into arches.

The Invincible Cavalry can't keep up with the speed of the rush, and they get caught in these traps.

Charging speeds diminished in an instant. Collapsing displays.

[No, what the hell is going on!?]

Cimeries' mouth drops open as he watches the Invincible Cavalry struggling, unable to even make it to the shoreline, let alone the main castle.

The situation was so ridiculous that even the demons were stunned.

And at the same time.

Flutter.

A long, reddish streamer of blood fluttered from the roof of the opposite spire.

“Hey, boyfriend, over here!”

All eyes turned to the top of the spire at the sound of a cheerful voice.

The owner of a trap for hunting only cavalry, who stuck countless skewers into the ground and bent them so that they were not visible to the eye.

A woman standing bravely with an expression that reveals the wait, confidence, and reward of the past four years.

Camus Morgue stood there.

Chapter 438

Dreaming the Impossible Dream(4)

◆

The restoration of Donquixote, the Spearman.

The knights who roamed the vast expanse of the sea with a single spear were freed from demonic control and served their rightful masters.

Tudor Donquixote. He is the heir to the former head of the family, Cervantes, and the true owner of the Donquixote family. The Lion King.

The exiled young lion returned to the family as an adult and avenged his father's enmity by slaying his evil uncle.

In normal times, this would have turned the entire empire upside down, but in these times, issues of this magnitude are rarely publicized.

It was a time of civil war, with thousands and tens of thousands of people dying every day.

However, the normalization of the Donquixote family was a great blessing for the Night Walkers.

“The supply routes are finally open again.”

Dolores said cheerfully.

The supply lines that the demons had cut had been reopened.

Food and water were finally flowing back into Fort Tochka.

The ever-increasing number of refugees could have caused great chaos.

“....”

Vikir stared at the view of Tochka from the conference room window.

High, thick walls.

A plateau where oxygen is scarce.

A rocky plateau surrounded by sheer cliffs.

It is definitely a tall and lonely fortress with iron walls.

“The only problem is that we don't have enough drinking water. It would be nice to be able to get our own, at least there's a section over one of the mountains where I suspect there's a water source.”

Dolores looked at the map and muttered wistfully.

But Vikir's demeanor was unperturbed.

“The water problem will be solved soon enough.”

“...?”

Dolores and the others looked puzzled, but Vikir didn't say anything more.

At that moment, Tudor, at one end of the table, spoke up.

“We now have a complete picture of the power situation in the Donquixote family.”

Tudor, the new head of the Donquixote family, had decided to cooperate fully with the Night Walkers.

It was a natural progression.

“We've completely rooted out the demons, and reinstated all those who have been purged or cast out.”

“How many of them can fight?”

Vikir asked, and Tudor didn't hesitate to reveal all the classified documents.

“Surprisingly, it's not too bad, about sixty percent of them are intact, but most of them are in the fleet. The cavalry took too much damage this time....”

As Tudor spoke, he glanced at the people around him.

Camus was sitting there with her arms crossed.

“Well. Are you saying that I'm to blame for the destruction of your family's cavalry?”

“Oh, no. It's not like that. The reason the Invincible Cavalry suffered so much damage was because they were brainwashed by demons and kept running in circles around the civil war zone. Who else could I blame but my incompetence and the wicked demons themselves?”

Tudor smirked.

But it would not be a laughing matter.

Donquixote's pride of Invincible Cavalry had been nearly wiped out.

Even if he avenged his father's enemies and skinned the demon to make the tassels that hang down the blades of his spears, it would not be enough.

Vikir gazed at the strap of Cimeries's leash hanging from the base of Tudor spear Gungnir and spoke.

“It will make the knights around you braver. Carry it with you at all times.”

“...Thank you.”

Nodding toward Vikir, Tudor continued.

“Still, Donquixote's Invincible Armada has remained largely unscathed and unharmed. It must be that the sea level has dropped significantly, preventing the fleet from reaching the coast, which hasn't been very helpful in the civil war.”

Vikir's eyes sharpened at Tudor's words.

“That's enough.”

It was Donquixote's Invincible Armada that had interested Vikir the most.

Many people had questioned that.

“But, brother, why do we need an Invincible Armada so much? We're in the middle of a civil war in the center of the continent, and there's not much of a naval battle going on, is there? Even if it's because of the supply routes by sea, the fleet won't be of much use now that the sea level has dropped so much?”

Sinclaire's question was on the minds of everyone in the room.

Vikir looked up from the map to answer this point.

“Soon the fleet will become very important. And when that moment comes, Tochka's water crisis will be solved....”

Right then. Vikir was interrupted by a voice.

“Pushishishi- that damn meeting, meeting, meeting. What kind of boring shit do you do every day without getting tired of it?”

There aren't many in the group who can interrupt Vikir in the first place.

Marquis de Sade, who was staring at Vikir with a bored-to-death expression on his face.

“Vikir. You know that, right? There are now two left.”

Sade held up two fingers and smirked.

When he had escaped from Nouvelle Vague, Sade had been indebted to Vikir.

In return, he had promised to kill up to three people of Vikir's choosing, which is why he's been following him ever since.

Orca, sitting next to Sade with his arms crossed, is a similar story.

“Unlike this escapee, I'm a man of my word. You said I'd protect up to three people you wanted, and now there are two left.”

Sade was referring to Passamonte, Orca was referring to Tudor.

Both had been indirectly killed and indirectly protected, but it had helped, so that was enough.

“ ...I remember that well.”

Vikir nodded and looked away.

“Is Cindywendy still here? We need to know what happened to Usher so we can figure out our next move.”

“I'm afraid not.”

The door to the conference room opened before Vikir could finish his sentence.

Cindywendy, clutching a stack of papers, walked around the corner of the table and sat down.

“Aren't you working your soon-to-be sister-in-law a little too hard these days?”

“I thought you didn't like being associated with the Baskervilles?”

Cindywendy smirked at Vikir's comment.

“People change, and I was able to put the Baskervilles out of my mind some time ago.”

“....”

“What about you, are you still carrying it around?”

Vikir's mouth fell open at that, and he remained silent for a long moment.

Cindywendy had joined forces with the Baskervilles, who had destroyed her family.

She claimed to be a hostess and to rule over the Baskervilles, but in reality, she had compromised and given up her vengeance.

“Enough with the chatter.”

Everyone in the room flinched at the sound of Vikir's unusually sharp voice.

Had she touched the reverse scale?

Vikir's voice was sharp enough to make even the mighty Sade and Orca cringe.

This was Vikir's true self, rarely seen except when dealing with demons.

However, Cindywendy quickly changed the subject with her characteristic smirk.

“Oh, my God, you look just like you did when you were standing outside the prison bars, nothing has changed.”

She shoved a stack of papers in front of Vikir.

“I'm scared, so I'll just cut to the chase.”

As usual, Cindywendy cut to the chase.

1. Signs that the Empire's civil war is about to escalate.

2. An alliance between the Morgue and Baskervilles.

3. An alliance between the Quovadis and Bourgeois.

4. Leviathan and Usher form an alliance.

5. Donquixote's declaration of neutrality and sealing of the gates.

“...Um. Other than that, the only thing I can think of is that the Quovadis declared a crusade against the Leviathan because of the Red Death. You know that Donquixote declares neutrality and stays out of the civil war because Lord Tudor himself said so.”

The Quovadis declared a crusade against the Leviathan in the aftermath of the Red Death long ago.

By their very nature, large group movements are slow to get started, but once they do, they pick up tremendous speed.

Donquixote decided to close the family for a time to repair the damage done by the civil war and due to various procedures for changing the head of the family.

Of course, it's only a nominal blockade, and since Tudor became the head of the family, it was natural for the Donquixote family to secretly support Night Walkers.

Camus set her chin and looked at Vikir.

“We've joined forces, haven't we? Looks like mom's decided to go all in and back the second prince. The one we don't know where he is, or if he even exists in the first place.”

“Perhaps it's more about keeping the First Prince in check than actually following the Second, since we Quovadis are in the same position.”

Dolores spoke up, looking at Vikir across from Camus.

Their gazes met in the air, and Sinclaire reached behind Vikir's back, over his shoulder, and pointed to the map.

“Our Bourgeois are still looking for the Second Prince, and the rumors of imperial enrollment in the Academy are our best lead at the moment.”

Civil war is all about cause.

The demons rally under a single goal, while the humans are pitted against each other under many banners.

Vikir thought of the rumored Second Prince.

Before his regression, the second prince had ultimately disappeared into thin air.

A mysterious figure whose existence was never really known.

'If he really is alive somewhere, maybe he could have united humanity sooner.'

Vikir's mind wandered this far, and he lifted his head to look at Cindywendy.

“Of the Seven Families of the Empire, which one is the knowledgeable in information?”

“...Hmm. That's right, it's God Killer. The Usher Family, of course, since they have the most people who specialize in assassination and infiltration.”

Just as Cindywendy was finishing her answer, the door to the conference room opened as if by appointment.

Bianca, looking furious, addressed everyone.

“The members of the God Killer Sniper Squad have been unbrainwashed, and I've heard all about what's going on within the Family.”

At the same time, Vikir's eyes sank deeply.

The Usher had not yet been freed from their demonic possession and were one of the key players in this civil war.

Now that the Donquixote family has been restored, there is no family more threatening than Leviathan and Usher.

And it is Usher Poe Madeline who currently leads them.

The presumed third of the Ten Corpses.

Drac-

The first to rise from his seat upon hearing Bianca's words was none other than Tudor.

It was Bianca who saved Tudor at the moment of Donquixote's downfall.

And now Tudor, Vikir, and all the other friends were reaching out to Bianca.

“Come with us. Perhaps your family can be saved.”

“....”

Light returned to Bianca's eyes, which had been black and dead.

At the same time, her cheeks were turning red.

“We must hurry. We must drive on before news of Donquixote reaches them.”

At Vikir's words, the eyes of all the Night Walkers burned with determination.

“Pushishishi- So we have our second objective now?”

“This will reduce our debt.”

Sade and Orca followed Vikir to their feet.

The second demon hunt was about to begin.

This was extremely unusual for Vikir's hunting patterns, as he usually left a long gap between hunts.

Chapter 440

The Fall of Usher (2)

◆

The Ushers' mansion was indeed a fortress.

Whereas Tochka was a natural fortress created by the natural environment, Usher's mansion was a man-made fortress filled with all sorts of bizarre traps.

Frames of books and paintings that sometimes collapsed, curtains that fluttered even when there was no wind, the cogs of a slow-moving clock, statues that suddenly burst into laughter, plants that withered and died in pots, stuffed animals, brick walls that were stacked on top of each other, chandeliers that were overly grandiose, and so on... were all traps filled with malice toward intruders.

But Bianca, who was born the owner of the mansion and has lived in it all her life, was able to tear through them all and get inside.

“The only time it's safe to walk through the halls is when the bookshelves collapse and the books on them fall, but only for ghost stories, not for other genres. Only when books titled 'The Masque of the Red Death,' 'The Black Cat,' 'The Cask of Amontillado,' 'The Jumping Frog, or Eight Orangutans in Chains,' 'The Heart of Treachery,' and 'The Adventures of Arthur Gordon Pym' fall to the floor.”

“Whenever the curtains flutter even a little, you must get low to the floor. It doesn't matter if the wind is blowing or not.”

“When the bell rings, the secret door between the hallways opens. Of course, you can't go in right away. You have to wait exactly five minutes before opening it, otherwise you might end up in a door that leads to a completely different place.”

“When that statue laughs, you have to be careful around the whole area, because while it doesn't trigger any traps... it likes to think that an intruder is about to die a miserable death.”

“If you see a plant in a pot and it's shriveled up and dead, don't walk past it. We don't grow any plants in our family.”

“Stuffed animals are okay to walk past. But some of them have moving eyeballs, and if I see one of those, always cover your ears and run fast.”

“If you see a red brick wall, make sure you never touch it, but if you do, run away from it immediately, and don't turn around if someone calls your name from behind.”

“Under no circumstances should you pass under a chandelier. But if you must, never look at the chandelier. Instead, keep your eyes on the shadow of the chandelier on the floor.”

Bianca continued through the many traps and labyrinths into the depths of the mansion.

Tudor, following close behind, said in a low voice.

“ ...I see why your personality is so twisted.”

“What, you bastard?”

Bianca squeezed Tudor's head once, then turned her head away.

“Heh, well. It's a little far from the usual.”

She added in a tiny whisper at the end.

“...Thanks for following me here, though.”

“What?”

“I didn't say anything. Let's go.”

Bianca dragged Tudor along.

Soon, Bianca and Tudor were standing in front of patriarch Roderick Usher's bedroom.

This room, too, was thick with the red death.

An unbearable level of poisonous venom spreads through the mansion, along with the watery mist that pours in.

It was like a clown, a dancing demon, spinning and jumping through the empty corridors.

Bianca and Tudor felt a surge of nausea even though they drank the saint's tears produced by Dolores.

Then the door to the bedroom opened.

Kkigigigigig-

The rusted hinges let out a dying groan.

The sight inside the slowly opening door made Bianca and Tudor's eyes widen.

“Father!”

Bianca exclaimed uncontrollably.

Seated in a chair in an awkward position is unmistakably Roderick, Bianca's father and current head of the Usher family.

He was pale enough to be a corpse at first glance, with a mummified complexion and a skeleton as thin as a mummy, but his eyes were wide and alive.

“....”

But he didn't seem to be in any condition to speak.

A black tongue moved a few times inside his parched and shriveled lips, but nothing came out of his charred throat but the sound of a broken clockwork.

“...Father, in such a horrible state!”

Bianca stroked Roderick's cheeks in disbelief.

But when she looked into his eyes, there was nothing in them.

Just dull, cloudy whites, with creepy flesh embedded in the center, fixed straight ahead.

Tudor bit his lip as he watched Roderick's condition.

“ ...It's the same condition as my father's.”

Just as Cervantes, the Spear King, had died of the Red Death, leaving him a wasted man, Roderick was in the same condition.

Just as Cervantes, the Spear King, suffered the Red Death and died in a state of ruin, Roderick was also in the same state.

“The Red Death is spreading through the mist inside the mansion, and the demon must have released its poison into the swamp, for the mansion was built on swampy ground, and the entire place has been gradually poisoned.”

After assessing the situation, Tudor pulled firecrackers from his arms.

Red and black firecrackers.

'Determine whether Roderick, patriarch of the Usher family, is alive or dead, and if he is alive and able to escape with you, set off the red firecracker; if he is dead, or if he is alive but unable to move, set off the black firecracker.'

Vikir had said this before entering the Usher's mansion.

Tudor's eyes dropped to his hands, and he bit his lip in thought.

“He's alive. Roderick is alive.”

Tudor's choice was a red firecracker.

Tudor is about to take it to the window.

Then.

...Teoeog!

A hand snatched Tudor's wrist.

It was Bianca.

“...Are you crazy?”

She snatched the red firecracker from Tudor's hand and tossed it into the swamp outside the window.

“Are you going to kill all the other kids?”

“No! Roderick is alive!”

“Don't you remember what Vikir said? My father... My father can't move anymore.”

Bianca lowered her head and trembled.

If anyone wanted to light a red firecracker more than anyone else at this moment, it was her.

Tudor could only look at her and bow his head in awe.

Just then.

“Hohohoho- Aren't you giving up too soon?”

A voice caught Bianca and Tudor's attention.

Turning their heads, they saw a woman with the same pale complexion as a corpse standing there in a casual manner.

Usher Poe Madeline. Roderick's sister and current acting head of family.

A shadowy figure who practically wielded the power of the Usher family.

“The same father, the same daughter. Even though your blood relatives are still alive, you are hastily treating them as dead.”

Madeline glared at Bianca with her corpse-like eyes.

Then she spoke, her voice filled with mockery.

“Are you going to bury your father alive too? Just like your father did to me.”

Madeline suffered from severe fever when she was young.

And Roderick buried her under the ground, with both her heartbeat and complexion changed to that of a corpse.

But somehow, some way, Madeline was alive.

After she was buried alive, she broke open the coffin, dug through the soil, and emerged through the center of the tomb.

Roderick was haunted for the rest of his life by the guilt of almost burying his sickly sister alive.

He would do anything she asked of him, and he would risk anything for her.

Eudeug-

Bianca gritted her teeth.

“You've been a demon from the start, haven't you, taking the body of my Aunt Madeline, who died of a fever, and deceiving my father all this time?”

“Hohoho- Well, I don't know. When did I really become a demon? When I was buried alive, or when I was born, or, I mean, was I ever a demon in the first place?”

Madeline had been closing the distance between her and Bianca.

Then. A line was drawn between Bianca and Madeline.

“Do not cross the line.”

Tudor. His unwavering gaze held Madeline at bay.

Madeline's eyes narrowed at the sight of Gungnir in his lone arm and the leather hanging down the hilt of his spear.

“Skinning the flesh of Pasamonte and using it to decorate your spear? Playing with the corpse of your uncle, whom you defeated in a contest for the throne, seems a bit grotesque for a knight of Donquixote's reputation for justice and virtue.”

Despite Madeline's scowl, Tudor did not lose sight of his original purpose.

Teog-

Grabbing Bianca's hand, Tudor turned and started running.

“Come on, Bianca, we have to get out of here!”

But Tudor and Bianca's efforts were in vain.

Madeline reached out her hand and the world around her froze, then a thick wall of ice rose up and blocked the window.

“Kuagh!”

Tudor stopped in his tracks for a moment.

And then Madeline's seductive voice whispered softly in his ear.

“I see you wish to leave the mansion, but not without my permission.”

“....”

“Hohoho- Would you stop looking at me so scary?”

Madeline covered her mouth with her hand and smiled gracefully.

Then, as if in good faith, she continued.

“Well, actually, it's not too difficult to get you out of the mansion, if you can pass my test.”

“Throw away the thought of deceiving me with your tongue.”

Tudor turned his back to the ice wall and held his spear tightly.

But the words that came out of Madeline's mouth were unexpected.

“Seriously, if you can pass one very simple test, I'll let you out of here.”

“...?”

Tudor's brow furrowed, and Madeline continued.

“All you have to do is prove to me that you are brave enough to pass my test. Donquixote's knights are said to be very brave, so you won't be afraid, will you?”

It was a cheap provocation made blatantly, but Tudor had no choice.

Then, Madeline said.

“'Where is the person who can kill me?' If you can get those words out of your mouth three times, I will recognize your bravery. I'll even open the doors of my mansion for you.”

It was an easy deal. There are no ambushes here now, except for Madeline's.

Tudor and Bianca stared at each other, their expressions stony.

Their gazes crossed quickly in the air.

Then, once Tudor was sure there was no danger around them, he opened his mouth.

“Where is the person who can kill me? Where is the person who can kill me? Where is the person who can kill me?”

Tudor's words were spoken with unwavering faith.

There was nothing that could harm him, except the demon right in front of him.

It was an obvious truth.

...But.

Madeline's eyes softened at the sound of Tudor's voice.

The moment Tudor sheds a drop of cold sweat in front of that ominous line.

“...It is here.”

A voice that seemed to be possessed by something came from right behind Tudor, right in his ear.

Chapter 441

The Fall of Usher (3)

◆

Tudor's mind flashed back to a story Sinclaire had told him.

'It is said that once, when the Emperor went to subjugate the Usher family, the Usher family wanted to have a one-on-one conversation between the emperor and the head of the family, leaving all the attendants behind.'

The emperor experienced the betrayal of two of his closest advisors in a place where he firmly believed no one could harm him.

The assassins of the Usher family were equally stealthy and vigilant.

Tudor thought the lesson to be learned from this story was that Usher's assassins had long since earned the trust of their targets.

...But the reality was that they were one step ahead of that.

Jjiiig-

Tudor jerked his head to the side at the cold wind behind him.

Bianca's dagger sliced through his side.

“Bianca!”

Tudor's voice didn't seem to reach her.

In her dilated pupils, there was no sign of the firearm she once held.

Madeline chuckled as she watched Bianca stand like a doll.

“When members of the Usher family are in the mansion, they become brainwashed without their knowledge. In a way, the path into the mansion is the route that draws the magic circle of brainwashing, and walking along that path is the trigger condition for brainwashing.”

She winked at Tudor and continued.

“The last line you said is the trigger. Once brainwashing is activated, outsiders are considered the first priority to be killed.”

“Damn it!”

Tudor raised the spear.

Bianca, with an expressionless face, raised her bow and fired an arrow.

Peopeopeong!

The spear swung around and smashed the arrows.

But Bianca's firing speed was still so incredibly fast that even Tudor could only stagger back.

“...Ugh, you're even faster than you were when you were sober, aren't you?”

Tudor tries to force a smile and make a joke, but Bianca's expression is cold.

Madeline laughs at Bianca's doll-like transformation.

“Finally, a young, fresh body is within my grasp, and I've always been troubled by this half-rotten one!”

After speaking, Madeline took off the belly band that was covering her stomach.

Then, the rotten and crumbling belly skin and the empty abdomen inside were clearly visible.

“...Also. The real Madeline died a long time ago.”

“Hohoho- yes, I've had a hard time covering up the stench, always having to fill it with perfume or dried flowers or something. But that's gone now.”

Madeline turned her head to look at Roderick in the chair.

“Poor Roderick. Why don't you just hand over your body to me? Your daughter will pay the price for your stubbornness.”

Roderick's pupils flinched at her words.

Tudor called out to Roderick with a glimmer of hope.

“Roderick, your daughter is in danger, you must wake up, the demon is after Bianca's body!”

Tudor continued to shout as Bianca shot arrows at him with her dazed eyes.

But Roderick was frozen in place.

His pupils flickered for the briefest of moments, but then a thick mist of water and a red deathly fog enveloped him again.

Madeline chuckled.

“Hohohoho – what do you expect when you see poisonous air rising from the swamp?”

She was right.

The demon had released poison all over the swamp, and it was mixing with the moisture rising to the surface and infecting the entire mansion.

“Kugh....”

Tudor knew it, too.

It would be impossible to cleanse the mansion without clearing the entirety of this watery fog that enveloped the grounds.

That's why Vikir had told him to lure the demons out of the mansion, as fighting inside would be futile.

However, Bianca's rushing toward him makes that impossible.

Even if Tudor ran outside, the demon wouldn't budge.

The demon would not move, for she already had the body she wanted so badly.

“Wake up, Bianca!”

Tudor shoved her back against the spearhead and turned the blade.

Rather than deal with Bianca, he intended to go straight for Madeline behind her.

However.

“Hohohoho- that's not going to work.”

Madeline was still standing there, unmoving.

A posture of absolute confidence and arrogance.

Kkilig-

Bianca aims her arrow at Tudor's back as he runs towards Madeline.

Then.

“...!”

Madeline's eyes widen slightly.

To her surprise, despite Bianca's arrow pointed at his back, Tudor hadn't turned around and was running toward her.

Kiiiiing-

An aura as blue as a tidal wave rises at the tip of Gungnir.

It could be seen that he was truly putting all his strength into the front, not caring about the threat behind him.

“Hohohoho- What, you trust your friend, you think she won't shoot an arrow?”

“Shut up!”

Tudor continued to run toward the front where Madeline was.

Even though Bianca, standing behind, is aiming at Tudor's back with her bow and arrow.

The corners of Madeline's eyes curved seductively.

“Poor thing. Who wouldn't be a fool from the Donquixote family? To be killed by the arrow of the woman he loves. The end of love is the grave, after all.”

Then, turning to Bianca behind her, she commanded coldly.

“Shoot, my dear. Let's make it easy for him.”

With Madeline's command, Bianca moved immediately.

Without hesitation, Bianca drew her weapon, pointing it at her friend Tudor's back.

Then, a single arrow fired with tremendous momentum.

...Pow!

A powerful charge containing all of Bianca's power and mana was fired, creating a gray-white gust of wind.

It flew in a graceful parabola and landed directly in Tudor's back.

Peoeog-

The sound of tearing flesh and splattering blood echoed through the room with a piercing sound.

“Hohohohoho- they're disgusting, they're such sloppy people! Now, both Usher and Donquixote are over!”

Madeline burst into laughter as she saw Bianca's arrow pierce Tudor's back.

...However.

Her laughter did not last long.

Peoeog-

A stream of red blood spurted from Tudor's back and stomach.

Bianca's arrow had clearly pierced Tudor's body.

And at that moment, as if he knew in advance the direction and location of the arrow's flight, Tudor twisted his stance to the side, rotating his body so that the arrow would tear through the flesh of his side and fly away.

The arrow passes through Tudor's body, leaving only a relatively light wound.

The arrow is stained red by Tudor's blood.

Ppeo-eog!

It flew straight on without losing any of its power, and surprisingly, it lodged itself in the center of Madeline's forehead.

“Kuugh!”

Madeline gasped as the arrow pierced her skull and exited the back of her head.

Her vision went black and her thoughts were cut off for a moment.

Her entire body began to shake and tremble.

Even a demon could not help but be shaken by an unexpected arrow piercing its head.

Moreover, what is this black blood on the arrowhead...!

'...Please go to a comfortable place.'

Strange voices in her head, and memories that were not her own began to surface in the center of her blackened vision.

A body growing cold. The rough palm that covered her vision. A face and voice full of scars.

'...He's a good person.'

At the same time, Madeline felt her entire body tremble violently.

She felt her fingers and toes twisting and curling strangely, like the body of an insect curling inward when it dies.

“Kuuuuuuuggghhh”

Madeline groaned as her body twisted and turned.

Just then.

“Run!”

Bianca's pupils returned to their normal color.

She grabbed Tudor by the back of the neck as he staggered, bleeding from the side, and turned and started running.

The ice wall crumbled from Madeline's impact, and Bianca and Tudor threw themselves through the window beyond.

At the same time.

...Pusyug!

Tudor lit the black firecracker he'd been holding since the moment the arrow pierced his body.

“...No way. You're not brainwashed! How!”

Madeline was still running forward, unbowed, despite the arrow piercing her forehead and the back of her head.

But was it too unexpected? It didn't stop Bianca and Tudor from throwing

...Pungdeong!

Swampy muck and mire surrounded them.

An unpleasant sensation, as if the evil spirit of the red death was sticking out its long tongue and licking their entire body.

But in the midst of it all, Tudor and Bianca looked at each other and held their hearts together.

Then, Tudor's arms, which were above the surface, were stretched high.

Bianca was holding on to him so that he wouldn't sink into the swamp.

Poof!

A firecracker exploded. A black pillar stretched high into the sky.

So that we can clearly see beyond the ridge where Vikir is waiting after completing some preparations.

“It's a success!”

Without even thinking about who went first, Tudor and Bianca hugged each other.

“Good job, Bianca! That last arrow went in!”

“...I wouldn't have made it if it weren't for Pigi's blood on the arrowhead.”

But the job isn't completely done yet.

[Kuaaaaaaaaagh- These cheeky bugs!]

The scream that erupted from the window was clearly not human.

A voice that pierced the listener's eardrums and drove fear like a stake through them.

A demon's voice.

There was no doubt that Madeline was showing her true colors.

As soon as they heard it, Tudor and Bianca nodded as if they had made a promise.

Tudor and Bianca quickly dived down to the bottom of the swamp, knowing that their goal was to lure the demon out of the mansion.

Boom.

It's too far to swim to the bridge that connects the mansion to the surface.

It's better to move slowly, underwater, holding their breath as best they can, than to risk being caught by the demon right away.

Tudor and Bianca swam beneath the black, rippling water.

Reddish will-o'-the-wisp lights were circling above the water, giving a clear view of the eerie and grim scene beneath the water.

...Kwakwang! Pungdeong- pungdeong- pungdeong- cheombeong!

Behind them, the windows of the mansion shattered, and they could feel the debris of the shattered windows falling to the surface of the swamp.

The surface of the water distorted wildly.

[...Where are you! ...Where are you!]

Somehow, the demon's voice came straight from the water.

Tudor and Bianca fought back a chill down their spines and dived deeper and deeper.

Black water plants reached out like water ghosts.

Tudor and Bianca ducked under the fiery glow of the will-o'-the-wisp and into the forest of aquatic vegetation.

They began to push their way through the heavy muck and ripples of the swamp floor, where many things had sunk.

Slowly. Slowly. To lure the demon out of the mansion.

Toward the ridge beyond, where Vikir and the others were waiting.

Chapter 442

The Fall of Usher (4)

◆

“Pu-haa!”

It was already the middle of the night when Tudor and Bianca crawled out of the water.

The air was icy cold. The wind cut like a knife.

As they turned their heads, they could see the Usher mansion casting a grim shadow over the swampy area that was filled with evil spirits of the Red Death.

“Get it.”

“...Yes.”

Tudor took Bianca's outstretched hand.

Hand in hand, they raced down the mountain path.

Pudeudeug-

A bird flapped its wings behind them.

Tudor and Bianca ran frantically through the dead trees that sprouted up like spines from burned corpses.

Their faces and bodies were scratched by sharp branches and thorns, but they had no time to think about it.

Red death dancing with phosphorus and sulfur fire and water mist wandering over the swamp.

Tudor and Bianca ran to their deaths through the darkness, relying on the fading favor of the saintess.

Pudeudeug-

The sound of birds flapping their wings came a little closer.

Then.

...Thud!

Tudor stopped running and fell to his knees on the ground.

Bianca gasped and helped him up.

“Tudor, are you okay?”

“...Um.”

A reddish glow continued to spread across Tudor's side where Bianca's arrow had grazed him.

It was a fatal wound, even if it only grazed.

Bianca hesitated for a moment, then spoke with determination.

“Get up.”

“....”

But Tudor shook his head.

“You never know when the demon will come after you. Vikir told us never to let our guard down until we're over the ridge.”

“Do you think I'm letting my guard down right now?”

“Uh. It looks that way.”

Tudor quietly pushed Bianca away.

“You go ahead. I'll get some rest and catch up.”

“Don't give a shit.”

Bianca closes the distance that Tudor pushed away.

She grabbed Tudor by the scruff of the neck and spoke.

“You realize there's nothing cool about what you're doing, right?”

“I'm not doing this to be cool. Do you still not know me?”

“So you know me?”

“....”

Tudor and Bianca's gazes locked for a moment.

Tudor spoke in a low voice.

“That night. You saved me when I nearly lost my life within the family, and you risked your own.”

“....”

“Now it's my turn. I can't walk anymore anyway. Let me do something for you one last time.”

Tudor's eyes, dying of blood loss and hypothermia, sparked.

It was the last spark of light that only a being who sensed the end of his life could give off.

...But.

“If you have the stamina for bullshit, walk.”

Bianca's glare was even more overwhelming than Tudor's.

“That night. I may have saved you, but you saved me.”

“....”

“Do you have any idea how relieved and grateful I was to see you still alive at the end of where I ran with my lungs bursting... Do you know how relieved and grateful I was at that time?”

Bianca curled her arms around Tudor's shoulders and pulled him close.

Then she growled.

“So live, somehow. As long as I live, you live. When I'm dead, it's up to you whether to search or not.”

“....”

Tudor was speechless at Bianca's non-threatening threat.

Soon, they were climbing the mountain path again.

Tudor's mana was long gone, and his body was riddled with cuts, large and small, from the mansion's traps.

His drenched body was constantly losing heat.

Pudeudeug-

Behind him, he heard the sound of another bird flapping its wings.

It was only a few feet away now.

“...Bianca.”

Tudor, barely walking with the aid of his spear, spoke in a fading voice.

Bianca looked up.

“Thank you.”

“...What an ominous way to start a greeting under the circumstances.”

“Just. I figured it was now or never.”

“Oh, really!”

At that moment, Bianca turns her head.

Thud!

Tudor fell to the ground.

“....”

Bianca stared at Tudor in disbelief.

And she cowered down next to him, too.

“...Yes. Well done, that was good enough.”

There was no response from the fallen Tudor.

Then, as Bianca looked at him, tears began to form in her eyes.

Bianca's once proud and confident expression quickly falls away, and she looks like a woman her own age.

She hugged Tudor tightly as his breathing slowed and bowed her head.

In the end, they didn't make it over the promised ridge, but they did manage to lure the demon away and set off the black firecrackers.

It was a situation where she was prepared as it was not a plan made with the survival probability of the two used as bait in mind in the first place.

“Thank you. For coming with me.”

She pressed her lips to Tudor's mouth.

Pudeudeug-

And a mysterious sound gets closer and closer.

Bianca lifted her head, a look of determination on her face.

She had no strength left, but she would resist with every last ounce of energy she had.

“I will die rather than have my body taken by you!”

She raised her bow as she stood before Tudor.

Across the inky darkness, she could see two red, blazing eyeballs.

Sprinkling an eerie red light, it was like seeing the dog of death from a grotesque legend come to life.

...But.

Flutter-.

What appeared in front of Bianca was not a demon, but something else entirely.

“You still look lively, which is good.”

Vikir. The Night Hound stepped out of the shadows.

Bianca's eyes widened.

“Vikir? How are you here? Isn't the meeting place over the ridge?”

“I picked you up. Well, I took some risks.”

With that, Vikir raised his hand.

A werewolf, a ghoul, a giant carapace centipede, a mountain turtle, a griffin, ... and several other creatures had their throats slit and were dripping blood.

Bianca suddenly realized that she and Tudor had made it this far without being attacked by any of the creatures.

That was because Vikir had been silently clearing the escape route all this time.

When they'd first made their plan, he'd been the one to abandon them, but he'd actually cared for them more than anyone else.

“...Vikir.”

Bianca's voice trembled, but Vikir waved her off as if it were no big deal.

Meanwhile.

Vikir turned his head and watched the trajectory of the black firecrackers as they rose above the Usher mansion.

Those firecrackers could only mean one thing.

Roderick Usher was dead, or at least as dead as he could be.

Bianca explained.

“My father is alive. But because of the red death poison that has taken over the grounds of the mansion....”

“I see the situation. Save your strength for the rest of the story.”

With that, Vikir walked over to the fallen Tudor.

After checking his pulse, Vikir nodded.

“He'll be fine. With some potions and a holy power poultice, he should be up and about in no time.”

“Well, do you think we can do that? We have to go over the ridge....”

“Yes, if you stay still.”

“Huh? What's that...?”

Bianca didn't even have time to ask.

Hwag!

Vikir scooped Tudor up on the spot. With Bianca on his side, he started running up the hill.

“What?”

Bianca panicked, but then squeezed her eyes shut.

Vikir's strength and speed were immense, and even with Tudor and Bianca on his back, he could climb the steep rock face in the blink of an eye.

It was like a bird gliding.

'...Thank God.'

Vikir was also relieved by the current situation.

In the original story, this was the place where Tudor died, and where Bianca's mind went crazy.

Usher's restoration operation.

It was supposed to happen much later than it did, but it was the right place.

Prior to the restoration of Usher, Tudor is gravely wounded while attempting to stop Bianca from being brainwashed by a demon, and as a result, he is unable to penetrate the Daylily of the Demon Legion and dies a long, hard death after leading his allies to safety.

Bianca is driven to madness by the guilt of having failed to restore her family name and of having harmed Tudor, her lifelong childhood friend and lover who had been there for her in her darkest time.

...But fate has changed.

Tudor survives, and Bianca's sanity is restored.

This was only possible because, at a crucial moment, Bianca refused to be brainwashed by Madeline.

“ ...I guess we have to thank Lovegood.”

Vikir stared at the brooch in Bianca's hair.

A hairpin with a pink heart-shaped brooch attached to it.

It's called a “love shield.”

It was an artifact that Vikir had gotten back in the day when he participated in the University League.

To be more precise, Vikir had gotten Decarabia as a reward for his excellent performance in the University League.

At the time, there was a student named Merelini Lovegood who had better grades than Vikir, and the prize she received was this artifact called 'Love Shield'.

'The artifact I won is called the Love Shield. It's a hairpin with a heart-shaped brooch, and it's supposed to protect against any kind of powerful brainwashing or mind control magic once you wear it, but only if you have someone you truly love by your side!'

The effect of this artifact, called the Love Shield, is a one-time defense against all powerful brainwashing.

However, the artifact requires the presence of someone you truly love for it to work.

<Dear Vikir>.

<With love?>

<-PS. Merelini Lovegood, President of Vi*Sa*Mo->

-'Perfume, skin lotion, shoes, belts, hats, sunglasses, shirts, bags, fountain pens, ties, wallets, sneakers, hairpins... Oh my. There is also an artifact that was used as a prize in the university league. Also, what is this? It's the key to the carriage?'

In the past, Lovegood had mailed the artifact to Vikir as a gesture of fandom, and Vikir had kept it and handed it to Bianca before infiltrating the Usher mansion.

'Take these with you.'

Bianca with a hairpin, Tudor with red and black firecrackers.

Vikir's preparation, just in case, saved Tudor and Bianca from a harsh fate.

“ ...It's the first time I've seen a face..”

Vikir, who was looking at his own face in a puddle on the ground, turned his head.

Kkoog-

He saw Tudor fainting and Bianca's hands clasped together as she looked at Tudor.

◆

Then.

Vikir found a temporary camp on the ridge, and in a pit covered with fallen leaves, he took out the potion he had placed beforehand and fed it to Tudor.

“...Huagh? Why am I still alive?”

Bianca cried out as Tudor woke up with a loud scream.

Just then.

Pudeudeug-

The sound of a bird flapping its wings came from far behind them.

Up on the ridge, Vikir stood in full view of Usher's mansion.

Just as expected.

[...Find them! ...Must find them!]

He could hear Madeline's poisoned voice and the sounds of Usher's knights moving about.

Tudor and Bianca's eyes widened.

“Get ready.”

Vikir spoke.

“It's time to pay them back.”

Chapter 446

The Fall of Usher (8)

◆

A demon with the form of a giant bird spread its four wings.

Its body was covered in snow, ice, and frost, like a suit of armor.

Within a single large orbital socket, its eyes were filled with glistening eyeballs, each emitting a strange light, and its long, sharp beak was filled with teeth.

Andrealphus, the Ice Duke.

The mastermind of the Age of Destruction, the spearhead of the demonic army that caused so much damage to the Human Alliance, has finally revealed its true colors.

[Handmade, though quite clever...]

Andrealphus flapped its massive wings and soared into the air in the blink of an eye.

The long tail feathers of ice and frost traced white trails in the air.

[It is of no use to me].

Andrealphus was right.

Water is no match for a flying bird.

Perhaps if there had been more water, but the severe drought had lowered the level of Lakedog so much that it was impossible to finish off Madeline.

[What can you people who live off the land do? Hohohoho-]

Andrealphus ascended to the heavens and laughed at all things below.

Hand attacks, formations, and sieges are all meaningless before the power of Andrealphus, who dominates the sky.

The daylilies stretched out their vines but could not reach it, and Marquis de Sade's improved Eightfold Formation had lost its effectiveness.

“Formation with bird flying. Eih-”

“I don't know if I can reach it.”

Marquis de Sade and Major General Orca stepped forward.

Kwakwakwakwakwang!

Whips and clubs stretched out with terrifying force, creating a storm of auras.

[It's absurd. Hohohoho-]

Andrealphus dodged the combined attacks of Sade and Orca with too much ease.

A flying demon, flying freely through the skies.

It could ascend to impossibly high heights and descend to the ground in the blink of an eye, so attacks from the ground were largely pointless against Andrealphus.

“Miss!”

“Are you all right!”

“What the hell is going on....”

Several of the de-brainwashed Knights of the God Killer Sniper Squad gathered around Bianca.

Bianca quickly took control of the situation.

“God Killer Sniper Squad, quickly pull yourself together and catch that monster first!”

With that, Bianca raised her bow and arrow and pointed it at Andrealphus.

The knights of the God Killer Sniper Squad also looked nervous as they prepared to shoot.

However, even though each and every one of them was a sharpshooter, it was difficult for them to hit Andrealphus, who was moving at a tremendous speed in the sky.

[Hohohoho- When I make my move, no one can catch me...!?]

But Andrealphus's self-congratulation was short-lived.

Pis-

Vikir leaped up, stepping on a dead tree that had fallen at an angle to the cliffside.

Vikir leaped a ridiculous height.

His leap seemed to defy gravity!

'All those years in the Academy's gravity chamber have been worth it.'

In the blink of an eye, Vikir landed at Andrealphus's feet and unleashed the 8th Form of Baskerville.

...Flash!

The dark solar storm raged furiously.

Ppajijijijig!

Startled, Andrealphus quickly halted its flight, spun, and fled in a near-vertical orbit.

Vikir had to be content with tearing off one of the demon's wings and one of its legs.

[Keuaaaghhhhh! How dare you little creature.]

Andrealphus's eyeballs turned an even deeper shade of red.

Eventually, the Demon King began to exercise the power granted to him without hesitation.

Jjeojeojeojeog!

A black circle of magic drew around Andrealphus.

Soon, the portal was torn apart and huge chunks of ice began to appear.

Hail. But they were far too large to be hail.

Huge chunks of ice, almost drift ice.

Ice slabs and ice boulders over 10 meters in diameter began to fall like raindrops.

Kwakwakwakwakwakwakwang!

The ground was devastated in an instant.

The people below didn't even dare to attack Andrealphus.

Jjeoeog-

Vikir quickly raised his head after cutting down a huge hailstone that was falling towards him.

Andrealphus was sneering from the corner of his mouth, as if he would never return to the ground.

[From now on, I'll never give you a break! Die in a hailstorm! Hohohohoho-]

Andrealphus summoned the hailstones as if on cue.

A steady stream of ice blocks rained down.

Camus, who was crushing the hailstones with her scorching hot iron skewers, spoke up in annoyance.

“This is a pain in the ass. We're just going to have to take a one-sided beating, and that guy can just fly away when it runs out of energy.”

“I agree.”

Dolores nodded, agreeing with Camus.

She was frustrated that her holy shield was ineffective against physical impacts like hail.

Sinclaire, too, was growing weary as she drew gold from the veins beneath the ground to create the shield.

“Brother, I don't think we'll last long at this rate, not even five minutes.”

Sinclaire was right.

As the hail continued to fall, the Night Walkers became increasingly exhausted.

In this situation, Andrealphus drove a wedge.

[...At this point, will we even open the gates of destruction?]

At that, everyone's faces turned puzzled.

Andrealphus chuckled.

[If I unleash the remaining power, I can open the Gates of Destruction, albeit imperfectly, but at the cost of my life].

“....”

Vikir looks up at the sky without speaking.

Seeing Vikir's gaze, Andrealphus spoke in a mocking tone.

[Perhaps you are the only one of these humans who understands my words. I don't know how a mere mortal could know about the Gates of Destruction, but... don't worry too much. I have no intention of opening it just yet.]

After finishing speaking, Andrealphus opened his mouth wide.

[With such an advantage, who am I to force myself to open the gate? Hohohohoho!]

The hailstones began to fall again.

[Once all of you are gone, I'll work with my two remaining companions to open the gate safely, aAnd in the end, the whole world will be covered with demons(Majins)! How easy is this in a world overflowing with scum who want power!]

Andrealphus spread its remaining wings wide.

And in the midst of the hailstorm that threatened to engulf the world, Andrealphus scorned and mocked them until the very end.

[Die, you scum! Everything you have done is worthless and in vain! I myself will make it so...!]

Just then.

“Are you that confident?”

Vikir's mouth opened.

He was staring at Andrealphus with a straight, unwavering gaze, even under such adverse circumstances.

Andrealphus looked down at Vikir with the gaze of a cat looking at a caught mouse.

[What the hell are you talking about?]

“Are you really that confident? I've been taught that behind overconfidence lies anxiety.”

[Hohohohoho- Anxiety? This body?]

Andrealphus laughed in disbelief.

[You are crawling on the ground like worms, and I am raining hail from so high in the sky. I may have lost a wing and a leg through the carelessness, but that's nothing compared to eating hundreds of human children].

“Yes, but there is still a glimmer of insecurity in you. If you are really so full of yourself, prove it.”

[Where does a worm dare such a petty provocation...]

As Andrealphus turned away as if not worth listening to, Vikir shouted.

“'Where is the person who can kill me?'.”

[...!]

The words that came out of Vikir's mouth were Andrealphus's line to Bianca.

“Where is the person who can kill me?'. If you can say it three times, I will recognize your courage. I'll even open the doors of my mansion for you. You won't be afraid, will you?”

Vikir turned to face Andrealphus, who was glaring at him, and continued.

“If you can say these words three times, I will recognize your confidence. I will accept defeat and death as sweet. You won't be afraid, will you?”

[Heh! What else can you do if I won't accept it? ... But hey, it's fun, and if your goal was to keep me interested and kill time, you've succeeded].

Andrealphus looked back at Bianca with a wicked grin.

But Andrealphus and Bianca are not the same. Their powers and circumstances are so different that they dare not even compare.

And so Andrealphus was able to cry out one last time.

[Where is the person who can kill me? Where is the person who can kill me? Where is the person who can kill me?]

The arrogance and confidence of one who stands in absolute dominance.

Andrealphus shouted proudly, standing firmly in the center of the sky.

At that very moment.

[...?]

As the last word was uttered, Andrealphus experienced a strange phenomenon.

A flicker.

The vision in his left eye flashed black.

Countless pupils had lost their function.

Andrealphus scratched his head, wondering what it was.

...Ppeoeong!

Andrealphus's head snapped forward with a loud explosion.

Hududug- hududug- hududug- hududug-

The face was shattered, the eyes popped out, and the left side of the skull was completely torn off.

A sniper shot of terrifyingly destructive power swoops in and blasts it in the back of the head.

[Kkyaaaaaagh! W-what is this!?]

Andrealphus screamed in horror, while Vikir's mouth opened.

“My handiwork was not necessarily to catch you.”

He was right.

A surge of water flooded the swamp, sweeping away all the mist and red death that had been rising around Usher's mansion.

And then.

On the roof of the crumbling mansion, at the tip of the spire, stood a lone figure.

A thin figure, complexion as pale as a corpse.

But his sunken eyes still glowed with the same fire as before.

Roderick. Usher Poe Roderick.

Usher's original master, the Archon, holds up his bow and arrow, pointing it at the sky.

Chapter 447

The Fall of Ushers (9)

◆

...Kwakwang!

Andrealphus felt an intense impact from the back of her head, and then her vision on the left side went blank.

[What the hell!?]

Andrealphus turned her head in surprise.

She saw the half-crumbling mansion of the Usher family, and a man standing atop the spiked roof.

A tall, lanky man, pale as a corpse, with large, sullen eyes, bloodlessly thin lips, and hair as long and thin as a spider's web.

Usher Poe Roderick. A man who is called a Bow Demon (弓鬼).

He raised his dying body that crushed by the Red Death, and picked up his bow and arrows.

And now he is staring at the sky with his usual gaze.

[Roderick? How can you come to your senses...? Argh!]

Andrealphus's face crumpled into a grimace.

The raging waters of the Lakedog had temporarily washed away the red death aura from the swampy grounds of the House of Usher's mansion.

Kwakwakwakwakwa...

The Red Death spirits are swept away by the blue foam and dissolve.

The aura of death and sickness that enveloped the mansion has temporarily dissipated, and clear air flows in.

Kkililig-

Roderick draws his bowstring once more.

His gaze, cold and dry, is focused on one thing and one thing only: Andrealphus in the sky.

“Madeline.”

The voice came from a shattered gut and a crumbling body.

At the same time, Roderick's arrow once again struck Andrealphus in the chest.

...Peopeong!

It pierced through and tore a huge hole in Andrealphus' body.

Andrealphus let out a horrified scream as flesh and blood scattered in all directions.

[Kyaaah! Brother! What is this! How could you do this to me!]

It was a demon's habit to take on the voice of its host when cornered.

But it only made the blood in Roderick's eyes grow redder and sharper.

“Madeline!”

Roderick pulled the bowstring once more.

Ppeo-eong!

Once again, Andrealphus's head exploded.

Her right side of her face was completely blown off, and now only her lower jaw and tongue remained.

[Brother! It's me! It's Madeline, the one you buried alive when you were a child! Are you going to kill me again?]

The monster, with only its lower jaw and tongue left, continues to spew Madeline's voice down its throat.

The sister who was blinded by a childhood fever.

She was buried by Roderick in an unknown grave.

But one rainy night, she dug up her grave and climbed out.

She was thought to be dead, but she was alive.

She overcame the horror of being buried alive and escaped the grave on her own.

She regained her health and grew up strong.

...But in fact, she died of a fever at that time.

It was that horrible, ugly, ugly demon that had taken over her empty shell.

Roderick's eyes burned with gray fire as he recognized it.

“Andrealphus!”

The name Madeline was no longer on Roderick's lips.

Now that he has finally let go of his sister, a sister he should have let go long ago, he will repay the debt of deception with interest.

Kkudeudeudeudeug-

Roderick. He squeezed the body that had been consumed by the Red Death to its limit.

Blood pulses through his dried, corpse-like body.

Bones crackled everywhere.

Bianca looks at Roderick and cries out.

“Dad, don't overexert yourself, you're not in good shape...!?”

For a moment, she saw her father's gaze upon her.

It's the eyes of a man who is ready to die. The eyes of a man who is ready to die, but at the same time, willing to give his all.

Bianca and Roderick. An unspoken message passed between them.

“...Dad.”

Bianca staggered as if her legs had given out.

Tudor, who was beside her, helped her up.

“Roderick, why?”

“...Dad.”

Bianca responded to Tudor's question with a despairing stare.

“He plans to end his life here.”

“...!”

The words startled everyone, and they turned their heads once more.

There stood Roderick the Bow Demon, preparing for the final blow.

Patsutsutsutsu-

The aura gathers around the tip of Roderick's arrow.

A fatal blow.

Roderick's entire body's mana surges.

And then.

...Kwakwang!

An unbelievably loud explosion erupted from the arrow.

A huge vortex formed, and countless lightning bolts filled it.

The wind swept away all the clouds in the sky, and the arrows flying through the center of it created a pillar of light that looked like a comet falling.

A strike from the heavens.

It was even more powerful than when Hugo had slain Andromalius.

Roderick's arrow flew toward Andrealphus with a terrifying aftermath.

And then.

Kwa-jig! Kkwaleuleung!

The arrow blew out not only the heart of the giant monster bird, but also its entire chest.

[Keuaaaaghhhh!]

Despite being hit by this terrifying sniper attack, Andrealphus didn't die immediately.

However, the unexpectedly fatal wound was enough to destabilize its trajectory and lower its altitude.

And where Andrealphus was gradually falling, Marquis de Sade and Major General Orca were waiting.

“Pushishishi- that Usher boy has given us a good gift.”

“This is repayment for the hail that fell earlier.”

The two old men, who had just been mocked by the hailstorm, were furious.

The whips writhing like vipers, the clubs crashing like a tsunami.

The aura of the two of them, who were so young in their horrific lives, flew through the sky.

Peo-eog! Kwakwakwakwang!

The whip and club tore off one of Andrealphus's wings.

Then the rest of his wings began to receive a baptism of arrows from the God Killer Sniper Squad.

Peopeopeopeopeopeog!

Andrealphus, whose body was riddled with arrows and turned into a hedgehog, shook her blown-off head and screamed.

[Kyaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!]

It was a terrible final cry, so terrible that it was hard to tell whether it was human or bird.

Kkililig-

The last bowstring is pulled.

“....”

Bianca took the final shot.

...Peoeong!

The final arrow flies, surely breaking Andrealphus's last hold.

Peopeong!

Bianca's arrow blew off Andrealphus's last tattered wing.

A falling demon has no wings.

Andrealphus didn't even seem to have the strength left to scream, let alone flee through the air.

The monstrous bird's body, falling toward the ground, pointed toward the Usher mansion.

And beneath it stood Roderick.

Roderick asked, looking at Andrealphus falling toward him.

“...Cervantes. What happened to him?”

It wasn't Bianca who answered his question, but Tudor next to her.

Tudor closed his eyes and shook his head.

Roderick nodded, noticing the spear Gungnir in his right hand and the empty left sleeve blowing in the wind.

“ ...So that what happened.”

Tudor's appearance and demeanor spoke for themselves.

Roderick closed his eyes as he realized everything that had happened.

Then he spoke in a dry voice.

“Please take care of the Usher family.”

It was the last thing he said.

...Kwakwakwakwakwang!

The half-destroyed body of Andrealphus crashed down on top of Usher's mansion.

The mansion and island, whose erosion had been halted for a moment, began to crumble once more as Andrealphus fell.

Rumbling.

With a thunderous crash, the Usher family mansion began to sink into the swamp along with its grounds.

[Ah... Aaaaaahh... The casuality... The casuality...]

A dying flame of a demon. The 3rd Corpse collapsing into the water.

The last days of Andrealphus the Ice Duke were miserable and lonely.

◆

Then the hail, storm, and thunder subsided.

In the middle of the quiet swamp, only wide ripples and foam remained.

The Fall of Usher.

Bianca's eyes welled with tears as she watched the mansion disappear beneath the bottomless swamp.

Turning to the Tudor on her shoulder, Bianca said.

“...Demons. I'm going to kill them all.”

“I agree.”

Tudor replied, looking down at his father's relic, the Gungnir.

The two young heroes sharpened their hatred of demons.

Then.

Jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog-

The sound of footsteps approaching their backs.

Vikir. The Night Hound.

A hunter who has been fighting demons in secret and alone since before the world changed.

Tudor and Bianca turn their heads to look at Vikir.

Gazes of unwavering faith and trust.

And then the old, seasoned hunter turned to the new, newly awakened hunters.

“There are only two left.”

With most of the Ten Demons responsible for the Age of Destruction hunted down, there were only two left.

The 1st Corpses, And 2nd Corpses. If they catch just these two, they will be able to prevent the Age of Destruction.

It won't be easy-perhaps harder than everything they've done so far combined-but it must be done.

And Vikir was no longer alone.

The Night Hound is followed by the Night Walkers.

Camus, Dolores, Sinclaire, Tudor, Bianca, Sancho, Pigi, and other colleagues from the Academy, as well as Marquis de Sade and Major General Orca from Nouvelle Vague.

In addition, a large force of personnel from Fort Tochka were supporting Vikir in every way possible.

“This is the final phase.”

The demons who had lost this many of their comrades would not stand idly by.

There is a high possibility that they will mobilize all the time and strength they have accumulated so far.

The Night Hound turned his back on Usher.

So did his followers.

The end is near. The prelude to all-out war was upon them.

Chapter 448

Declaration of War (1)

◆

A dark underground space.

It is extremely quiet, except for the occasional sound of water drops falling from the ceiling hitting the stone floor and breaking.

Then. The sound of loud footsteps shattered the silence.

“Heoeog! Heog! Keoheog!”

A young man was running down the hallway, his face distorted.

He was naked, his skinny limbs dotted with large handcuffs and shackles.

Süskind de Leviathan. The eldest son of the extremely poisonous Leviathan family.

He hid himself close to the bottom corner of the basement stairs.

Soon, several soldiers with spears were seen patrolling the stairs.

“...This is how it happened.”

Süskind cursed himself as he clutched his head.

A young master of House Leviathan, he had been taken captive one day without warning and imprisoned in the family's underground facility.

As the next Householder to lead the House of Extreme Poison, Süskind was well aware of the facility.

It was a prison for imprisoning the most dangerous elements to be excluded from the family, political opponents, and those who could not be controlled among those who inherited the blood of Leviathan, and at the same time, it was also a laboratory where all kinds of terrible human experiments were conducted.

“Thomas, I was trying to connect the dots between his involvement in the demonization case and Principal Winston's outbursts at the Academy. .... There's definitely a connection to our family.”

Principal Winston's outburst, the growth of a demonic plant called the Hell Tree at Colosseo Academy, and the demonization of Thomas, who attended the Night Hound's convoy.

And as this series of events was swept under the rug by the First Prince, Süskind continued to point out the absurdity of the situation.

Common sense dictated that Leviathan should not have sided with the First Prince at this time.

...But common sense came at a heavy price.

Forced out of bed before he could even open his eyes, Süskind was thrown into the dungeons here. It was here that he met many members of the family.

All of them opposed the civil war.

It was only then that he realized exactly what was going on.

Something unknown and terrifying had consumed Leviathan, and there was no going back.

...Tatag!

Süskind sprinted through the darkness, taking advantage of the disappearance of the patrolling guards.

It was his strong mind and body that had allowed him to survive all the cruel experiments in the prison.

Although Süskind was an arrogant person steeped in the sense of being the chosen one and privileged, he was still an elite who did not neglect discipline.

Running up the underground stairs, he came upon a secret door hidden in a secret place.

The only people who know of this place are the Patriarch and the youg master.

Süskind pushed the door open with a glimmer of hope.

Drrrr-!

The heavy bricks shifted, opening a passage to the depths below.

Sensing a sentry approaching from behind, Süskind quickly slammed the door shut and descended into the darkness.

'There's no way out of here, but... at least there's room to rest for a while. I'll heal here, repair the damage done to my body by the experiments, and then break out.'

Süskind descended the secret staircase, thinking this and that.

But soon he came upon a horrifying sight.

A dark underground alcove.

The floor was littered with countless jars.

And they emanated an unpleasant aura that gave him goosebumps just looking at them.

The jars emitted an aura of dancing red evil spirits.

Süskind recognized it immediately.

“...Red Death!”

How could he not?

It was a terrible plague that, until a few years ago, the entire family had been obsessed with developing.

At first, it simply caused a fever and was contagious, but later it caused people to go berserk and even attack others indiscriminately.

“Unbelievable! Wasn't the Red Death abolished due to the incident caused by that bastard?”

Süskind looked at the jars in disbelief.

Each of the large jars held a person.

It was an eerie sight to see a man and a woman drenched in the red drug, their bodies curled up like fetuses, staring up from the jars, their eyes narrowed.

Every single one of them had the same look in their eyes.

'Porridge... here... give me...'

The maid who cleaned their rooms every day, the old man who tended the garden, the chef who made their desserts so delicious, the butler who was always so strict and stern, the instructor who taught them martial arts when they were young, the younger siblings of their relatives from the other families who they only saw on holidays, the distant elders of their extended families who they often greeted...

These are all familiar faces in the jar.

Süskind stepped between the jars on shaky legs.

Soon he came to the innermost jar, a huge one.

Hiss- hiss-

Two breathing sounds can be heard from inside the jar, which is half buried in the ground.

In the jar that Süskind looked down at, there were two large snakes tangled together.

Each breath they exhale sends a cloud of dancing red evil spirits into the air.

“...Are these the sources of the Red Death?”

Süskind broke out in a cold sweat.

At that time.

Hissing-

The two snakes looked up at him and began to breathe heavily.

Süskind was about to jump back in surprise.

[When is that a good smell?]

A sullen voice said from behind him.

He turned, startled, and saw a man in black robes standing there.

Süskind recognized him immediately.

“...Ah, Father.”

Hobbes de Leviathan. The patriarch of an extremely poisonous family.

He looked at his eldest son and smiled coyly.

[I'm not your father, Süskind, I'm just the demon who ate your father and took his shell].

Süskind's complexion paled at the unusually honest answer.

He'd had some idea, but he'd never expected him to reveal his identity so openly.

Süskind clenched his teeth and asked.

“What did you do with the youngest?”

[He had already become like Thomas, the second son.]

“Stop talking nonsense! There's nothing we can do about Thomas because he has a terrible personality, but not the youngest! He's too good-natured and innocent to be our brother, so he'll never become a demon...!?”

But Süskind didn't get to finish his sentence.

Chwaag!

Two snakes jumped out of the jar behind him, grabbed him by the neck and waist, and pulled him into the jar.

Süskind couldn't even scream as he was pulled under the jar.

[Ah, ah- I had kept him alive because he was the body I was going to change into.]

Hobbes, noticing that the body of Süskind in the jar was bent in a strange way, lamented.

[It's a shame to turn him into a poisonous person(毒人), but I can't help it, I've still got one more body to change into...]

The red evil spirits that had been floating around in the jar began to dance and crawl into Süskind's body.

His eyes, which had gone in different directions, began to glow red, and red spots began to form all over his body.

Just then.

[How's it going, this time?]

Another voice came from the top of the basement stairs.

A man covered from head to toe in black robes looked down at Hobbes.

Hobbes smiled and replied.

[It's First Corpses. What can I do for you?]

[I'm here to discuss the civil war, and it's time to discuss the succession to the throne].

[There are still many eyes watching. If you have anything to discuss, send an owl.]

[It's okay sometimes. I don't know how long it's been since I've had a conversation like this face to face with colleagues.]

[Even now, only you and I are left.]

[Yeah, because of the damn demon hunter].

Hobbes, or rather, Second Corpses and First Corpses, whose faces were covered with black robes, began to talk about various things.

[It seems that Third Corpses has been defeated, and there is a faint trace of her attempt to force open the Gate of Destruction in her magic path before her life was cut short].

[Hehehe- If I'm going to die, I'll open it and die. She seems like a pathetic wretch].

[It's not something to laugh at. No matter how alone we are without a sense of camaraderie, this is a big problem.]

[Haha. The purpose of opening the gate is the same].

[Yes. All our colleagues of them, are dead, and now it's just you and me. Now is the time to make a deal.]

Hobbes nodded.

[If it's a civil war, don't worry, I'm about to finish making a large batch of poison, and once these guys are done, the war will be a piece of cake].

[He was the first poisonous person, wasn't he?]

[He was a failure. He succeeded in strengthening the flesh and making the personality berserk, but he lacked the all-important contagion. The ones aging in the jar now are an improved version. These are the real thing].

Hobbes turned away as he finished speaking.

He turned in the direction of the two snakes that had poisoned Süskind earlier.

[The essence of my magical power is embodied in the form of a demonic beast. The Ouroboros, a venomous fountain, an artifact that allows them to bite each other's tails and create an endless supply of venom. As long as we have this, we can create as many poisonous person as we want].

[That's great. It'll help us in the war.]

[Of course. A madman, plague-spreading raiding party of maniacs. It has tremendous tactical value].

Then the man who had been listening to Hobbes up until this point opened his mouth to ask.

[Then why don't we try and wipe out the 'Night Walkers' who will be in Tochka Fortress by now as a test?]

[Huh? What are they?]

[The demon hunter who recently killed 4th and 3rd in quick succession is said to be nesting there, and for some reason a lot of refugees are heading there].

[Hmm... It's a high, rugged place, but it doesn't have drinking water, so it wouldn't be a good place to shelter, let alone take in refugees.]

[But that's what they're doing. They're buying up large quantities of food and drinking water and seem to be preparing for a sit-in].

[Hahahaha! Foolish! There's no water source there, and if I let the Poisonous Person loose, they'll just barricade themselves in and die of starvation].

Hobbes bared his teeth and laughed.

He waved a hand in the air, and an army of Poisonous Person with red spots all over their backs and bodies stood in formation.

[The others have fallen victim to the Demon Hunters while standing idly by, but not me. If we know where they are, shouldn't we be the first ones in?]

[Be careful, there are many refugees there, and the Demon Hunter is a heartless man, he may use them as shields].

[The human shield strategy doesn't work for me. The more filthy humans we have, the better. Infect them all, turn them into poisonous person, and that's it.]

The black-robed man laughed with satisfaction.

[Indeed, for a Demon Hunter with so much to protect, a type like you would be like a natural enemy.]

[No problem.]

Hobbes grinned wryly and continued.

[I'll conscript all the Poisonous Person, and we'll set out a month from now at this hour. I'll go and cut the throat of the Night Hound or something. ...No, wouldn't it be better to just make him as a Poisonous Person, all of them, Even all of his limbs.]

[I trust you. By the way, can you do me a favor?]

[A favor? You to me? What?]

[... To kill a man].

The man puts a piece of paper with a face on it down in front of Hobbes.

[If he were alive, he would look like this right now].

[...? What's this? He looks like a worthless bastard.]

[I think so too. I'm asking just in case.]

Hobbes shakes his head, but he can't help but nod.

First Corpses (一番尸). Aka, the Marquis of Discord.

It was the first time in his life that the high and arrogant being in front of him had ever asked for such a lowly favor.

Chapter 449

Declaration of War (2)

◆

Watch Champions League For Free

Poker, Roulette, Blackjack&More!

Episode 451 Declaration of War (2)

A stack of papers lay on the desk.

They were all different reports, but they all had the same word at the end.

Defeat. Defeat. Defeat. Defeat. Defeat.

And then the one looking down at them spoke in a heavy voice.

“...The Western Front has collapsed.”

Raspane Morgue.

The mood in the room sank to a somber hush as the Matriarch of the House of Morgue spoke.

The top item on the agenda of the Alliance of Houses meeting, held by the heads of Ironblood Swordsman Baskerville, Mage Clan Morgue, Faithful Quovadis, and Tycoon Bourgeois.

It was the current state of the civil war.

Poisonous Dark Master (劇毒暗家) House Leviathan.

A family that has been recognized as a master poison manufacturer since the Warring States Period before the Unified Empire.

Having recently absorbed the powers of Donquixote the Spearman and Usher the God Killer, Leviathan was growing in strength at an alarming rate.

Raspane frowned.

“The 'poisonous people' created by the Leviathan family were more difficult to deal with than I thought. It is an army made up of madmen who have lost their sense of reason, and they even spread infectious diseases to the surrounding area...”

“'Red Death'. If you are infected with it, it saps all the energy from your body, killing you, and when you die, you turn into a puppet. Or should I say, a living corpse... It's hard to describe.”

Cardinal Martin Luther of the Quovadis was equally puzzled.

At least Morgue and Quovadis were dealing with magic and holy power, so the damage was relatively minor.

The knights of House Baskerville, on the other hand, who fight with hand-to-hand combat, suffered considerable damage from the poisonous attack.

If Osiris, the young patriarch, and the Seven Counts had not done well in local wars in each region, a significant portion of the territory would have been lost.

All eyes then turned to Damian, the representative of the Bourgeois family.

“Wasn't the Bourgeois family an ally of the Leviathan family in the past?”

“Hmm. I don't know about that, as it was the work of the previous head of the family.”

“And you are not one now, Damian?”

“Technically, I am the acting head of the family. The current Bourgeois family's head is elsewhere....”

“But you said that you have acquired quite a few of the remaining secret documents, and I don't mean to criticize you, so please share them with us.”

At Cardinal Martin Luther's polite request, Damian opened his mouth.

“Many of the documents were lost, so I don't know the details. All I know is that when the Red Death was first created, it was sprayed as a test on the natives of Jungle, and when the natives fought it off surprisingly well, the Leviathan, alarmed, created an even more contagious and effective variant. The result is the Poisonous Man, who are now defeating our armies day after day.”

The creatures created by Leviathan are as strong and fierce as demons, but they have no mind and are entirely under the control of their masters.

They also emit a red mist that drains mana and weakens the body at the mere touch, and if inhaled for long enough, can turn an otherwise healthy person into a monster.

The Leviathan family even absorbed all the remaining troops of the Usher family and the Donquixote family, which were allied families, and created Poisonous Man, so its power was growing day by day.

Adolf, the Magic Star of the Morgue, spoke up, his face grim.

“The Western Front has been completely overrun, and we've lost all the rubies we've mined. How hard it has been to dig up that ruby ??vein! Damn the Leviathan!”

“The world is getting worse and heresy and cults are running rampant, so we are in a lot of trouble.”

“Wildfires, droughts, starvation, demonic ravages, plagues, and cults and heresies... It's the end of the world.”

Martin Luther and Damian looked grim.

Then. A new person spoke up.

“ ...Didn't I say we should have prepared for that long ago?”

A sarcastic voice, a jab at the heads of Baskerville, Morgue, Quabadis, and Bourgeois.

Professor Banshee Morgue, no, Banshee the Principal of Colosseo Academy, crossed his arms in disbelief.

“Not only are the young bloods of the House dying, but innocent common citizens as well. People matter, not rubies like that.”

“What? When did I say people are less important? I'm just saying that I'm in charge of ruby mining right now!”

Adolf, a delegate to the Morgue Light Hall, and Banshee, a former member of the Morgue Dark Hall, do not get along.

Banshee snorted at Adolf and the others.

“This would not have happened if I had completely re-investigated the whole case when my pupil was wrongfully acquitted at trial. Leviathan wouldn't have been raised like this in the first place.”

Banshee. He was also one of the people who worked harder to save Vikir's life than anyone else when Vikir was imprisoned.

He glared at those who opposed Vikir's life-saving efforts at the time, or who were unsympathetic or lukewarm.

“Isn't this the result of being blinded by personal interests, turning a blind eye to important issues, keeping your mouths shut... and what were you all doing until the demons came out in such a big way?”

At Principal Banshee's words, many people shook their heads or averted their gaze.

Then, the representatives of the other academies smiled and tried to lighten the mood.

“Haha, this is not the place for blame, is it?”

“Principal Banshee, let's not vent your anger, we have more important things to do right now.”

“That's right, the immediate concern is how to stop the poisonous army that Leviathan has created.”

Basilios, the Warden of Varangian, Hippolyte, the headmaster of Themiscyra, and Blue Whale, the Master of the Magic Tower, looked at Banshee and fidgeted.

They are worried that their once united alliance will be divided again.

“....”

This was something that was on Banshee's mind as well, so he kept his mouth shut and just made a frowny face.

When Dyrachium, the Warden of the Verangian Boot Camp, died after failing to recover from the wounds he received during Sadi's attack, Basilios, the new Warden, comforted Banshee.

“But the situation got a lot better when our Confucianists got involved.”

“That's right, as the participation rate of student soldiers increased, the number of soldiers also increased.”

“At this rate, we may not be able to overwhelm the poisoners, but we can at least equalize the situation a bit.”

Banshee was still not pleased with what Hippolyte and Whitebeard were saying.

“I hope everyone can cover up the mistakes of adults through the students' sacrifice.”

“....”

“Furthermore. It is groundless optimism to say that the situation has become tense due to the intervention of the academies. If we look at it coldly, students are nothing more than newbies that professors need to protect. Just because student soldiers participate in the war will not significantly increase our military power. It just happens to be at the right time.”

No one responds to the rhetoric.

Principal Banshee continues, his eyes shining.

“The Leviathan Family are now bringing the Poisonous Army back home. The evidence is that many situations in which we were intentionally defeated and retreated in battles taking place in various places are being captured.”

“Why would they retreat when they have the advantage of having broken the Western Front?”

Raspane asked, and Banshee was silent for a moment.

“....”

Is it because of his connection with his hometown, Morgue, and because of his older brother, High Councilor Snake?

After a moment of silence, Banshee spoke, his tone slightly more polite than before.

“We are gathering our forces together, to make it look natural, to feign defeat.”

At those words, the faces of all the leaders turned grave.

Leviathan is secretly gathering their forces together.

No one was stupid enough to not understand the meaning of these words.

The Leviathan Family must be preparing for a large-scale local battle that could decide the outcome of the war.

Leviathan, Usher, and Donquixote combined.

If the legions of poisonous soldiers spread across the country were to advance in unison, their power would be immense.

It was likely to be the final battle that would decide the outcome of the war.

“ ...The problem is, we have no idea where, when, or how they plan to strike.”

Everyone nodded at Raspane's words.

Where, when, and how.

The most important of the three is the 'where'.

This is because defense forces must be stationed in advance in places where fierce battles are likely to occur.

The great minds of the day began to put their heads together.

Soon, various locations were being considered for raids.

“It could be the Red Awl Castle, with its massive veins of ruby. Ruby is the best transmitter of magic, so they'll be eager to secure it....”

“Maybe it's Dortsmile? Since this is where the core facilities of the Magic Train are located, if this place is destroyed, the distribution and supply routes of the allies will be cut off....”

“It could be St. Mecca, where the first Red Death was found in a well in the slums, so there could be something hidden in the area....”

Political reasons, strategic reasons, cultural reasons, and many other reasons are presented as evidence with detailed analysis.

A hundred schools of thought contend (百家爭鳴).

Everyone was talking about different regions.

All of them could be attacked by Leviathan, so it was hard to pinpoint one region.

...Just then.

“Tochka.”

One of the men spoke up.

A voice that offered no evidence, but sounded terribly confident.

Everyone in the room turned to look at the speaker.

“....”

A cold impression.

The energy radiating from his entire body is sharply forged like a sword.

The scent of blood was evident in his every move, and every time he moved his gaze, it felt like a sword was being drawn.

His identity is Hugo.

Hugo Le Baskerville, Patriarch of House Baskerville, the Iron Blooded Swordsman.

He looked down at the map and spoke.

“They will come to Tochka.”

The words were so full of certainty that everyone questioned them.

“Fortress] Tochka? Why is that remote plateau...?”

“Isn't it a place with good defense, but no water source for drinking water, so it has no tactical value?”

“Anyone with even a passing knowledge of military tactics would avoid places like this.”

“From the Leviathan's point of view, there's no reason to attack it.”

“Do you have any reason?”

Hugo's answer was simple and to the point.

“My son is there.”

Chapter 452

Infiltration of the water source (1)

◆

“We're running out of water.”

Hearing Cindywendy's words, the expressions of everyone in the conference room turned serious.

Tochka. A natural fortress. An impenetrable fortress where a single soldier could defend against a hundred enemies.

However, the fortress has a fatal flaw: there is no drinking water nearby.

Cindywendy continued.

“The number of refugees from all over the empire is staggering, and even if we had enough food, it would be hardly enough to distribute the water.”

“Can't we buy it even if we pay more?”

“There is still money left. Although I have used up almost all of my wealth, there is some assistance from the Bourgeois, but I have nothing for sale at the moment.”

Cindywendy shook her head at Camus's question.

Dolores spoke up, her tone worried.

“The Leviathan's poisonous people keep cutting the supply lines, so our water isn't getting here. At this rate, we'll be wiped out by starvation before the war even starts.”

Humans are 80 percent water.

The amount of water stored in the human body is approximately 50L.

Without doing anything, the body breaks down fat and produces about 0.25 liters of water.

This means that humans can only go for about three days without drinking water, after which dehydration becomes life-threatening as the stomach rebels.

“I wonder if all the people of the empire are here, so many of them.”

“It's all because we've been so good at spreading the Ark story. ...But have we taken it a little too far?”

Bianca and Tudor nodded in agreement.

'Fire and water will only avoid this place, and only here will true salvation be achieved.'

The land of salvation in the new revelation.

Dolores, the Night Saint, created a new oracle for the Church and spread it among the people.

The refugees who fled their homes to follow these words have gathered in vast numbers within the walls of Fortress Tochka.

Of course, those who ignored the oracle, those who did not believe, did not come.

The Night Walkers had made every effort to send them to the nearby highlands.

“We've managed to hold out so far, with help coming in from many directions, but we can't do it anymore....”

Even the great Cindywendy raised both hands and feet.

So far, many people besides the Night Walkers have been sending support without realizing it.

Bisamo, led by Lovegood of Themiscyra; alumni of Colosseo, such as Gordon and Underdog; the entire Colosseo staff, including Principal Banshee; the Ballak clan of the Western Jungle; Mozgus of Quovadis; Adolf of Morgue, Damian of the Bourgeois, Isabella of the Baskerville, and many other benefactors from all walks of life have sent food, water, troops, and other manpower, and the refugees of Tochka have been able to live a better life than before, despite their discomfort.

But now things were different.

As the civil war in the empire gradually intensified and the Leviathan family grew in power, there was a disruption in the supply of drinking water.

The vast Tochka Plateau is quickly becoming overwhelmed with refugees.

“There were fights between refugees over water rations again today. The vigilantes are keeping order, but I don't know how long that will last.”

Camus's voice was serious.

Dolores spoke with a serious expression on her face as well.

“Judging by the amount of water we have left, I'd say four days, if we conserve and save..., and then it's really over.”

After all, there's only four days of water.

If you consider how long humans can survive without water, that's about a week.

Everyone in Tochka has about a week to live.

In the end, everyone's eyes are directed to the highest table in the conference room.

Cindywendy, Camus, and Dolores, the top leaders of the Nightwalkers, also paid attention to a spot higher up than them.

Vikir.

There was a man who was always so expressionless that it was impossible to tell what he was thinking.

Finally, Vikir's mouth opened.

“Hold on.”

The words were met with different reactions.

Camus nodded in understanding, Dolores wondered how to convince the others, and Sinclaire scratched her head, trying to figure out how to hold on.

Cindywendy just sighs heavily with a 'here we go again' look on her face.

Just then, Pigi, next to her, asks in a cautious tone.

“Vikir. We all believe in you, but I'm sure many of the refugees here don't, and I don't know what to tell them. We can't just tell them to hang in there, can we?”

“But I can only tell them to hold on.”

Vikir opened his mouth.

His tone was flat, but still full of conviction.

“You've done a much better job than I expected, and we've been able to gather a lot of people, so I was wrong to be a bit off. But give it a little time and everything will work itself out. I can promise you that.”

“ ...You're just saying that because you don't think it's possible to wait that little bit longer?”

It was the Chihuahua who interrupted from the side.

He had become Vikir's loyal aide, and he was quick to criticize him.

“Isn't it frustrating for the people around you to keep the plan to yourself? Why don't you share it with the people around you? No, why don't you just wait and see when there's only four days' worth of water left?”

Chihuahua's bluntness caused a few people around him internally delighted.

But Vikir's attitude didn't change.

“I can't help it. If I blurt out my plans too soon, the enemy might get wind of it, and if I tell them, they won't believe me, and our allies might be rattled. I'm hoping they've gotten the hint and will trust me this time.”

“Well, you're still as stubborn as ever, even though you're a young man on the outside, you're like a middle-aged man on the inside, so what are you going to do about getting married later!”

Chihuahua's whining caused several of the women around him to flinch.

Vikir, meanwhile, was forced to give in to the Chihuahua's persistent nagging.

“...Is the drinking water situation so bad that we can't even last a week?”

“You've seen and heard, there's still more refugees coming in, and I was being optimistic about four days. In a week or so, this place, Tochka, will be overrun with people who have died of dehydration!”

Collecting dew or squeezing the juice from plants has its limits.

Something terrible could happen before Vikir's solution really came to light.

“It's true, that there's not much we can do but wait.”

A look of sadness appears on everyone's faces after hearing Vikir's words.

Just then.

MiniPin, in the corner of the room, cautiously raised his hand.

“Mr. Boss... No, Senator. I have something to tell you.”

Meeting Vikir's gaze, he pulled something out of his pocket and placed it on the desk.

It was a small cage, and inside was something with blue wings flapping about.

Sinclaire's eyes widened at Vikir's side.

“That's a nymph, isn't it?”

“That's right, we only just caught it yesterday.”

MiniPin nodded.

He was a former scout, and the Empire's foremost expert on the ecology of many monsters.

“Nymphs only live where there is water.”

Everyone's eyes lit up at MiniPin's words.

Even Vikir gestured for MiniPin to continue.

MiniPin spoke as best he could.

“I found this nymph on a mountain peak not far from Tochka. It's a high, steep, rocky place, and it's so thick with bushes that it's hard to see what's above when you're looking up from below. I thought I'd die several times trying to gather it.”

“Why do you think the nymphs live there?”

“Because there's water there, of course, isn't it?”

MiniPin said, almost convinced.

“I think there's a volcanic lake on that mountain peak, down in the crater.”

A water source. There might be a lake hidden on the other side of Tochka, on top of a jagged mountain peak.

“There's a 99.9% chance there's a lake there, and a nice, clear, freshwater lake at that.”

“...Hmmm. So why hasn't it been discovered before now?”

“Well, I saw the nymph's trail and spent days and days tracking it down, and I nearly fell to my death dozens of times. If it took an expert collector like me to find it, no one else could have done it.”

Hearing MiniPin's answer, Vikir stroked his chin and thought hard.

The presence of a water source near Fort Tochka was something that hadn't been revealed before the regression.

Perhaps it was a butterfly effect of having MiniPin as a consignment.

'If this is true, it's a great piece of information.'

Vikir recognized the value of this information.

Camus, studying the map, spoke thoughtfully.

“It's not too far away, and the terrain suggests that if we blast the bedrock enough, we might be able to create a waterway to Tochka.”

“Judging by the size of the crater, it looks pretty big and wide, so if there's a water source, I'm guessing it's plentiful.”

“Nymphs only live in large lakes with lots of water. There's a lot of potential.”

Dolores and Sinclaire agreed.

Vikir nodded as well.

MiniPin is a talented person who was selected and chosen during his time in the Imperial Capital, so he also trusts Vikir.

Vikir considers for a moment, then nods.

“Very well. We'll change the plan slightly. First, we'll get the water source for this point.”

Vikir, who is extremely conservative when it comes to changing plans, decided to do something different this time.

A makeshift. No more, no less, just enough drinking water to last a week or so.

When Vikir's decision was made, Cindywendy smiled broadly, as if all was right with the world.

“Finally, I see a way out! I'll support you with all my might!”

The others all look determined and eager to join the quest for water.

Just then.

“Emergency! Emergency! Emergency!”

An urgent report comes in from the sentry on the watchtower outside the window.

“The Leviathan's poisonous man are attacking up ahead, and there's an unknown number of them!”

It was a report that instantly overturned the excited atmosphere caused by the discovery of the water source.

Chapter 453

Infiltration of the water source (2)

◆

“House Leviathan!”

“The poisonous people are coming!”

“They're numerous!”

The cries of the fortress guards were all similar.

The horizon was stained black.

An army of poisonous people covered the ground like a curtain descending from above.

The battle for the destruction of Fortress Tochka began in earnest, with the red death aura flowing like a demonic spirit.

Kyaaaaaaag-

The poisonous people rushed madly towards the first wall.

They cling to the walls with their bare bodies with a fierce aggression and ferocity that cannot be considered human.

...Peoeog!

Just as a bird dies when it hits a wall, the first poisonous man who rushed at the fortress smashed its head against the solid wall of Tochka Fortress and died.

Then another poisonous man stepped on the corpse and smashed his head against the wall.

...Peoeog! ...peoeog! ...peoeog! ...peoeog! ...peoeog! ...peoeog! ...peoeog! ...peoeog! ...peoeog! ...peoeog!

The bodies of the poisonous people piled up one after another, gradually taking on the shape of a mass.

And there was a single figure leading all these poisonous people.

The black hood and cloak that covers his entire body, and the scythe he holds in his hand, has not only the blade but also the hilt bent in a bizarre way.

“...What is he?”

“Has he come to harvest or something?”

The guards ask in disbelief.

...Flash!

The monster swung the scythe in his hand once.

A terrifying poisonous energy flew out with the strike and struck the city wall.

Kwakwang!

The blow was so heavy that the entire city wall shook.

The Harvester wielded his scythe as if he had come to harvest the lives of his enemies.

With each blow, a powerful poisonous aura surrounded him, and the poisonous people around him grew stronger and stronger.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca stood together.

“Is that dark fellow the leader of the vanguard?”

“He seems to be quite skilful. His scythe wielding is quite impressive.”

“He does look like a commander....”

“I think the soldiers call him 'The Harvester,' and it looks like he's here to harvest our lives.”

Bianca was the first to step forward.

“Let's see what you got, shall we?”

Bianca's arrow, the one that had killed Andrealphus, was aimed at the Harvesters.

Peong!

The arrow shot through the air.

“...!”

The Harvester seemed to instinctively sense the threat.

But he didn't raise his scythe.

Chachachachachag!

Bianca's arrows were blocked, as countless poisonous people formed like a human shield.

Bianca fired a few more times after that, but all of her arrows were blocked by the shields before they could reach the Harvester.

“Cih. You're so cheap. What kind of master are you?”

Bianca clicked her tongue as she watched the Harvester back away from the arrows.

But even now, the poisonous people kept coming.

Waves of red death.

The poison they breathed and the fountains of blood they spewed as they died could infect even the unaffected, turning them into poisonous people.

If not for the purifying power of Dolores, who maintains a wide-area divine barrier at the heart of Fort Tochka, this iron fortress would have been shaken.

Chwaag-

The Harvester stretched his hand out to the side, and the poisonous people's path changed.

The Harvester continues to lead the poisonous people, attacking the weakest points in the walls.

He was strong in combat, but he also seemed to have a keen eye for tactics.

“Ugh, these monsters....”

“A combination of a military minded commander and soldiers who blindly follow him. It was not for nothing that they swept through the civil war.”

“And with its poison, it's no wonder it's invincible.”

“Damn it! It's scaring the soldiers!”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca gritted their teeth and encouraged their men, but the tide was turning in Leviathan's favour.

Just then.

“Don't back down, you idiots!”

A gruff shout came from the ramparts above.

All eyes, friend and foe alike, instantly turned to the central castle wall.

There, a huge old man stood tall, holding a club.

Orca. 'Orca Montreuil-sur-Mer Javert'. The warden of Nouvelle Vague.

A master of defence and fortitude, he looked out over the entire battlefield from beneath the ramparts.

“If you retreat, everyone behind you will die! If you fight here, the only thing you'll lose is your own life, and what better business is there than to die alone, or to have your entire family slaughtered!”

The soldiers' eyes snap back to focus as they hear Orca's rant.

For a split second, the atmosphere stopped tilting.

The seasoned veteran did not miss the timing.

“The spearmen and the head carpenters, step forward.”

At Orca's command, the men who had been waiting in the wings stepped forward.

They stretched out their long spears and long trees at the poisonous people climbing the ramparts, pushing them back from a distance far beyond their reach.

And the furry cushions and bamboo drapes that the refugees had made overnight fell down to catch the poisonous blood.

Orca looked away.

In the distance, he could see a cloud of dust rising with the poison fog.

“Dig a hole in the ground, bury the jar, and select those with sensitive senses of hearing and touch to go into it. You can tell if the enemy is digging a tunnel.”

Orca began to organise the defence of the fortress.

“Assign five men to each castle, but appoint one captain for every five strokes, and one captain for every twenty-five strokes. The Chiefs of Command, who are in charge of the 50 strokes, are to direct the divisions of the respective defenses and defend only their respective areas.”

The pre-positioned troops move at Orca's command.

Orca watched the poisonous people squirming camp in real time and continued to give orders.

“The artillerymen in charge of the fortifications must keep the charcoal fires burning and beat the drums every ten minutes, so that the soldiers know they only have to hold out until the next drum. Also, the militia will be on guard inside the castle to ensure that no rogues interfere with supplies, especially oil and gunpowder.”

The tide of battle began to turn again when Orca, who had been watching the situation from the sidelines, stepped to the forefront.

The soldiers had been reassured by the appearance of an old war hero.

With Tochka's defenders now organised, the Poisonous People's offensive was forced to retreat.

“As expected, you're good at it.”

Vikir, who was leading the soldiers on the other side of the wall, looked at Orca's command in the distance and nodded.

Even before his retreat, Orca had been a master of defence and defensive warfare.

It was no exaggeration to say that Orca's participation in the latter stages of the war had kept humanity alive.

Unfortunately, he was protecting the Nouvelle Vague at the bottom of the deep sea while the war intensified, and he entered the war at the very end, so he was unable to prevent countless people from dying in the early and middle stages of the war.

...But now is different.

Brought to the surface by Vikir, Orca was working for humanity before the war had even begun in earnest.

And in earnest!

“We're in trouble! They're coming from Leviathan House with shields and carts, and the Poisonous Army is approaching!”

The poisonous army was carrying shields to defend against arrows and stones, and long ladders for the city walls.

There were also huge poisonous man with huge axes, trying to chip away at the stones and pillars at the base of the walls.

But Orca's face remained unchanged as he gave the following instructions.

“Pour the oil supplied to the militia onto the ramparts of the wall, and the potters throw charcoal on it. Put away the lances and the hangman's nooses, and in their place, tie sacks of gunpowder and iron shavings to chains and roll them over the ramparts.”

Soon, the oil is flowing down the slightly sloping walls of Fort Tochka.

The poisonous man, who climbed the castle wall as if they were rock climbing fell down after struggling, covered in oil.

The slippery walls were too steep for even the strongest of poisonous man could not climb it.

Gunpowder, shards of iron, and charcoal rained down on them.

Kwakwakwakwang!

The oil, flames, and gunpowder combined to create a chain of explosions.

The shards of iron scattered together spread with terrifying force, tearing through the poisonous people.

Not a single limb was left intact amongst the small and exploding bodies that soared into the sky.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca's mouths dropped open in amazement.

“Well, I don't think you have any particularly ingenious or special strategies, but you're still amazing.”

“It is exactly as it is in the textbook. It is an extremely standard and exemplary water battle.”

“It's actually quite difficult to be precise, because you need to know exactly what's going on with your troops and control them so that you don't lose your supply and troops.”

“Is sticking to the basics the most difficult thing? That's amazing... I guess this is a matter of age and experience.”

As time passed, the poisonous people's general offensive was clearly weakening.

The red evil spirits on the horizon were gradually opening up holes.

The brave soldiers looked up at the ramparts and cried out.

“Woaaaah! The poisonous people are backing down! It's the war hero of the old country!”

“We've almost stopped them! Hail, Major General Orca! Hail!”

“Javert, what do we do now!”

“Hurry up and give the next order!”

The crowd was sending a torrent of abuse towards Orca.

However, the Orca only exhaled thick cigarette smoke and frowned as if it were annoyed.

“What do I know after that?”

...?

The words that made everyone doubt their own ears came out of the mouth of the old country's war hero.

Orca chewed on his words as he watched the enemy's fire slowly die down.

“I only defend. Offence is for others.”

When he finished, he jerked his cigarette to the side in disgust.

Everyone's eyes shifted to the side wall Orca had pointed out.

And there, an old man with a creepy smile on his face.

“Pushishishi....”

Sade. The former Marquis de Sade, Cédric de Sade, Ang-gajumang.

He looks down at the poisonous army in front of him with a look of amusement on his face.

Chapter 455

Infiltration of the Water Source (4)

◆

Viscount Giuseppe Baldini, a demon of the House of Leviathan, was a man of some importance in the battle to destroy Tochka.

He was guarding the rear of the fortress, far back from the front line that surrounded Tochka.

The front siege network of Tochka Fortress was so tight that there was literally no room for even a needle to pass through, but the back area, where only Tochka's walls were visible, was relatively loose.

But lax was only relative, as Viscount Baldini had a large number of minions standing guard, and he himself was constantly on guard in the command center barracks.

[... Still, it's a good thing, for there's no chance of the enemy coming this far back.]

Even before he became a demon, Viscount Baldini was a man who sought stability and security.

His personality hasn't changed much since becoming a demon, even though he's gained great power.

[If the enemy appears elsewhere, I can quickly reinforce them there. In normal times, we can be a little more relaxed, but only in wartime do we need to be quick to respond.]

And so Viscount Baldini is now enjoying a cup of tea and a biscuit, enjoying his reverie.

Right now.

Teng-

The sound of the guard post door opening was heard.

At the same time, the panicked exclamations of some of the lower-ranking minions could be heard.

[Ha, you must not enter without permission...]

[Ugh- No way...]

[Oh no...]

Viscount Baldini looked up, wondering what was going on.

He saw a woman standing there.

Her cascading red hair and intensely glowing red eyes were the color of blood, as if they had been marinated in it.

Above all, this overwhelming magic emanating from her, how on earth....

He quickly checked his schedule for the day, but there were no appointments with the high-ranking demon.

No visits from above were scheduled either.

Viscount Baldini tensed up.

[...Who are you?]

In response to Viscount Baldini's question, the red-haired woman revealed her identity and affiliation.

[I'm 'Tzersi', the left wing commander of the Tochka Exterminators, and I need to get past this post to the rear, so fill out a pass for me].

Viscount Baldini racked his brain, trying to think of a high-ranking demon named Tzersi in the main camp.

But there were no female minions of that name and rank in Leviathan that he knew of.

'Well, I don't know all the people in my family. She could also be a person from the House of Usher or the House of Donquixote.'

House Leviathan had recently absorbed troops from House Usher and House Donquixote, which had led to a sharp rise in their power.

Because of this, the chain of command was not yet fully organized.

So Viscount Baldini decided to continue the conversation in a gentle tone, rather than jump to conclusions.

[If you'll excuse me, ... I'm afraid my memory is too poor to recall who you are, but what brings you here?]

[Do I have to tell you all that? It's a top secret from the headquarters. Just give me your pass].

The red-haired woman, who gave her name as Tzersi, snorted and gave orders in an arrogant tone.

Viscount Baldini swallowed hard to keep from cringing.

'Judging by your arrogance, you're a Leviathan, and I don't need to confirm it.'

However, Viscount Baldini was also not an easy person.

[Pardon me, this is wartime, we will follow military law. Could you please show me your ID?]

Tzersi's brow furrowed at that.

The magic she'd been subtly exuding earlier had now become a full-blown blast.

[...Okay. You're going to protest, right?]

[No, I'm just asking you to go through the procedure. Even though I'm an external figure, I've been to the main house a few times, and I don't recognize you from those times. ...]

[Hmph, Isn't it natural that I am an illegitimate child? You idiot.]

At the mention of illegitimate child, Viscount Baldini closed his mouth as if he was going to be sick.

An illegitimate child from a real family would certainly be rarely seen in the public eye.

After all, an illegitimate child is the family's scion.

'I shouldn't have brought up the subject of the real family and illegitimacy, now that I've stirred up the illegitimate child complex of such a high ranking figure. I'm sure I'm in trouble.'

Just as Viscount Baldini realized that things were getting out of hand, Tzersi spoke up.

[Okay, okay, I don't need a pass, I'll go back to the main camp and come back with an ID, you're right, it's military law].

[...Yes? A, aaah. Thank you so much for your understanding].

Viscount Baldini's eyes narrowed as he realized that things were going to be unexpectedly easy.

He was almost suspicious that the other party would back down so easily.

Viscount Baldini should have been appalled, however, at Tzersi's next words.

[You seem to be very fond of military law, so I'll give you military law. I will 'dare' to go back to the main camp and get my ID. A mission so urgent that I forgot my ID will be greatly delayed by your inflexible attitude, and you will pay for it.]

[....]

[Oh, and before I go, I'd like to take a look at the condition of the sword and shield hanging from your waist, and I want them in front of me right now, and why is the button on your uniform top unbuttoned, and why is the knot in your boot laces tied like that? I'm going to take a good look at how well you're following the military code before I head back to base, and I'll report back to my superiors as soon as I get back].

Tzersi's eyes radiated heat like hellfire.

It was as if she would not tolerate even the smallest, most microscopic of pods.

She turned to Viscount Baldini, who was trembling in front of her, and shouted.

[Attention! Why do you keep sitting there while your superiors are talking! You arrogant bastard!]

[I, I'm sorry!]

Viscount Baldini quickly rose to his feet and saluted.

Tzersi gritted her teeth and circled around him.

By military law, everything in this room is illegal.

His sword was lightly stained and his shield was rusted, if only slightly.

The inside of the barracks was dusty, and the soldiers' clothes were often unbuttoned or untied.

[I was going to be reasonable and let it slide, but given your attitude, I can't].

[....]

[Poor clothing, poor maintenance, poor hygiene in the barracks, poor soldier discipline Hey... And you're drinking tea and biscuits in the middle of a battlefield? Apparently, they're not rations, they're chaplain's snacks. Also, is this the time of day when you're allowed to eat?]

[....]

[You're not following any of the military laws you like, so what's the point?]

[....]

[A man like you, so strict with others and so lenient with himself, is bound to get into trouble someday].

Tzersi reached out with a casual hand, grabbed Viscount Baldini by the hair, and yanked him back.

...Kwak!

Then, in an eerie voice, she said.

[No, I'll have to send you to the front lines right at dawn tomorrow, and as soon as I get back to the main camp, I'll send your proposal to...]

At that, Viscount Baldini shouted in a voice that was almost crying.

[A, a pass, I will write you a pass, I am guilty of death!]

Then Tzersi shook her head.

[It's not necessary, I'm going back to the main camp. Your class and unit will be assigned to the frontline suicide raiders at dawn tomorrow].

[Front, frontline!? Suicide squad there!?]

The assault squad was the unit that suffered the most casualties in today's siege with Major General Orca and Marquis de Sade.

Viscount Baldini's face was beginning to turn as pale as a corpse.

The normally stoic Viscount Valdini dropped to his knees and began to beg.

[My, my, I was short of thought, I'll give you a pass, and I'll contact the rear and arrange for you to go with as little inconvenience as possible, please, just the assault party...!]

The mood in the barracks had completely changed.

Tzersi nodded, annoyed, but not surprised.

[I've memorized your face, your name, and your unit number, in case something happens to send me back to the main camp...]

[Well, I'll make sure that doesn't happen!]

[...Hmm. I'll count on it].

Finished speaking, Tzersi snorted and grabbed her pass.

She turned on her heel and left the barracks.

Viscount Baldini, left behind in the barracks, wiped the sweat from his brow and breathed a sigh of relief.

One of the lesser minions beside him asked with an uneasy expression.

[Viscount, do you think it's okay to issue me a pass without identification?]

[Hey. Didn't you see the magic that bitch just gave off?]

Viscount Baldini shook his head as if he'd just been dismissed from a crane.

[And by the looks of what she's doing, she's a absolute poisoner, a demon to the bone].

◆

[Look at that. I told you this works, right?]

She brought her low voice back to its original state in an instant.

Camus Morgue. She'd sold her ancestor's name long ago and pretended to be a demon.

“The name is full of magic energy. And I am also confident in my ability to emit magic energy. Of course, it just smells.”

When she finished, Camus turned her head.

On her shoulder was Seere, tears dripping down her cheeks from the smell.

Whatever.

“Well done.”

Vikir patted Camus on the shoulder.

The first gateway to the water source was easily breached thanks to Camus's initiative.

With a pass from Viscount Baldini, the gates behind them were nearly free passes as well.

After that, they passed through a few more private guard posts.

Huug-

A gust of wind from the front hit everyone's noses.

The breeze carried a hot, foul odor.

Vikir looks up and sees red spirits swarming over the horizon.

“...The Plaguelands. Probably a place of poisonous people.”

“I'll cover you from here.”

Dolores summoned the last of her holy power and gave each of them a drop of her Tear of the Saint.

With the exception of Vikir and Camus, who were immune to almost all poisons, everyone was protected by Dolores and able to survive the Red Death.

The group of eight then made their way over the gentle ridge to the next gateway.

Along the way, a red mist drifted across the ground, strewn with the corpses of the poisonous people.

Soon, through the red mist, they could see Leviathan's second siege network.

Seeing the shadows of barracks and wooden fences, Vikir began to calculate the distance.

Where poisonous people are present, strategies such as disguised identity will no longer work.

“15 minutes to infiltrate.”

From now on, it was time to force a breakthrough.

Chapter 460

Infiltration of the Water Source (9)

◆

[Oh- the demon hunter from back then, s this the first time since the trial in Nakajaniye?]

“....”

Vikir did not answer Flauros's question.

Talking to demons was an energy drain in itself, and he didn't feel it was worth the effort.

So Vikir decided to just give a short pep talk.

“Die.”

The magic sword Beelzebub emitted a crimson aura.

...Flash!

There was no guarantee of a one-hit kill anyway, so Vikir chose the most confident of the options, 4th Form.

A four-toothed slash.

His strongest attack in his previous life and his most comfortable attack in this life.

Not only does it cost almost no mana, but it's more skillful than breathing.

Vikir's sword attack perfectly grasped in all four directions, biting through the space of Flauros.

But Flauros's skill with the spear was just as impressive.

'Original Ouroboros'. A deadly weapon, a terrifying artifact that creates red death.

Flauros smirked.

[Seven Demon Sword... Is that Beelzebub? However, there are many other weapons made from the remains of ancient demon constellations. At that time, there were more than one demon constellation. And my spear is one of them].

Are these the remains of demons who lived in some distant past?

The two weapons containing poison were clashing fiercely, creating countless sparks.

Kwakwang!

The Red Evil Spirit and the Dark Sun clashed.

Before he knew it, Vikir was using his full power against Flauros.

“Tsk-”

Vikir stepped back, spitting blood that had turned red from the plague poison.

Madame's poison was rapidly circulating in his body.

It bubbled through his veins, churning through his body as it ate up any plague poison that came in from outside his body.

It had been a long time since it had reacted so violently, perhaps recognizing the Red Death as an unwelcome rival.

...Pakang!

The Original Ouroboros slammed down on Beelzebub with the tip of its two blades.

At the same time, the hilt made from the sack of the Hell Tree struck Vikir's head.

“...!”

Vikir, who tilted his head back to avoid it, had a scar on his forehead.

It was a vicious wound that would not easily regenerate, even with Basilisk's regenerative powers.

[A sack carved from the shards of the Hell Tree. When Amdusias was killed, I also obtained some fragments.]

Flauros smiled wickedly, his eyes still full of amusement.

Then.

“Vikir!”

“Vikir-nim!”

“Brother!”

Red, white, and gold. Three shimmering lights emanated from the sides and behind Vikir.

Camus, Dolores, and Sinclaire were supporting Vikir.

Camus's fire, Dolores's holy power, and Sinclaire's magic and money were now directed at Flauros in front of him.

Wagigigigig- ujijig!

The sound of powerful intangible forces clashing and twisting against each other.

The ground shifts, breaks, and reconnects, naturally changing the landscape around them.

Even in the midst of his struggle, Flauros looked at Vikir and his companions and spoke in wonder.

[You guys fight really hard for others. There will be no benefit to you personally in confronting me...]

Fighting together, a sight that would certainly be incomprehensible to a demon.

A demon is basically a being who engages in 'the struggle of all against all'.

In the first place, demons are a concept defined by humans, so they are not grouped into a single species.

For example, 3rd Corpse Andrealphus and 4th Corpse Cimeries are as far apart as a goldfish and a grasshopper in terms of biological characteristics.

Vikir knew this, and could somewhat understand Flauros's puzzlement.

“You might not be able to sympathize with beings who don't know how to do anything other than fight and steal.”

[Isn't that the same for you too? In the first place, humans are a deteriorated version of demons. The part you occupy in this worldview could be better performed by demons.]

Flauros smirked, but continued to thrust his spear.

Apart from the swinging spear, the demon's tongue also continued to wriggle like a snake.

[My poisonous soldiers have probably begun the siege by now, and I'm very curious to see how long your friends in Tochka will hold out].

“...!”

Vikir gritted his teeth.

House Leviathan's poisonous soldiers had finally begun the siege of Tochka.

It was unclear how long they would be able to hold off such a powerful army of mutants.

They are fortunate to have Major General Orca and Marquis de Sade on their side, but in the face of overwhelming numerical superiority, they are helpless.

[There is no hope for you. No water has been found, and you cannot protect your comrades. I can't wait to see the look on your faces when you see that all the humans in Tochka have been turned into poisonous people.]

The faces of the entire group fell as they heard Flauros' words.

But there was nothing to argue with.

So Camus, Dolores, Sinclaire, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca all just stared at him in disbelief.

Except for ...Vikir.

“You underestimate the power of humans.”

Flauros narrowed his eyes in surprise at Vikir's words.

[Is this the kind of situation that can be solved by force?]

“That is unknown.”

[I see, hahaha- you seemed to have the most realistic personality, didn't you?]

“That's why I say that.”

[...?]

With that, Vikir drew Beelzebub out even longer.

8th Form. The black sun spun even more fiercely, crushing Flauros.

Soon, the distance between Vikir and Flauros has narrowed to the point where their noses are touching.

Udeudeug- udeug!

At the forefront where energy clashed with energy, Vikir whispered into Flauros' ear.

“It is not wise to predict the future, for it changes just as quickly as you predict it.”

[....]

“Just like right now.”

[...?]

Flauros just shook his head.

...Peoeog!

His vision flashes black for a moment.

Flauros jerks his head back with a jolt that feels like his throat is being ripped out.

An iron arrow the size of a child's forearm was stuck in his temple and was trembling.

An arrow much stronger than the one fired by Bianca.

How tough does the bowstring have to be to send off such a large and thick arrow like that?

And how strong does one's arm have to be to pull such a string?

Even Flauros had experienced such a powerful arrow before.

A memory of how everything almost went to waste with just one carelessness.

A night when he had truly feared for his life.

[...No way!?]

Flauros turns his head in horror.

Pfft.

Another arrow flew by, this time lodging itself in the center of Flauros' forehead.

[Keug!?]

Flauros backs away, spraying black blood.

And a thin shadow flutters over the cliff behind it.

“Long time no see, Husby.”

The female warrior turns to Vikir and offers a brief greeting.

Seeing her face, Vikir can't help but breathe a sigh of relief in many ways.

Aiyen. A female warrior of Ballak. A colleague who was imprisoned at Level Ten in the Nouvelle Vague has appeared again.

Aiyen smirked at Vikir, then greeted the Night Walkers behind them.

“Some I've seen, some I haven't. Anyway, please take care of me.”

“That! Where can you pretend to be friends!?”

Camus exclaims through gritted teeth, and Aiyen's eyes narrow.

“Why? Do you want to be stripped off again?”

“Kyaaaaaah! You're behind!”

Camus's hostility was even stronger than when she was fighting the demon.

But their confrontation was interrupted by another figure.

[Hohohoho- If it's Ouroboros, you have the same name as me, isn't that stealing?]

A thick whip flew out and struck Flauros across the torso.

Sadi. The professor who rode all the way to Nouvelle Vague to save her grandfather, Marquis de Sade.

She activated Belial's eyeballs and turned into a demonized version of herself, blocking Flauros' path.

...Cheolsseog!

The whip swung like a snake, slicing through the poisonous people in the area.

Aiyen was also sending arrows and punching holes in Flauros' body.

“I caught almost everything before, but then lost him. But not this time.”

Aiyen, who is a native of Ballak's hunting grounds, had once tried unsuccessfully to sneak into Leviathan alone and assassinate the patriarch, Hobbes.

It is a matter of shame for Ballak's hunters to pursue the same prey twice.

So it's no wonder that Aiyen is so eager to make amends.

...Peong!

Flauros dodged the spur arrows with an annoyed expression.

Flauros forcibly pulled out the two arrows lodged in his head and growled, showing his fangs like those of a leopard.

[Fate does not change just because two miscellaneous things increase.]

Just then.

“Two?”

One more voice whispered in Flauros's ear.

[...!?]

When had he been caught from behind?

Without even realizing it, they were right behind him.

Through the gap that Aiyen and Sadi had created.

...Cheolsseog!

A large leech clung to Flauros's back.

The Magic Sword Asmodeus.

A terrifying weapon that sucks the blood of its victims.

It was sucking the life force out of Flauros's body in a single gulp.

[Keuhag!?]

For the first time, a bloody scream came out of Flauros' mouth.

“....”

Vikir's eyes narrowed as he recognized the face of the figure holding Flauros tightly behind him.

A body connected to the Magic Sword Asmodeus, black veins covering the entire body, and a black aura fluttering fiercely over the shoulders.

Black Tongue.

An old acquaintance from Nouvelle Vague, whom he had thought he would never see again, glared at him.

Chapter 461

Infiltration of the Water Source (10)

◆

A world where red evil spirits run rampant.

The Saint's Tears, stored deep within Tochka Fortress, were drying up.

The holy water that the priests, led by Dolores, have been sprinkling all over the walls is running out, and so are the poisonous people's attacks.

The walls, once so high, were now much lower.

The ground had been raised by the many corpses of the poisonous people that had fallen from above.

The siege began at dawn and continued until nightfall.

...Kwakwang!

A black palm rose above the castle wall.

The palm, larger than the average soldier's body, was rotting with poison.

[Geu-oooooh!]

A mutant, whose combat strength easily surpassed that of a poisonous common soldier, emerged over the castle walls.

It had been bathed in oil, flame, gunpowder, and nails during its climb up the wall, and its appearance was even more hideous than when it first reached the base of the wall.

“Aaaahhh!”

“Poisonous people! No, it's a monster!”

“Stop it, stop it! If that thing gets inside the castle...!”

The soldiers brought out their clubs and long spears and tried to push the mutant back, but it was like pushing a boulder with a toothpick.

The heavily built creature was not being pushed back at all.

[Ku-rrrrrrrrr...]

Then, the mutant pulled itself fully up onto the walls.

The first poisonous man to successfully climb the walls of Tochka was born.

The creature stood nearly six meters tall, its tongue dangling from its missing lower jaw as it stalked its prey.

Eventually, the Mutant spots a boy soldier who is too late to escape.

[Ooooooh!]

The Mutant raised its giant palm.

“Aaa... Ahhhh....”

The boy soldier tripped over a stone beak on the ground and could only cry out, not even daring to anticipate the weight of death falling upon him.

And then.

Jjeoeog-

A hideous mouth gaped open.

A mouth that has everything you would expect, with protruding gums, sharp teeth, and a tongue that dangles from one side.

The problem is that it is stuck all over the body, not where it should be.

The mouth attached to the center of the mutant's palm pointed at the soldier on the ground.

“No!”

Several soldiers rushed to the boy's aid, but it was too late.

...Just then.

Boom!

A terrifying sound erupted.

It felt as if something huge and fast had swept past in a blink of an eye.

“...?”

When the boy soldier regained his senses, the monster was no longer in front of him.

Because it was flying like a piece of trash into the sky in the distance.

...Boom!

The flying poisonous man disappeared into the sky, and soon collapsed into a blood clot on the ground.

And in front of the boy soldier stood a tall, old man looking down at him.

Warden Orca. The Overlord of the Nouvelle Vague prison guards.

He stood guard on the ramparts, a large club in his hand.

“Hold your ground, boy soldier.”

With that, Orca walked up the ramparts, his club in place.

His demeanor was casual, as if nothing had happened.

“...Yes!”

The boy soldier saluted as if he'd been crying all day.

His eyes shone, rekindling the hope that had been dying from lack of sleep and water.

Soon, energized by Orca's appearance, the soldiers began to push back the poisonous people again.

They scavenged for oil and lit the fire with gunpowder scraped from the floor.

If they couldn't find a piece of iron, they'd pick up a rock and throw it.

Orca barked out instructions in a gruff voice.

“Each of you report to the Chancellor on the state of the castle tower, and abandon the broken parts of the outer castle; we can stop it from the inner castle!”

“Tell all the vigilantes in charge of security within the castle to come up, the situation within the castle is pointless now!”

“Focus your arrows on the poisonous soldier, and don't let them take down the lower part of the walls!”

“For the stokers of the cannons, pour in the oil and gunpowder without sparing anything! Just hold out until the next drum beats!”

His gaze reached every corner of the defenses.

He would closely examine in real time what was crumbling and what was holding, and then send in reinforcements.

Of course, he didn't just give orders.

He was at the front of the line, swinging clubs to crack the skulls of the poisonous people.

Neither long, sharp spears nor thick, fast arrows could penetrate Orca's unseasonably thick coat of fur.

...Charararak!

As the club wrapped around the chain flew through the air, and all the mutants hanging from the ramparts fell with their skulls cracked open.

“Oooh, Major General Orca, the god of defensive warfare!”

“Master of water warfare!”

“As long as Orca-nim is here, Tochka will not fall!”

The soldiers' morale was high.

However. Many have seen the back of a hero, but few have seen the front.

No one could truly see the expression on Orca's face as he stood on the front lines.

'...This is a difficult situation.'

Orca's brow was currently furrowed.

No one could see the cold sweat running down his temples and spine, hidden by his tight gray hair, beard, and thick fur coat.

Orca gazed at the horizon below the ramparts.

It was all black.

The sky was filled with red death spirits, and there was no end to the number of poisonous people coming.

“No wonder we have a civil war.”

The House of Leviathan was indeed powerful enough to overwhelm the combined forces of all the other Houses.

Moreover, each and every one of the poisonous people coming from now on were mutants of great size and power.

No matter how invincible Tochka's fortress may be, it is ultimately overwhelmed.

Even Orca, a master of defensive warfare, could not overcome such a numerical disadvantage.

Especially in a place like this, where ragtag vigilantes recruited from the refugee population make up the overwhelming majority of the army.

“This is regrettable. If only my soldiers in Nouvelle Vague had been there....”

Orca fumbled with his other hand, the one holding the bloodied club.

He searched for a cigarette.

However, the cigarette had long since been burned off, with the insides turning black.

Orca cleared his throat, which was parched from lack of water.

It was his habit when he ran out of tobacco.

Just then.

Chuck.

A cigarette pack was held out from Orca's right side.

It was filled with his favorite thick cigars.

“...?”

Orca instinctively pulled out a cigarette.

And then.

Chick-.

A matchstick flicked out from Orca's left side, lighting the end of his cigarette.

“...?”

Orca is just about to turn his head to the side.

[Geu-oooooh!!]

Two giant poisonous mutants leap toward Orca.

And.

Kwa-kwakwakwakwang!

In the blink of an eye, the two mutants are torn to shreds.

One shredded by the swirling storm of charges, the other impaled by the countless spikes protruding from the ground and ramparts.

Then, beneath a shower of falling flesh and blood, two shadows rose from the dust.

“So.”

“Who will be the next head of the prison?”

Two figures, a man and a woman, stood in front of Orca and asked the question.

Both faces were familiar to Orca.

“D'Ordume. Souaré. How did you guys get here...?”

Major General Orca looked a little taken aback.

Then a squeaky voice came from behind him.

“You can't see me because I'm small? I was a little taller.”

Orca's gaze turned to see a girl in a black helmet.

BDISSEM.

She reached out and swung a bunch of BDISSEM restraints.

Peopeopeopeopeog!

The poisonous people climbing the castle are instantly reduced to powerless, mana-less fools, and falling down the walls.

Out of the water, the effect was less effective, but it was enough to halt the poisonous people's general assault.

“...Huh.”

Orca seemed surprised to see the Nouvelle Vague's wardens here.

And then. Something happened that surprised him even more.

Kkuleuleuleuleug-tsutsutsutsu...

A rust-colored glow that started on one side of his vision and slowly colored the entire area.

It looks like moss is growing all over the castle walls.

It sprouted from between the bricks that made up the walls of Tochka Fortress, from the gaps between brick and brick, and soon covered the entirety of the vast wall.

[...Oook?]

[...Grrrr?]

[...Kiik-sshhh?]

The poisonous mutants climbing the walls, sticking their fingers between brick and brick, were bewildered by the greenish liquid that filled every gap they could find.

It was slippery and squishy and... intensely hot!

Chiiiig!

The terrifying acidic green liquid soon began to cover all the poisonous people climbing the walls.

[Kaaaaaaaaaagh!]

The poisonous people scrambled to escape the melting skin, flesh, and bone, but it was too late.

Jjeobjjeobjjeobjjeob-

The liquid that oozed from between the cracks in the stones of the wall moved as if it were alive, engulfing the poisonous people and growing in volume as it did so.

“Has it even come....”

Orca muttered to himself as he watched the green ooze slide down the ramparts, devouring all of the poisonous people.

Flubber J Tarbond.

Even the prehistoric creatures of unknown race that had inhabited the Nouvelle Vague since before it was discovered had made its appearance here.

Chapter 462

Infiltration of the Water Source (11)

◆

The whirlpool of slashes roars like a giant serpent, wiping out the poisonous people.

D'Ordume spins the axe blades that have sprouted from his forearms, shredding the poisonous people beneath the ramparts.

Souaré was no slouch in her dwarven power either.

Earthen spears protruded from beneath the ramparts, skewering the charging poisonous people in an instant.

The twin walls towing the Nouvelle Vague were equally effective in the deep sea as they were on land.

With only two more joining the front line, the poisonous force slowed slightly.

Orca asked, feeling his strength returning a little.

“How did you guys know to come here?”

“I'll explain that when we're done with the immediate situation.”

D'Ordume replied as he crushed the head of one of the poisonous people.

Apparently, he had been through a lot.

Orca nodded for now.

The urgency now was to stop the poisonous people from trying to overcome Tochka's walls.

The situation was gradually improving.

Cheolpudeog! Cheolpudeog! Cheolpudeog! Cheolpudeog!

A giant greenish liquid bubbled up and slid down the walls of Tochka.

The green liquid flowed down the slightly sloping walls, which were designed to protect against artillery fire, and then began to engulf all of the poisonous people climbing the walls.

Flubber. The most mysterious creature in Nouvelle Vague had made its appearance here.

Jjeobjjeobjjeobjjeobjjeobjjeobjjeob-

Covering an enormous area, the green, liquid monster began to fatten itself by devouring all the poisonous people it could find.

Those swallowed into its body struggle desperately, only to fall deeper and deeper into its bottomless slime prison.

Pusisisisisig-

Orca clucked his tongue at Flubber's insatiable appetite, which consumed even the mutants.

“How did that thing get here?”

This time Souaré answered.

“It must have followed us when it ran out of places to live, for it was a prehistoric creature that was quite attached to the place called Nouvelle Vague.”

“Followed us? Voluntarily? Did it have any sense of loyalty?”

“No, I think it just followed the scent of its prey. It had once consumed a certain poison in prisoner called Sakkuth, and it must have liked it quite a bit.”

Souaré was right.

Indeed, Flubber had been feasting on Leviathan's poisons, and apparently the very idea of red death was quite appealing to Flubber's palate.

And since they had been bred to be even more potent than they smelled, perhaps their flavor would be even more intense.

“...I'm glad to see you like the taste.”

Orca couldn't help but say this with sincerity.

He had to admit, the poisonous mutants that had been plaguing Tochka so relentlessly seemed to Flubber to be nothing more than a big lump of candy.

But there was more.

“Warden Orca, give me orders!”

“I don't want to follow those wardens!”

“Khahaha! You're the only one who can boss me around!”

Behind D'Ordume, Souaré, BDISSEM, and Flubber, countless other figures appeared.

All of them wore the uniforms of Nouvelle Vague's guards.

The guards of the Nouvelle Vague.

An elite group of all-stars who spent their days in the harsh environment 10,000 meters below the surface of the sea, working more like service than work.

Here they were, the men whose humanity was unknown, but whose skill was untouchable.

A grin appeared on Director Orca's dull face.

Then he blew a puff of smoke from his cigarette and shouted.

“Now! It's a suppression formation! Give those foolish dead men their due!”

The prisoner must be returned to where he belongs. The same goes for the dead.

The guards of Nouvelle Vague chuckled and crossed their arms.

Then the guards began to take control of the front lines, leaving the vigilantes who had volunteered among Tochka's refugees behind.

“Oi- oi- those who can't use mana, stay back.”

“What, you're joining the war with your kid? You're out of your mind. Get back!”

“This is for people like us, who have nothing to lose!”

These were people who had spent their lives preventing and quelling riots.

The poisonous people' display began to collapse in the blink of an eye.

As the old guard joined the front lines, Orca's skills as a master of water warfare were truly shining through.

“From now on, all positions above the rank of Captain will be filled by Nouvelle Vague! I'm reorganizing the system in real time! You stokers, get off your ass! Continue beating the drums as before, but double the time interval! Push out all the stones in the women's room!”

Lieutenant Colonel Bastille, who always made sure everything was in place before Orca told him to do anything, took charge this time.

“The stokers are to go down to the castle and procure oil and gunpowder; the drums are to be beaten longer, for the guards can hold out much longer than the vigilantes; the reason we are rolling the stones down is to start an all-out war, so everyone throw away your spears and long spears and arm yourself with your favorite weapons!”

The guards of the Nouvelle Vague who take care of themselves so that Orca does not have to give detailed explanations.

The rest of the guards are pushed to the front lines to wipe out the poisonous people.

Peopeopeopeog!

BDISSEM has subdued all of the poisonous people around her, tossing them behind her.

With their strength and mana sealed away, the poisonous people are reduced to fools and impaled by the vigilantes' long spears.

Flubber continues to grow in size, devouring more and more poisonous people.

D'Ordume and Souaré also sweep through the poisonous people at breakneck speed.

Suddenly, Orca turns to BDISSEM beside him.

“But. Flubber Was that guy originally that small? Wasn't it bigger before?”

“It's split up now. The main body is somewhere else.”

“...Else where?”

BDISSEM opened her mouth to reply, but the sound was muffled by the poisonous mutant screaming loudly from above.

Orca asked once more.

“Wait. If you're all gathered here, does that mean... 'he' is alive too?”

BDISSEM immediately understood who Orca was referring to.

“If it's 'Black Tongue,' he never made it out of Nouvelle Vague and died.”

“...I see.”

Orca clicked his tongue for a moment, then spoke.

“It had to be done. We're better off without that rebellious behavior. It only divides our allies.”

“Well, it's not quite gone, though.”

“...?”

The unintelligible words from earlier kept coming.

So is Black Tongue dead or alive?

Just when Orca thinks he's about to get a proper answer.

...Boom!

The walls collapsed in front of him, revealing a giant poisonous mutant.

It was larger than any Mutant he had ever seen before.

Its grotesque appearance was like two or three mutants mashed together into one body,

Intimidating just standing there, so large that even Flubber couldn't swallow it in one bite.

[O-ooooooh...]

It opened its mouth and attempted to sweep away the guards on the ramparts with a single blow.

“...Tck.”

Orca was just about to raise his club to strike back.

Jjeoeog-

There was a twist before that.

The poisonous mutant's head caved in, and a black thunderbolt rained down from above.

A whip. A long, thick weapon.

Like a spear falling from the sky, it dented the poisonous mutant's skull, sending its massive form sprawling and tumbling down the city walls.

Kwakwakwang!

A heavy vibration rises from beneath the walls.

Orca's frown deepened as he looked at the cloud of dust rising.

It was the sound of laughter that made his ears perk up.

“Pushishishi-”

Across the walls. An old man stood like a ghost on the uneven surface of the ramparts.

Marquis de Sade.

He was still looking at Orca with a look of amusement.

Orca growled.

“I thought you'd thrown me out long ago. Where have you been hiding, and now you're popping out?”

“Out? Why would I? This was just getting interesting.”

“...?”

Orca raised an eyebrow.

It wasn't long before he realized what was amusing Sade so much.

Suddenly, countless shadows began to fall to his side and behind him.

That's right.

The guards weren't the only ones fleeing from Nouvelle Vague.

“Kukukuku – it's always fun to follow Marquis de Sade around.”

“To fight under him again, it will be an eternal honor.”

“I can't wait to get on the rampage.”

“Ah- old times!”

Prisoners of Nouvelle Vague, now escapees.

Now that there are no cells to imprison them, no guards to keep them, they have gathered under the name of their former master, or former superior, Marquis de Sade.

Each and every one of them had been involved in the 47 Man Riot in the past.

Those who had escaped exile or extermination, but had been drunk on Marquis de Sade's turbulence and followed him, remained secretive.

There were also a great many who had envied Marquis de Sade's power and notoriety in prison and sought to join him.

The monsters of Level Nine bared their teeth after Marquis de Sade.

The descendants of the defeated nations, who had been holding their tongues for so long, united to vent their frustrations.

Sade chuckled and turned to Orca.

“Honestly, what kind of war do you want to fight with a bunch of little chick from the academy or refugees? You've got to be a little more than this to command.”

“...It's absurd that I'm thinking the same thing as you at this moment.”

Orca spit out the cigarette, lit a new one, and turned away from Sade.

But it was an unspoken message. Orca would defend the castle, and Sade would counterattack.

Whether Sade got the message or not, he just chuckled.

Then Marquis de Sade raised his whip high and shouted to the prisoners.

“Here we go! Counterattack! Let's wipe out the foolish enemy, or better yet, drive them right back to the water source!”

Most of the poisonous people panicked while wearing BDISSEM handcuffs.

The people who know best in the world how terrifying those restraints are are the guards and prisoners gathered here now.

Their eyes widened in unison and they clenched their weapons.

The heat was so intense it could burst at any moment, and Marquis de Sade poured oil on it.

“Aren't you all thirsty! Let's go get some water!”

The guards, prisoners, and refugees were all thirsty for the scarce drinking water.

A fire burned in their eyes as hot as their throats.

Now it was time to counterattack.

Chapter 464

The Prelude to a Counterattack (2)

◆

[Goooooooohhh!]

Powerful poisonous mutants burst through the ground.

Each one of them is a monster with a huge and hideous body.

One of the men at the forefront of the reinforcements drew a crimson sword and began slicing the poisonous mutants into pieces like rotten radishes.

...Peopeopeopeog!

Osiris, the young lord of the Iron Blood Swordman Family, stood tall over the corpses of the poisonous people, who were collapsing with a fountain of blood.

“Eat a lot, nephew.”

Osiris swept away even the evil spirits of the Red Death and turned his head to the side.

There stood a girl with black hair and red eyes.

“Yes uncle!”

“...Not uncle, Samchun.”

“Uncle!”

“I'm sad. Why don't you call me Samchun....”

But before Osiris could finish his sentence, the Pomeranian stretched his hands out in front of him.

Tsutsutsutsuts...

The Wraith Tree grew.

Dark red ghosts rise above the corpses of dead poisonous people as if they were being pulled out.

Skull-shaped berries burst open on its gnarled branches.

A battlefield is the best place for a Wraith Tree to grow.

Then.

[Kyaaaaah!]

From behind Pomeranian, one of the surviving poisonous people rushed forward, dragging his battered body.

It was a cunning creature that had been lying on the ground like a corpse the entire time.

It stretched out its long arms to grab Pomeranian.

Peopeopeog!

Three strands of strikes sliced through the poisonous people's arm.

Fluttering-

Three black wisps of blood stood in Pomeranian's way.

Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro.

They looked up at the mountain peaks beyond the dead bodies of the poisonous people and murmured.

“Let's go. Our lord is waiting.”

“Our is waiting.”

“He is waiting.”

The Trident of Baskerville, no, the Trident of Vikir.

They were escorting Pomeranian and leading the Knights to the summit.

Of course, the road to the mountain peak was long and difficult.

With so many poisonous mutants rampaging like demons, even the strongest knights could not easily break through the walls of the siege.

...That was until the Seven Counts of House Baskerville stepped forward.

Six shadows stretched across the battlefield, which was entirely covered with dark red aurora.

The six counts, minus the long-vacant seat of Cane Corso, emerged from the mountain of corpses.

'Boston Terrier' Les Baskerville, leader of the Knights of the Pit Bull.

'Great Dane' Les Baskervilles, leader of the Knights of the Mastiff.

'Isabella' La Baskerville, leader of the Knights of the Doberman.

'German' Les Baskervilles, leader of the Knights of the Shepherds.

'Metzgerhund' Les Baskervilles, leader of the Knights of the Rottweiler.

'Cu-Chulainn' Les Baskervilles leader of the Knights of the Wolfhounds.

Having spent their entire lives on the battlefield, they quickly adapted to the war against the poisonous mutants.

Peopeopeopeopeopeopeog!

Boston Terrier beheaded a staggering number of poisonous soldiers in a long series of strikes.

Waves of blood rushed from the ground and showers of blood fell from the sky.

“Hehehe – I probably caught the most on this battlefield.”

However.

...Bang!

With a deafening bang, a gigantic, fleshy, poisonous mutant fell backwards.

Great Dane, who had punched a hole in the demon's huge head, walked out, wiping the blood from his knife with the hem of his clothes.

“What's the point of catching many? You have to catch the big one. I've probably caught the biggest one on this battlefield.”

“Bullshit! Catching a lot is the best!”

“Are anglers competing based on what they catch? Even if you catch just one, it's best to catch the big one.”

Just then.

Jjeoeog-

A black slash was drawn between the bickering Boston Terrier and Great Dane.

One of the poisonous mutants fell to the ground in half, and Isabella stepped forward.

Her path was streaked with blood.

At first glance, she had killed far more poisonous people than Boston Terrier.

Among the piles of bodies, there were often larger ones than Great Dane had killed.

“If you have time for bullshit, why don't you cut down one more?”

“....”

“....”

Boston Terrier and Great Dane grunted and averted their gaze.

It was always a losing proposition with that young, smart woman, whether they fought with swords or words.

The other Counts were pushing the poisonous peolpe to near pulp.

German, fiercely charging through the ranks as if he could not lose to Isabella, Metzgerhund, flashing his six teeth as if to prove that he was the best of the 6th Form, and Cu-Chulainn, 4th Form Master who unusually insists only on the 4th Form.

Each of them is unique and violent, and they tear apart the poisonous peolpe's siege with ferocity.

The Knights, following their leaders, charge through the center of the battlefield.

Soon, the senators of House Baskerville also appeared on the front lines.

Old men with bushy eyebrows and long beards, wear black iron armor, slicing and dicing the poisonous peolpe.

“Heoheoheo- Sade and Orca are out on the battlefield, shouldn't we be in the back room?”

“I'm sure they've aged a lot too, Why don't we see each other again after such a long time?.”

“Holholhol – it reminds me of the old days., these are the guys I ran into on a fictional day on the battlefield.”

“By the way, things must be pretty bad for them to drag us out, huh?”

“I was tired of being treated as a waste of the previous generation, so let's loosen the reins and run wild.”

“Yeah. I guess the head of the house will take care of everything~”

The entirety of the Baskerville family is in motion.

The Morgue, the Quovadis, and the Bourgeois were all racing across the battlefield with their armies.

Morgue head Raspane and her deputy, Adolf, were in attendance.

Pope Nabokov I of Quovadis, Cardinal Luther, and Archbishop Mozgus were also on the battlefield.

Bourgeois also poured all of the family's wealth into this battlefield, and even Damian, the acting head of the family, was at the forefront of the war.

“Advance to the water source!”

“Let's break through to Tochka!”

“Don't stop! Keep marching!”

The reinforcements were on their way to Tochka, as had been decided at the previous meeting of the Alliance Houses.

It was the result of the persuasion of Kirko, who had once led the Nouvelle Vague's elite into the meeting.

Kwakwakwakwakwang!

The red death spirits were all burned to death by the flame-type magic unleashed by Adolf the Mad Mage.

Beside him, the three sisters, Highsis, Middlesis, and Lowsis, were searching for Camus.

“Camus! Where are you!”

“We are working really hard!”

“Can't we talk about this after the war?”

Of course, there were other forces besides the four allied families.

The Verangian Boot Camp, the Magic Tower, the Themiscyra Women's College, and the Colosseo Academy.

Faculty members, led by Principal Banshee, also appeared on the battlefield.

“Hahahaha, finally settling a score!”

“Hmph, you filthy poisonous bastards.”

“Vikir-nim, I'm coming-oh!”

Young talents such as Bakilaga, Hohenheim, and Lovegood were also leading the student army and advancing.

Even.

“Pushishishi! What's this, we're going to be late for this fun feast!”

Even Tochka's counterattack force, led by Sade, had reached the peak.

A large army of Orca and Nouvelle Vague guards, prisoners, and refugee vigilantes were trampling the poisonous army relentlessly.

“Young master, we're here!”

“Boss! Where are you!”

“...No, why me too!?”

Chihuahua, MiniPin, and Cindywendy are also seen being included in the reinforcements.

“Did you come to see me?”

“Ew! What are you doing, everyone else is watching!”

Suddenly, Osiris swoops down like a bird of prey and embraces Cindywendy with a huge smile on his face.

...And there was a gaze looking down on it all from a mountain peak.

“....”

[....]

Vikir. And Flauros.

The Demon Hunter and the Demon King stood sharply opposite each other.

And behind Vikir stood Camus, Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko.

...Flash!

The 8th Form of Baskerville, the black sun rose high in the sky.

Surrounding it were scorching flames, iron skewers, powerful rain of arrows, divine protection, golden giants, and blood-sucking creatures.

“It's over.”

Vikir continued speaking with confidence.

“The demon kill.”

But faced with Vikir's declaration, Flauros was still not relaxed.

[Well. Is that so?]

“...?”

Vikir narrowed his eyes.

Flauros jumped back and soon stood on the ledge of the crater.

That was the place where Vikir launched a slash to clear the waterway before the battle began.

Peering into the deep furrow, Flauros smirked.

[You've come all this way and there's no water, aren't you disappointed, my friends?]

“It doesn't matter. If I can kill you here.”

[Hmm- no, we should at least have water, considering the refugees in Tochka].

Still frowning, Flauros waved his hand into the dark void.

And he held out his tightly clenched fist in front of Vikir.

[What do you think is in here?]

Vikir didn't enjoy talking to demons, and he didn't want to know what was in that fist.

But before Vikir could answer, Flauros opened his fist wide.

It was a nymph.

“...!”

Vikir's eyes widened, and Flauros chewed and swallowed the shivering nymph in one bite.

He smirked and opened his mouth to speak.

[Actually, if it's water, it is. A lot].

Flauros raised the spear he was holding high.

And he said one last thing.

[You should have dug a little deeper.]

A moment. An emotion flashed through Vikir's mind.

It was a sense of loss.

'Lying leopard'.

It was the nickname of the 2nd Corpse Flauros.

It is Flauros' habit and ability to tell plausible lies about everything.

Vikir hesitated. He couldn't predict what Flauros was after, or what his motives were.

And then, as Vikir had predicted, Flauros revealed something he had been hiding.

...Kwakwang!

The demon's spear struck the bottom of the cratered pit.

And then something incredible happened.

Kwalkwalkwalkwalkwalkwalkwalkwalkwalkwal-

A tremendous amount of water gushed out from the point of Flauros's spear.

MiniPin's information was not wrong. There was indeed a water source in the crater.

But when Camus, Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko saw the water gushing out, they couldn't help but wonder.

“What's going on? Why are you suddenly finding water sources?”

“...It's suspicious.”

“What are he planning on doing, handing over drinking water?”

“He's voluntarily giving us water in this situation?”

“I have a bad feeling about this.”

They couldn't fathom why the demon was so willing to give them water.

And in this situation.

“...!”

Vikir was the only one whose expression changed drastically.

Chapter 465

The Prelude to a Counterattack (3)

◆

“...!”

Vikir was the only one whose expression changed drastically.

Vikir had seen all of Flauros's malice in that split second when the water burst forth.

'Lying leopard'.

That's Flauros's nickname the 2nd Corpse.

It is his habit and skill to tell plausible lies at every turn.

He has the ability to make others believe his lies, and he is adept at deceiving others with various tricks.

...Peopeong!

The embankment collapsed and the underground water inside burst out.

Kwalkwalkwalkwalkwalkwalkwalkwalkwal-

A huge amount of water gushed toward the ground.

The water in the underground lake was clear and clean enough for the nymphs to live in.

So the absence of water at the source was a false proposition created by Flauros.

...The problem was that Flauros's spear was stuck right where the water flowed.

Shiririk.

Two snakes gaped at the stream.

The water grazed their razor-sharp fangs and instantly turned red.

Yes. As soon as Flauros opened the waterway, he was releasing a huge amount of plague poison into the water.

It was the same trick that had infested the Usher mansion.

“What! Water!”

“There was actually water here!”

“Oh my God, I thought I was going to burn my throat out!”

“But the color of the water is weird.”

“It's groundwater, maybe there was some dirt mixed in..”

The soldiers were delighted to see the water flowing down the slope.

They put their mouths to the pale reddish water and gulped it down.

...The reaction was immediate.

“Keoheug!?”

Those who drank or touched the water began to vomit and have seizures.

“Euag!! It's poison!”

“You've been turned into a poisonous man!”

“Don't drink the water!”

“Quickly bring the priests!”

The priests quickly applied their spells, and the soldiers didn't turn into poisonous people.

But the damage done by the massive drain on their holy power was irreversible.

“Don't drink the water!”

“Spread it backwards! They must not drink the water!”

“Don't even touch it!”

The soldiers spread the message to their comrades below.

But the water was going down much faster than the messages were spreading.

Also, many of the soldiers in the back of the line resisted the advice to not drink the water.

“What's going on, guys, why are you telling us not to drink water?”

“I don't know. Are they trying to keep it all to themselves?”

“All this water? Isn't it because you get diarrhea or something if you drink anything?”

“Kahahaha- I don't care about that, I have a strong stomach!”

There was great chaos in the rear troops.

People turning into the poisonous people, people writhing in pain, and priests wasting tons of holy power to heal them.

Watching all of this, Flauros burst out laughing.

[Ha-hahahaha! How's that, demon hunter, spectacular, huh?]

Flauros imbued the hand holding the spear with even stronger magic power.

The water began to turn a dark blood color.

The Original Ouroboros was producing a massive amount of poison even now.

The reason Flauros was able to spread the Red Death across the entire continent and create an enormous number of poisonous soldiers was probably thanks to the unique abilities of that spear, which was no different from his alter ego.

...Chiiiig!

Vikir drew upon Madame's poisonous blood and burned away all the plague poison that had entered his body.

At the very least, Madame's poison should be enough to suppress the red death.

However, it was impossible to stop all of the Red Death that was dissolved in such a huge amount of water.

The gravity of the situation began to dawn on everyone in the group.

The water from the source would surely flow down the hillside and reach Fort Tochka.

Refugees suffering from starvation due to insufficient drinking water will definitely drink this water in a hurry, and the result will be....

[I told you, I'll turn all the trash in Tochka into poisonous people. I'm a man of my word!]

Flauros laughed, his face contorted.

The turbulent waters rushing down the mountain valley were now stained red.

At this rate, even the Salvatio forces rushing toward the water source here would be swept away and drowned.

And the refugees left behind in Tochka, unaware, will drink the water and turn into poisonous people, too.

“....”

Vikir gritted his teeth at this horrifying realization.

He shouldn't have come to the source. He should never have left Tochka.

He should have stayed within the walls, locking the gates, even if it meant dying of thirst.

In the end, they had fallen for Flauros's trick, and they would all be poisoned.

Vikir quickly looked away.

Dolores was there, nodding her head with a determined expression.

“We must not give up until the end, for miracles only come to those who act!”

Dolores clasped her hands together and released all of her remaining holy power.

...Paas!

The white pillar of light she created cleansed the water around her.

But it wasn't enough. It would be impossible for Dolores to purify the entirety of this huge waterway with her power.

“...Ugh!”

Dolores' expression frowned.

Sweat poured down her face, and she felt like she might collapse at any moment.

Just then.

Tuck-

There was a hand on her shoulder.

Vikir. Night Hound rested on Dolores' shoulders and gave her strength.

“I'm sorry. I need a place to lean right now....”

Dolores's heart began to pound hard as she watched Vikir shake his head in disbelief.

The thing she had always hoped for had happened.

She would never forget the moment when the scarred hound, who never relied on others, rested his head on her shoulder for the first time.

'I can't let you down, Vikir!'

Dolores's eyes changed.

“Miracles are granted only to the first to reach out, and to those who believe and do, it shall surely happen!”

Dolores knocks on the door of limitation while reciting a prayer.

Her soul resonates, and a pillar of pure white light emanates from her.

And all the priests of Quovadis House, seeing the holy light she emits, begin to purify the waters with all their might.

Paaas!

Martin Luther unleashed a massive shield of holy defense, washing away the entire wave.

Mozgus and the rest of the elite priests of Quovadis followed Dolores' lead and stood in front of the red tide.

To their surprise, the color of the bursting wave cleared for a moment.

The red energy was slowly draining away.

However.

[Hahahahahaha- Are you fools?]

Flauros stood atop the rock, sneering at the priests who were trying to purify the waters.

[Holy power is not infinite, and how long do you think you can keep the poison at bay? It would be more efficient if you saved it and used it to escape.]

The demon's words were reasonable.

A huge amount of poisonous water flows through the mountain peaks.

Even if they could hold out for a while, the situation was already effectively over.

A wave of red death would soon wash over the reinforcements.

And, by extension, the countless refugees who have flocked to Tochka.

It seemed self-evident that the world would soon be filled with poisonous people infected with the Red Death.

But then.

...Kwakwang!

Vikir still hadn't given up as he formed eight teeth toward Flauros.

[Futile endeavor, demon hunter, for soon it will be a world of poisonous people down there, and no matter how vicious you try, your world is doomed... Hmm!?]

But the determination in Vikir's eyes was enough to shut Flauros' mouth.

“Your poison is certainly strong. Far beyond my expectations.”

[....]

“But at best, your poison has only defeated me, not this world.”

As he spoke, Vikir's eyes blazed with a terrifying light.

“Do not underestimate this world.”

Vikir pushed forward with all his might, his feet planted on the ground of the world he'd grown up in.

He put his entire weight on his big toe and ran so that the tip of his forehead was the farthest forward.

Black Sun. The eight strikes swung fiercely, tearing through Flauros's body.

Kwak-kwak!

But even as he looked at the fountain of blood gushing out from his body, Flauros laughed leisurely.

[Hahahaha- So what does this mean, the humans down there are already finished...!?]

Suddenly. Flauros' expression, distorted with ridicule, hardened.

The peaks came into view, a stream of water cascading down a series of tiers.

The waterfall at the base of the first peak is red.

The waterfall below the second peak is also red.

...?

The color of the waterfall at the bottom of the third peak is strange.

Transparent color. Clear water. Somehow, the water beneath it didn't carry any of the red death spirit.

“Uh, what?”

“What happened to the water in the area we missed?”

“Who purified that place?”

The priests who were purifying the water were also puzzled.

The soldiers at the bottom of the mountainside drink the flowing water and tilt their heads.

“What? Why did you tell us not to drink the water?”

“Hmm? It's fine, it's so clear and cool.”

“Ouch! Didn't the guys who went up first lie so they could drink all the water? There's so much!”

The soldiers were right.

The water that began to flow down the peak was crystal clear, even though it was untouched by holy power.

The water was flowing swiftly toward Fort Tochka in the distance.

[Uh, what's going on?]

Flauros stretched out his neck with a dumbfounded expression.

Only then did the view of the mountainside below come into focus.

Gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp.

There, a giant spider, the size of dozens of adult men combined, stood against the current, drinking water.

A spider with its head buried in the waves, sucking in huge amounts of water.

A radius of tens of meters of red death could be seen swirling around it, being sucked in.

“Wait a minute. Where have you seen a lot of spiders?”

“No way!”

“If it's a poison-eating spider....”

“Oh my God, that thing!”

“Are spiders on the ground supposed to be that big?”

The spider's performance was so impressive that Camus, Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko each had something to say.

Vikir's face lit up.

Baby Madam!

The one we lost so long ago had reappeared with a much larger body and more powerful poison!

But Flauros's momentum was not dead yet...

[What can a spider do, it's quite large for a spider, but that's all it is, a spider at best!]

Flauros shouted nervously.

He firmly believed that the appearance of a single spider would not turn the tide of the battle.

However.

Ppajig-

That steadfast attitude was shattered as the landscape beyond the spider began to reveal itself.

...Kung!

Another spider appeared.

This one was just as big as the original.

Crawling up beside the original big spider, it too began to suck up water and absorb the red death.

...Kung!

Another giant spider appeared next to it.

...Kung! ...kung! ...kung! ...kung! ...kung! ...kung! ...kung!

And again. And another. The spiders just keep coming.

The number of spiders was already beyond counting.

Moreover, the spiders that kept appearing were much bigger and fatter than the first ones.

Then.

Vikir's mind flashed back to the words that Cindywendy had said not long ago.

'Ah, speaking of Ballak, it seems that... has gained a new guardian recently. Apparently, They say it's quite a 'trusty friend'.'

Ballak's new guardian. A trusty friend.

'Now that I think about it, is it already time for it to get dark like this?'

The night that had fallen around them was unusually dark.

But when he looked up, the sun was still hanging at the end of the sky.

...So why is it so dark here?

[...!?]

Flauros jerked his head up.

There, he saw something huge, almost blocking out the sky.

At first glance, one might mistake it for the night sky.

Sssssssss...

The leaves of the nearby trees rustle in unison.

It was casting an even thicker shadow over the peaks here.

Extremely.

Slowly.

Absolutely.

No sound.

It was so close.

It's approaching without anyone knowing.

Stealthily.

...But with a clear purpose!

Chapter 468

The Prelude to a Counterattack (6)

◆

The nature of the Leviathan.

...Flash!

The entire basement brightened up.

The Spatial Traveling Magic Circle that occupied an enormous area had completely lost its effectiveness.

This magic circle, which allows one to travel over a very long distance in a single bound, is extremely costly and labor-intensive to construct, but its effectiveness is certain.

Flauros stood up in a state of complete disrepair.

His left arm and chest arm had been ripped off and torn away as he walked out of the circle of light.

[Damned demon hunter, biting and clawing until the very end...]

If he hadn't moved his heart to the right in the moment of crisis, he would have been in real danger.

Thousands of thoughts, one mistake (千慮一失). The moment of relief at the end might have cost him his life.

'Demons kill.'

The demon hunter's final growl was still echoing in his ears.

Flauros shuddered once.

Then he had to surprise himself at his body's reaction.

'...Am I shaking?'

Fear imprinted deeply on his subconscious.

Flauros shook his head, trying to clear his thoughts.

'That can't be, it's just the result of using up too much magic. I'm just tired.'

But he couldn't help the bitterness in his heart.

After all, in the end, he had been chased away by a mere mortal.

Flauros sank into a chair in the corner of the stone chamber.

He opened his bloodshot eyes and spoke.

[Once again, I'm sending all the poisonous soldiers to Tochka, and this time it will be nothing like the battle at the Water Source.]

Even if they were able to draw water from the source area, it would only prolong their lives by three days at most.

Tochka, which basically lacks drinking water, was not a good place to camp.

[The poison here is limitless. It's a fight we can't lose].

In other words, the demon hunters stuck in Tochka are still just flies.

All they had to do was bring in more troops and completely isolate them.

This was also a battle of pride.

A fight to restore the pride that had been torn away in the battle for the Water Source.

'I will not spare a single human being in Tochka.'

Flauros looked at the Original Ouroboros in his hand.

The two snakes that crawled out of the sack made of Hell Trees entered the jar again, biting each other's tails, spinning around and starting to create poisonous fog.

Infinite poison. Infinite poisonous people. There is no house or power that can stop Leviathan now.

The same was true even if it was a union of the remaining Houses.

'Soon, the First Crown Prince will become Emperor. In the civil war, in the race war, I will be the victor. And then it will be the right time for me to accomplish my great work.'

As Flauros pondered his future plans.

The black-robed man who had collapsed in the magic circle stirred to his feet.

Seeing him, Flauros smiled in the face of Hobbes.

[Well done, my heir. Thanks to you, I was able to grant the crown prince's request. It was fitting that you sowed the seeds of the Hell Tree at the end].

“....”

The Harvester stood still, unresponsive.

Flauros rubbed his hands together, assuming it was fatigue.

[Yes, you must be tired, go get some rest. We'll be busy mass-producing poisonous vials for a while, and as soon as you're strong enough, you can return to work].

“....”

[Then head to Tochka as soon as the Poisonous Man Legion is complete. It's time to end this once and for all, and soon our family will rule the world].

At Flauros's words, the Harvester merely bowed his head deeply.

◆

The Harvester removed the black hood that covered his face.

There was pale skin, deep dark circles, and the face of a young man whose youthful appearance had not gone away despite the passage of time.

Granola.

He sank back into the couch with a deep sigh.

His life had certainly been a solid one, from entering the Colosseo Academy, the best university in the empire, as the third son of Leviathan, and returned to his family after earning the honor of graduating early as the valedictorian. Rising to the rank of Captain of the 'Comprachicos', the core force of Leviathan's essence and one of the most powerful legions of poisonous mutants.

...But.

Even though he had succeeded in achieving the title he had so desperately sought, a position that earned him the recognition and respect of everyone in his family, and a life that was far more successful than his snooty, arrogant brothers, he couldn't help but feel a bit empty.

Since when?

...When he watched his uncle, whom he had known since childhood, a man who was always kind to him even if he was always eccentric, slowly lose his mind after he started experimenting with drugs?

...Or when he watched his classmates die in Hell Tree?

...When being put in a position where he was forced to look on in silence as countless people turned to poisonous people?

In the midst of this chain of thoughts, a voice suddenly echoed in Granola's head.

'I don't think you're a bad person, we were friends...'

Pigi. A blurry face, nothing special about him, but for some reason he stuck in Granola's memory.

As Pigi last words replayed in his mind, his hands, which had never trembled in all the years he'd killed so many people, began to shake violently.

The voice of a friend from long ago echoes in his ears.

'Why are you being so nice to me?'

'...Well, because we're friends.'

Granola bit his lip.

“Vikir.”

Granola couldn't quite define what he felt when they reunited.

What he could say with certainty was that the gleam in his eyes, unwavering to the end, was the same.

He always had a reason for everything he did.

Vikir was someone he couldn't help but look up to, someone he couldn't help but follow and admire, someone he always wanted to chase and surpass, but couldn't even reach in the end.

He crossed unimaginably harsh lines of fire, and now he stands here, holding himself back.

He had always had a belief and a reason for his actions, and this time would be no different.

Granola groaned in a low voice.

The question he'd been pushing to the back of his mind had come to the forefront of his thoughts.

'Am I living my life right now?'

To produce poisonous soldiers to wipe out the opposition and make the First Prince Emperor.

To unify the empire in the truest sense of the word, uniting seven fragmented powers into one.

Dalgeulag-

Suddenly, Granola felt a foreign object on his left breastbone.

A necklace. A small brooch in the shape of lips.

It's something he's worn around his neck for years, but never paid much attention to.

But today, it caught his attention unusually.

“ ... 'Straight Lips'.”

An artifact she received as a prize in the University League when he was a rookie.

In fact, his current ranking wouldn't have been possible if it weren't for Vikir.

“I used to feel bad that I got a useless artifact while everyone else got a good one.”

An artifact that tells you the truth, no matter what the question, only once, yes or no.

The artifact was made from the lips of a sage who lived long ago and could only be asked once by a single person.

The cooldown time is about a hundred years. It's practically an artifact made just for Granola.

“....”

Granola stared at the dry lips.

Come to think of it. He remembers a conversation he had with a classmate when he first got this artifact.

'I'm the only one who does this.'

'Why, I think it's a very nice artifact. I sometimes have a lot of doubts about my life. It would be nice if I could ask you about it.'

'...Tsk, why do you have such doubts? I'm always doing well, you should be proud of yourself!'

Sinclaire. The words of the woman he once admired, smiling brightly, suddenly popped out of Granola's old memories.

“...The straight lips.”

Granola's mind raced through a series of events.

The inferiority complex of being overshadowed by his older brothers, the pressure to live up to the family's expectations, the tragedy of his Uncle Sakkuth, his only escape, the geniuses of the other families he met at the Academy, the small friendships that blossomed in the ranks, his rapid rise through the ranks of the main family, his appointment as a captain in charge of countless poisonous soldiers, and the task of turning countless others into poisonous people, and then war... and war....

Granola looked up.

A black cloak hung on a rack, and a massive scythe leaned at an angle.

Granola reached out, wrapped the cloak around himself, and picked up the scythe.

Granola turned his head and peered into the darkness beyond.

Inside countless cages, he could see poisonous people scraping at the bars with their teeth and nails.

Beings who had once been human, rendered irrational by drugs and abuse and programmed to hate everything in this world.

Granola turned his head.

He lifted his hand and placed it on his left chest.

“..., My father said. They are evil, we are good, and we, the Leviathans, will become the greatest house, and by extension, the prophets who will revive humanity. They are small sacrifices for that day, and after death, they will be saved by God and enjoy glory and power forever as heroes who stood at the forefront of the crusade.”

His mind races with thoughts.

His father's words, his uncle's last appearance, his classmates reunited on the battlefield after graduation....

Finally, Granola opened his eyes as if making a judgment.

After thinking about it three times, he finally put his hand on his left chest and asked.

“Am I right in the judgment I am about to make?”

Immediately, a small light emanated from Granola's left chest.

...Dalssag!

The Straight Lips were trying to give a proper answer.

Chapter 469

Tochka Annihilation Battle (1)

◆

The drinking water has run out.

There was a sense of urgency in the Tochka Fortress.

Cindywendy, who had unfolded the map, spoke with a serious expression.

“We succeeded in drawing water from the water source and were able to hold out for three more days, but it's really impossible now.”

Although the influx of refugees has slowed considerably since the siege of the water source, the number of people already inside the fort is staggering.

It's no wonder that Cindywendy, who was responsible for providing food and water to their mouths, to feel sick.

Meanwhile, Osiris, sitting next to her, was just as grave as she was.

“The Leviathans have come with a plan this time. They've got a whole bunch of poisonous people in the rock formation below the peak. More than three times as many as this side.”

Although Tochka Fortress is an iron fortress that is advantageous to water defenses, it only works in battles between a small number of people and when both sides have large troops, the story is different.

Cindywendy and Osiris spoke in serious tones.

“We're running out of water anyway, so tomorrow's battle will be the limit, and we'll have to settle for that.”

“All-out war, then. There's no other option. With the numbers we have, there will be local battles, large and small, outside of Fort Tochka. The good thing about our misfortune is that we have many excellent commanders on this side.”

The elite troops have been assembled, led by outstanding commanders such as Orca and Sade, as well as the generals and warlords of their respective houses.

Although it was hopeless, it was a good idea to try to break through head-on.

“What do you want to do, little brother?”

Osiris looked up and saw Vikir standing there.

“....”

Vikir didn't answer for a while.

He just stared out the window, counting the stars in the night sky.

“Is it starry night? Please come up with some kind of solution. You're the one who said we just have to stay here!”

Cindywendy exclaimed.

Even Osiris, who would normally have stopped her, was showing a rare impatience tonight.

It was only natural, given the circumstances.

Right then.

Hwiiiing-

A gust of night air blew in through the open window.

“What?”

“What kind of wind....”

Cindywendy and Osiris covered their faces with their hands.

It's natural for a breeze like this to come in when the window is open.

However.

“...!”

Vikir's expression changed drastically.

Vikir lightly moistened his index finger with saliva and held it upright.

“...Southeast wind.”

Vikir opened all the windows in different directions and checked the wind direction at the same time.

Vikir then returned to the southeast window, where he had always spent his time standing still.

He began to look at the constellations hanging in the corner of the night sky.

“One... two... three... four... five... six... seven....”

The seven stars are commonly referred to as guiding stars. It's a special constellation that can only be seen from a specific direction and has been a guide to many people since ancient times.

Hwiiiing-

Once again, the night wind blows. This time from the southeast.

Suddenly, Cindywendy and Osiris noticed something strange.

'...Come to think of it, has the wind ever come in from this window before?'

It seemed that there had never been a breeze from this window, where Vikir had always stayed.

After realizing this trivial fact, an unexpected feeling of excitement rose in the hearts of Cindywendy and Osiris.

“One... two... three... four... five... six... seven....”

Vikir continued to count the stars.

The fact that there are seven guiding stars in the northern night sky is no secret, even to the young shepherds who live around here.

...But.

“One... two... three... four... five... six... seven....”

Vikir's third count of the stars was a little different.

“...Eight.”

The far end of the guide star. There was a single star shining blue.

The light of the eighth star, the one that had formed after the seven guiding stars, pierced Vikir's retinas and shone brightly.

Vikir, who had been counting the stars in silence, finally nodded.

“Good, that's one more. It has settled down for sure.”

“...?”

Vikir's unclear words left Cindywendy and Osiris scratching their heads.

Soon, Vikir, who had remained silent despite everyone's encouragement and criticism, made his move.

“Tomorrow at noon will be the final battle.”

It seemed like a sudden declaration, but Cindywendy and Osiris could feel it.

That tomorrow's battle would be the stage that Vikir had been planning and designing for so long, the true conclusion.

◆

Twelve o'clock in the blazing noon sun.

The legions of poisonous soldiers besieging Tochka have begun to move.

Major General Orca's face was as grim as ever as he prepared for the final defensive battle.

With every last drop of drinking water gone, there is no longer any hope for tomorrow.

“I'm not even sure if we'll make it to midnight tonight.”

“Pushishishi- There is no reason for an old man who has lived well to struggle to survive for just 12 more hours.”

Marquis de Sade scowls from beside Major General Orca.

But unlike the corners of his mouth, which always curled upward, his eyes were not smiling.

“Pushishishi– there are no more troops and no more water. It's truly an extreme situation. It's been a long time since I've had a battle like this. Was it about 50 years ago? Ever since the fight with the Baskerville dogs at Salt Desert...”

“Shut up, escaped prisoner. I'm not even remotely curious about your saga, so go talk somewhere else.”

“Eih- this could be the last time, and you still being rude.”

Marquis de Sade pouted and shut up.

The two of them sat far away from each other on the castle pedestal and were silent for a long time.

Finally, Orca spoke first.

“...Die without shame.”

“Huh?”

Sade frowned in confusion, and Orca spoke again.

“I hate to admit it, but you're of the same generation as me. Aside from me, you're the only one still on active duty.”

“So?”

“Whether you like it or not, you and I have come to represent our generation. Let's not end it ugly.”

“Pushishishi– take care of yourself, old man.”

“...Escaped prisoner.. At best, your advice was given in good faith.”

The two bad friends didn't look at each other until the end.

They just stared off into the distance, at the poisonous clouds that were turning the horizon black.

Then the army split in two, with Orca and Sade leading the way.

Orca to defend and Sade to counterattack.

The House of Morgue and the House of Quovadis, specialized in defense, guarded the outer castle of Tochka under Orca's command, while the House of Baskerville and House of Bourgeois, specialized in attack, caught the enemy off guard under the command of Sade.

O-ooooo!

The giant poisonous soldiers began to surge toward the walls.

“...!”

Orca's brow twitched.

The poisonous soldiers that were now coming to the forefront were all dressed in familiar attire.

The black blood-like robe of the iron-blooded swordsman Baskerville, the red robe of the mage Morgue, the white priestly robe of the religious hymn Quovadis, and the golden cloak of the rich Bourgeois.

These clothes, all dry and tattered, clearly took the form of 'shrouds.'

“ ... The family tombs of each family were stolen.”

The ancestors of the Baskervilles, the Morgue, the Quovadis, and the Bourgeois.

Their corpses were being processed into poisonous soldiers, the dead soldiers of the dead.

It was a moment of revelation, of the grave robbing that had once raged across the Empire.

Ku-gugugugugu...

The swordsmen of Baskerville stood at the forefront, stripped to bone, leather, and poison.

Facing them, the spiders of the Jungle stood on Tochka's ramparts, their fur bristling.

Madame Hatchling glanced over.

There, a separate unit was seen moving independently without receiving instructions from Sade.

Vikir. The person in charge of operating the separate unit.

“....”

Vikir was quietly watching the poisonous dead soldiers appearing at the front line in the distance.

Rather, what was growling with the will to go on a rampage was the detachment standing behind it, and the seven hunting dogs that commanded that detachment.

'Boston Terrier' Les Baskerville, leader of the Knights of the Pit Bull.

'Great Dane' Les Baskervilles, leader of the Knights of the Mastiff.

'Isabella' La Baskerville, leader of the Knights of the Doberman.

'German' Les Baskervilles, leader of the Knights of the Shepherds.

'Metzgerhund' Les Baskervilles, leader of the Knights of the Rottweiler.

'Cu-Chulainn' Les Baskervilles leader of the Knights of the Wolfhounds.

They stood still in the back, waiting for Vikir's instructions.

Except for the two who had been arguing loudly earlier.

“Killing a lot is best.”

“Big kills are the best?”

Boston Terrier, the leader of the Pit Bull, and the Great Dane, the leader of the Mastiff, had been at loggerheads since earlier.

And Isabella, the leader of the Doberman Knights, who was looking at the two with a pitiful gaze, walked between the two and whispered to Vikir.

“Turning the bodies of our ancestors into the undead is counterproductive. If anything, it increases our combat power by raising their anger. This will increase our short-term firepower.”

Isabella's judgment was cold and accurate.

Even German, the leader of the Shepherd, made the rare move of nodding in agreement with his rival.

“I think so, too. A prolonged battle would certainly be demoralizing, but we've run out of water anyway. A burning thirst will be quenched by a rage that burns hotter than that.”

Meanwhile, Metzgerhund, the leader of the Rottweiler Knights, turned his head as if to say that he didn't care.

Instead, his gaze remained fixed on Vikir.

“Nephew, I've heard your 6th Form is quite impressive, but I won't ask how you acquired such skill. I just want to see what you're capable of.”

“So am I. The 4th Form is my favorite sword technique. If you say that you don't have a sense as a master... You're lying!”

Cu-Chulainn, the leader of the Wolfhound Knights, had his gaze fixed on Vikir from earlier.

Since they are experts who would be disappointed to be second in the 6th and 4th Form, respectively, they seemed to want to use this opportunity to compare their skills with Vikir.

The tense muscles swell to the point of bursting, and the tendons flutter violently.

Like a rubber band pulled taut, the hounds are ready to spring at any moment.

In the midst of all this.

Vikir pulled something out of his bosom.

It was a red whistle. It was the symbol of the Baskervilles' military power.

...! ...! ...!

The piercing sound of the whistle echoed through the dry air.

Kwakwang!

The Baskervilles' numerous fighting dogs pawed the ground and shot forward.

Black shadows running in the sand dust. It is a very different production from the wind blowing in the barley field.

The final battle was now beginning.

Chapter 470

Tochka Annihilation Battle (2)

◆

Black shadows rise from the dust.

The hounds of Baskerville sprint like the wind that shakes the ears of barley.

And standing in their way are the hounds of a previous generation.

Cheolkeodeog... jeolgeuleog... deolgeuleog...

The swordsmen of the Baskerville family, with only their skeletons and skins remaining, walk towards them with their shrouds waving.

With each step they take, the clatter of rusted metal, knocked-out teeth, and jawbones clash.

Chaang-!

The famous swords of the previous generation revealed their teeth that had turned into saw blades.

Isabella, German, Boston Terrier, Great Dane, Cu-Chulainn, and Metzgerhund stood against him. The six Knights Commanders also drew their respective weapons.

The Count of Boston Terrier, sword drawn, was the first to leap to the front of the display.

The Count of Great Dane was next.

“Hahahahaha, old dogs with missing teeth, where are you pretending to be active duty?”

“ ... Look. These are our ancestors.”

“Yeah, well, if you're tired, just lie down quietly and wait and then eat the ancestral rites!”

The two clash fiercely with the Baskervilles' dead soldiers wearing shrouds.

The wide slash characteristic of Boston Terrier was attacking many dead soldiers at once.

The violent, storm-like slashes were irregular and chaotic, but they were just as destructive.

In contrast, Great Dane slash is thin but dense.

A large, gargantuan dead soldier charged forward, relying solely on his size, only to be sliced in half by the enormous weight of Great Dane's slash.

Isabella and German then jumped into the fray.

“Why don't you go over there instead of coming over to me?”

“Hmph, you're just going to take all the credit for your achievements?”

“...There is such a difference in military strength, so where is the monopoly?”

These two people have often been told that men and women seem to have reversed.

German began to catch up with Isabella, showing both a sense of rivalry and a sense of victimization.

Isabella, characteristically efficient and cost-effective, began shifting the trajectory of her sword as if she were setting down a checkerboard.

With minimal movement and aura, dozens of dead soldiers had already fallen.

German was also displaying a sword skill that was not far behind Isabella's.

With a strength comparable to hundreds of poisonous soldiers, the poisonous dead soldiers were collapsing like scarecrows.

Meanwhile, Metzgerhund and Cu-Chulainn were closely following Vikir, the leader of the detachment, on both sides as if they were guarding him.

“6th! Let's go for 6th Form!”

“4th Form! Compete with 4th Form!”

Both of them were proud of their swordsmanship, to the point of arrogance.

However, since the level of extreme intention has been reached, such level of mastery is to be expected.

Hwilililig- kwagig!

Feeling the stinging gaze on his back, Vikir unfolded the 6th Form without a care in the world.

The 6 teeth pierce through the poisonous dead soldiers without a second thought.

Vikir's 6th Form, honed over the years in the Hell Tree, had certainly become a formidable skill.

Peopeopeopeog!

Of course, so was the 4th Form.

The 4 teeth he had honed so fiercely in his last life had paid off in this one.

The four teeth stretched out as naturally as if he were just breathing, shredding the dead soldiers in front of him.

“...Ooh!”

“...Indeed!”

Metzgerhund and Cu-Chulainn watched in admiration as Vikir spat out 4th and 6th Form almost simultaneously.

Of course, the more this happened, the more their competitive spirit was inflamed.

Kwa-jijijijijig!

Metzgerhund's carnivorous appetite and Cu-Chulainn's voracious appetite were like a meat grinding mill, crushing the poisonous soldier defenses.

Behind the Seven Counts, who are breaking through the most fiercely contested front lines as if they were in no man's land, the hounds of Baskerville are steadily closing the distance.

And at the forefront of it all was Vikir.

Peopeopeopeog!

Vikir raises his magic sword, Beelzebub, and a dozen heads rain down from the sky.

Hwiiing-

A humid southeastern wind from afar swept away the bitter blood incense.

Just then, as Vikir was leading his detachment through the front lines, something came into view in the distance.

“...!”

Skinny giant bodies emerging through red fog and dust.

O-oooooh...

It was a unit of tall, poisonous soldiers over a dozen meters tall.

Their muscles and skeletons deteriorated from their obsession with height, but their grotesquely elongated arms could reach over the walls of Tochka when stretched out.

They walked slowly from beyond the lines, exhaling a red mist of death from the sweat pores of their bodies.

They were probably specially designed to attack Tochka's high walls.

'...If we let those things get close to the walls, it'll be a headache for the defense.'

I'm sure Major General Orca will take care of it, but it would be best to minimize the burden on Tochka's own nature.

There are refugees there to protect.

'Fortunately, their poorly constructed skeletons will slow their approach. We'd better cut them down before they reach the walls.

Vikir made a quick judgment call.

“Let's hit those giants over there first!”

“Yes!”

The seven counts sheathed their swords and turned on their heels at Vikir's command.

The seven hundred knights following them did the same.

Vikir had just crossed the battlefield at the head of a small army.

But then, he heard a cackling laugh from the side.

“Pushishishi- where are you running so hard? I envy your youth.”

Vikir turned his head to see an old man standing on a tall outcropping of rock off to the side.

Marquis de Sade, he appeared like a ghost, without warning.

Behind him were the Nouvelle Vague all-stars: D'Ordume, Souaré, BDISSEM, Flubber, and Kirko.

Even the demonized Sadi.

Vikir asked in a tone of disbelief.

“...What's the combination, are you under arrest or something?”

“Pushishishi- no joke. I borrowed it from the old man, Orca. It's better in small numbers to strike back.”

Marquis de Sade laughs as if it's no big deal, even as he berates the wardens who once imprisoned him.

Behind him, of course, D'Ordume and Souaré's expressions are utterly rotten.

Especially the expression of Souaré, who was in charge of the solitary confinement cell where Marquis de Sade was being held, was quite something to behold.

Marquis de Sade asked.

“Anyway, were you on your way to the walls?”

“Yes. It's going to be a pain in the ass if those big things get stuck on the walls.”

“Pushishishi – you're quick to judge, and accurate.”

Marquis de Sade and Vikir, both masters of tactics, were right on the spot.

Just as he was about to turn away, Marquis de Sade's gaze fell upon the six men and women standing behind Vikir.

“Hoo – I wonder where all this young life comes from. Are you the new Seven Counts of House Baskerville?”

The six men and women's brow furrowed in unison at the word 'young'.

Boston Terrier, Great Dane, Isabella, German Shepherd, Metzgerhund, and Cu-Chulainn all turned toward Marquis de Sade, their sharp killing intent spraying in a show of dominance.

“Ugh, aren't you a little old for the battlefield, old man? I think you're closer to the dead soldiers standing there than we are.”

“Hey, no disrespect to the old man, I'm sure he's got a lot of courage coming out of the back room.”

“There's nothing to discuss with you, you're labeled a top-class war criminal by the Empire, and we'll put you back in the buns when the civil war is over.”

“It's disgusting how prisoners launder their image. Consider yourself lucky, old man.”

“Marquis de Sade, the old monster. A perfect opponent to test my newfound advanced form of carnivory.”

“...A powerhouse. I want to fight him.”

Marquis de Sade smirked as he watched the seven counts posture for battle.

“The older the puppies are, the more they bark. There is no particular character in this generation's Baskervilles. Except for that old man, Cane Corso.......”

Just then.

Peopeopeopeopeong!

A loud boom erupted from the walls.

“...!”

Vikir and Marquis de Sade, who were approaching the wall, stopped in their tracks at the same time.

One after another, the tall poisonous soldiers who had just reached for the castle gates collapsed.

Below them, a dark storm was blowing in, severing their ankles.

“Hmmm – there's someone quite useful over there, who is it?”

Marquis de Sade is interested.

The troops guarding the lower part of the castle walls, cutting off the ankles of the poisonous soldiers, soon began to approach.

Eventually, the being standing at the forefront of the black wind appeared in front of Vikir.

“We heard the red whistle, but we were still a little late in gathering. I don't want to use my age as an excuse, but this is getting old...But.”

At the sound of his voice, Vikir couldn't help but look surprised.

The immaculately pressed suit, the handsome mustache, and the polite greeting.

“...Really. You've really grown up, Master.”

Deacon John Barrymore was there.

Chapter 471

Tochka Annihilation Battle (3)

◆

The battle becomes increasingly fierce.

The hands of the clock that held Tochka's fate slowly descended, pointing to four in the afternoon.

Jjeoeog-

A giant poisonous soldier is cut in half.

Deacon Barrymore, who saw the Marquis de Sade whipping the whip and shaking off the blood, clapped his hands and said.

“You still do great work.”

“Pushishishi- still? Do you remember my old skills?”

“To be honest, I've seen more of it in books and papers than with the naked eye, but it's still more than recorded.”

John Barrymore, loyal to House Baskerville for four generations, said as he sliced through a number of poisonous soldiers with the sword in his hand.

“It's strange.”

“What do you mean?”

“What I mean is that right now I, no, all of us gathered here-are now under your command. It is amazing that people who once fought over the fate of the empire are now joining hands.”

Deacon Barrymore was answering Marquis de Sade's questions while knocking down poisonous soldier one after another with an undisturbed attitude.

Vikir, meanwhile, watched, his mouth slightly agape.

“I didn't realize that the butler had such great sword skills.”

“Hehehehe- I've always been good at dogfighting. When I was younger, I often fought with the patriarch, though I had a slightly better chance of winning back then.”

In fact, he'd once heard the elders of Baskerville say of Barrymore, in passing, 'That bastard became a man back then'.

'Is it a case of getting older and milder?'

It's hard to imagine that now, looking at his bushy mustache.

Vikir thought as he sliced open the head of the giant poisonous man in front of him like a watermelon.

Meanwhile, Barrymore's eyes were filled with admiration.

“You have indeed grown up, Master. I still remember that day when you was choosing chocolate from the food warehouse... I'm sure the patriarch will be pleased.”

“....”

At the mention of patriarch, Vikir turned his head in silence.

Where is Hugo now that the full force of the Baskervilles is here?

Then, catching Vikir's gaze, Barrymore smiled casually.

“My lord has gathered all of his regular troops and is heading straight this way. He's a bit late since he's on his way through the Civil War, so he's a bit slower than the other troops who took a detour....”

Then.

Kwakwakwakwang!

A loud explosion erupted that obscured the conversation between Vikir and Deacon Barrymore.

A poisonous man tore in an odd direction, and irritated voices clashed on both sides.

“How dare you stab me, you lunatic!”

Sadi. She screamed sharply, demonized by Belial's eyeballs.

And in the direction her axe-eyes squinted, she could see another woman standing.

“Ah, I'm sorry. I didn't realize you were human, not with all that demonic energy spewing out of you. Watch out for the blind sword.”

Isabella La Baskerville is the woman offering Sadi an apology that isn't really an apology.

The leader of the Doberman knights of the Baskerville family, she struck again, cutting down the poisonous soldiers.

It was an inconsiderate slash, despite the fact that Sadi was right next to her.

Sadi ducked her head to avoid Isabella's sword and growled through sharp teeth.

“Ohora-you're still a bitch, you vile bitch, trying to get rid of me with a blind stab.”

“Then you're still a wretch, too, though I suppose that's to be expected from a traitor's blood.”

“Hohoho – why would you recommend such a traitorous bloodline to the Imperial Captive, let alone as your successor?”

“It is the regret of a lifetime that I allowed a person like you to take over. A stain.”

Isabella seemed to be trying to wipe away a stain on her life in the midst of a battle.

Sadi, of course, was just as eager to kill her former superior.

Just then.

...Pow!

A rock spear suddenly protruded from the ground, separating Sadi and Isabella.

The poisonous soldier thrown to the sky and was nailed in the air without even touching the ground.

A mocking voice mocked them as they retreated, each losing a few strands of hair.

“What a waste. I wish you were both dead.”

Where Sadi and Isabella's gazes turned, Souaré stood.

The three women's gazes met in one place.

“Hohoho – what kind of Themiscyra Women's College reunion is this? Three of our classmates have gathered, haven't we?”

“Classmates? You trash bitches, don't you dare mention my alma mater's name.”

“It's good to see my old dorm roommates after all these years. Life in the deep sea was so lonely that I didn't like it.”

Sadi, Isabella, and Souaré.

Three classmates who graduated with honors from Themiscyra Women College and went their separate ways.

One became an empire-shaking villain, the other became a countess who supported the great family, and the last one became a symbol of protecting the worst prison.

...But.

These three people, who thought they'd never see each other again after their paths diverged, are now in the same place, doing the same thing.

It is the struggle to survive.

Jjeoeog-

One by one, the giant poisonous soldiers collapsed, and smaller poisonous soldiers took their place.

As the bodies pile up, the ground rises, and the Red Death grows ever more powerful.

The hour hand now points to 6, and the poisonous soldiers are even more numerous.

Or maybe it just seems that way because they have fewer allies.

“....”

Vikir was still at the forefront, silently slashing at the poisonous soldiers.

There was no telling how long the priests' blessing would last.

Just then.

Vikir spotted a familiar face not far away.

An elderly Baskerville. They had met a few times before and after the regression.

The hound was the same age as his master, Hugo.

'Was his name Pavlov?'

He remembered, as he was one of the more long-lived of those with the same middle name.

Pavlov Van Baskerville.

He struck down the poisonous soldiers with a sword whose teeth had been chipped away and turned into saw blades.

Kwazik-.

The sword, wielded like a sharpened blunt instrument, dented the poisonous soldier's head rather than severed it.

Doesn't he even have a handful of mana left for his aura now?

Vikir was just about to move to help Pavlov.

...Peoeog!

A spear from the front pierced Pavlov's abdomen.

“Hey!”

Vikir rushed forward and supported Pavlov's limp head.

“Don't lose your grip!”

Vikir shouts urgently, but Pavlov just stares at him.

Then, his mouth curves into an arc.

“You're a good man, you are.”

“....”

“But that's okay. I go about my business, you do yours.”

With that, Pavlov took one last deep breath.

He exhaled with all the force he could muster.

“High-ranking Leviathan appears on the front lines!”

It was a loud cry that reached the ears of everyone on the battlefield.

“...!”

All eyes, including Vikir's, turned to the front.

Up ahead, the fog was red, thicker than any other.

And the figure emerging from the fog was one Vikir recognized.

2nd Corpse, Flauros. Also known as the 'lying leopard'.

Its left hand had grown grotesquely long, and it smirked down at Vikir.

It was obvious that this was the same evil beast that had thrown the spear at Pavlov a moment ago.

[You are finished].

Leading a vast army of poisonous man, Flauros looked past Vikir to the walls of Tochka beyond.

[It's a miracle you've lasted this long without a sip of water. But no matter how much you whine at God, the limits are clear. Now the moment has come to realize reality, bugs.]

Perhaps if it weren't for that last demeaning remark, there might have been quite a few humans sympathizing with Flauros.

Suddenly, a staggering number of poisonous soldiers began to push through the lines.

“Fall back! Fall back, everyone! Get inside the castle and lock the doors!”

Marquis de Sade shouts in an unusually urgent tone.

Major General Orca, guarding the walls, gritted his teeth.

And then.

Peopeopeopeong!

An army of giant poisonous soldiers began to hang down, holding on to the castle.

The smaller poisonous soldiers were crawling on the backs of the larger ones, climbing up the walls.

“Douse them with oil! Light the fires! Pour out all the gunpowder you have! Archers and stokers, hit all the stocks! There is no point in saving anything!”

Orca and Sade's orders were met.

Everyone in Tochka blocked the approaching army of poisonous soldiers.

...But it was not enough.

The poisonous soldiers scaled the walls by the dozen, their corpses forming a massive formation.

The wall was now a gently sloping climb.

“...It's over.”

Cindywendy muttered in a cracked voice as she watched the whole scene from the watchtower.

She hadn't had a sip of water in several days, and she was beginning to feel defeated.

Of course, it was also something that everyone on the front lines was feeling more and more clearly and tangibly.

Peoeog!

Tudor staggered back, red blood gushing from his forehead.

Now the saint's tears were losing their power.

The banners that had flown everywhere had long since been torn to shreds.

The faces of the knights are darkened.

The priests, too, have begun to weep instead of chant.

The poisonous soldier heads were sticking out one by one in front of the castle wall, which was overflowing with evil spirits and the Red Death.

“...Is this really the end?”

Even the most glorious and colorful epic must come to an end.

Tudor smirked through blurred vision.

The thought crossed his mind that the end of his life wouldn't be so bad after all the black and red.

...That was it.

Ttag!

A small noise pierced Tudor's ears.

It was heard as clearly as a miracle even amidst all the explosions and tearing noises.

Tta-ag!

The noise is heard again.

It was the sound of small rocks flying.

It flew out of thin air and struck the poisonous soldier in the forehead as it stuck its head out of the city wall.

“...?”

Tudor turned his head.

Then he squinted his eyes, which refused to open.

Badeulbadeul...

There was a girl, her whole body trembling like a withered tree, but she wasn't backing down at all.

Tudor remembered her face and her name.

-'My name is Sammua! Can you tell me the name of the benefactor?'

-'My name is Tudor. No last name.'

The girl he'd saved from a small country town he'd stopped in one day.

'Shammua', a common name that means 'God has heard'.

Now she was standing on the city walls, throwing stones at the poisonous people.

“Tudor-nim, I will help too!”

Tudor's eyes widened at the girl's cry.

Bianca sarcastically sat next to him.

“When did you flirt?”

“You think so! It's dangerous, we need to get her to back off... Huh!?”

But Tudor couldn't put his words into action.

He couldn't turn his words into action, because he was faced with the solemn expressions of the family members who appeared behind the girl.

And behind the family was an entire village.

And behind them, all the refugees who had flocked to Tochka stood with indignant faces.

“Let us fight too!”

“We can't just stay under protection!”

“One man can do his share!”

“I'm a veteran after all!”

“I will repay you for sharing food and water!”

“Protect the Night Walkers!”

All the refugees who had been inside Tochka up to this point began to pour out.

The men picked up their heads, long spears, and whatever rocks they could find.

Women nursed the wounded and fetched the drinking water they had saved despite extreme starvation.

Tochka, an iron fortress, is structured so that one girl can defend against 100 soldiers.

The poisonous soldier, who thought they might have climbed over the castle wall, began to fall again due to the shower of raindrops and slings.

“...! ...! ...!”

Some light returned to Cindywendy's eyes, who was in charge of all supply and procurement on the watchtower.

The embers of a fire that had been thought to be completely extinguished had been reignited.

It was the beginning of a counterattack that no one had expected.

Chapter 472

Tochka Annihilation Battle (4)

◆

It only takes one man to throw a single stone.

A large number of people climbed the walls of Tochka and began to throw stones as hard as they could.

Tochka is a fortress built on a rocky area. The thing rolling around in the ground is a stone.

An enormous number of stones.

Tired of fleeing the harsh wheels of fate, tattered by hard lives and accumulated abandonment, their anger accelerates down the high walls of Tochka Fortress.

Hududug- hududug- hududug- hududug-

Needless to say, the destructive force was immense.

Peopeopeopeopeopeopeopeog!

The poisonous soldiers climbing the walls tumbled down, their heads cracked and exploded.

The shower of falling rocks, as powerful as the hail from Andrealphus, was slowing the poisonous soldiers' general assault.

“Now! Tighten up left and right!”

Marquis de Sade and Orca realized that this was their last chance to counterattack, a chance that would not come again.

Soon, the two veterans led their last remaining troops out and began pressing the poisonous soldiers on the left and right flanks, where the falling rocks could not reach them.

Vikir, too, was leading a small army to corner the poisonous soldiers.

The battle was fiercer than any battlefield they had ever seen.

It was the bloodiest battle before and after the Regression.

Peoeog-

Vikir thought to himself as he blew the head off a giant poisonous soldier that stood in his way.

'...We must seize the momentum and take the demon's head.'

It was the only way to end the war.

Vikir led the Seven Counts and the Seven Knights through the countless streams of the poisonous soldiers.

Poisonous blood flowers bloomed all along the front lines where the hounds dug deep, and countless heads rolled in the dust.

...Kwakwang!

The poisonous soldiers grab the ground with their giant palms and tear it apart.

Vikir ducks to the side, out of the way of the poisonous soldier palm that falls directly in front of him.

Thwack!

The poisonous soldier's chest split in two, releasing a fountain of dark blood.

Just then.

“...!”

Vikir felt goosebumps burning up the back of his neck.

It wasn't an uncommon sensation on the battlefield, just a sign that the enemy was attacking from behind.

Normally, he would have simply flung himself to the side to avoid it.

...But the truly unusual experience was about to begin.

Peo-eog!

With a dull noise, the chill on the back of his neck disappeared.

The poisonous soldier that had been reaching for him from behind was dead.

Vikir turned his head to see who had killed the poisonous soldier, but it was impossible.

Even at this moment, there were countless poisonous soldiers in full bloom in front of him.

Jjeoeog- jjeog! Peoeog! Deng-geong-

Vikir extended his magic sword, Beelzebub, and slashed at the poisonous soldiers in front of him.

And as he did, one strange thing after another happened.

...! ...! ...! ...! ...! ...!

The poisonous soldiers coming behind Vikir were continuously being defeated.

'Someone's backing me up.'

Vikir glanced behind him, but he couldn't make out who was behind him in the rapidly shifting vision and the shower of blood and rocks that sprayed everywhere.

[Hmm – It's so fast I can't see it clearly?]

Even Decarabia hadn't figured out who the helpers currently guarding Vikir's back were.

Only.

Peopeog! Kung! Ujijijig!

One thing is for sure, Vikir's back is being supported in near-perfect support.

'Who is it? Camus? Aiyen? Dolores? Sinclaire? Kirko?'

But they were already far away, across the battlefield.

The Seven Counts and Seven Knights who had been following close behind had also long since fallen behind, at the edge of their physical limits.

'...I guess we'll just have to trust them.'

Vikir decided to take a chance on his mysterious assistant, who had been watching his back without making a single mistake so far.

...Flash!

Vikir bared his eight teeth at the giant poisonous soldier that appeared before him.

Just then.

Teoeog- kkigigig!

Vikir's hand stopped in midair.

Surprisingly, a poisonous soldier appeared to counter Vikir's sword.

A grotesquely contorted creature, its entire body twisted.

Vikir recognized it immediately.

“...The eldest son of House Leviathan. Süskind.”

Once a promising young man, the next great talent, the one who would carry the empire in the future.

But now he'd long since been reduced to a grotesquely contorted, poisonous demon.

Thud!

Süskind, still standing after being struck by Vikir's blow... No, what was once Süskind.

It pushed against Vikir's sword with its mouth gaping wide open in a display of incredible strength and regeneration.

'This thing's size and regenerative power... It won't be easy.'

Vikir furrowed his brow and tried to increase his power.

...Beonjjeog!

A blow retraced the same trajectory that Vikir's blow had traveled just moments ago.

The Baskerville 8th Form.

Eight teeth fell straight onto the marks Vikir had made.

Kwakwakwakwang!

The massive flesh of Süskind shattered and scattered on the spot.

And in the shower of flesh and blood that followed, Vikir realized who had stood behind him all this time.

Black blood blowing in the wind, red eyes as if looking into a mirror.

And the beard that grew from not being able to be shaved while running through the battlefield.

The lord of Baskerville, the iron-blooded swordsman. Master of all hounds.

Hugo Le Baskerville was there.

Father and son, facing each other with eight teeth bared.

Neither Vikir nor Hugo spoke as they looked into each other's faces.

“....”

“....”

Hugo was the first to break the silence.

Charak-

He swung the famous sword 'Balmung' returned from the Bourgeois family once and shook off the blood.

Then, nonchalantly, he spoke, like the sound of the wind, a mere whisper, leaving no trace.

“You've grown up, and I haven't done anything for you.”

Vikir paused at the words.

He wanted to say something, but he didn't know what.

“....”

That was the end of the brief silence.

Hugo opened his mouth to say something more, but then shut it and turned away.

He had reached the 8th Form, which he hadn't realized he had reached.

Kwa-kwakwakwakwang!

A strike that split the sky and earth at the same time swept through the poisonous soldier.

Vikir quickly realized that now was not the time for distractions.

Soon, father and son were back to back, swinging their swords.

Where Vikir's sword slashed, Hugo stabbed through the gap.

Vikir slashed through the rest of the gap where Hugo's sword had gone through.

On the battlefield, the presence or absence of someone you can trust with your back is crucial.

As the tide of battle slowly turned, there was an awkward, ethereal silence between the two men, a silence that was more than blood and flesh.

Just then.

[Hahahaha-]

A laugh rises from the battlefield beyond.

Vikir recognized its owner at a glance.

Flauros. The source of all evil.

His eyes glowed as he grinned at Vikir.

[Rampage, my poison is infinite!]

As if to prove his point, Flauros pulled up behind him, a massive carriage behind him.

A carriage with a black barracks on top.

It was the poison recharging station Vikir had seen on his way to claim the water source.

O-ooooooh!

One by one, the poisonous soldiers began to withdraw from the walls of Tochka Fortress.

Presumably to enter the black barracks behind them to gain more power and poison.

[With this, the number of poisonous soldiers can be infinitely increased! My poison can even raise the dead!]

Flauros shouted in a confident voice.

...But not before the barracks exploded with a loud boom.

Kwakwakwakwakwakwang!

A barracks where poisonous soldiers recharge their wasted poison.

It was now engulfed in flames.

And in real time!

“...?”

Vikir scratched his head in confusion.

Why would a poison charging station explode at this point?

But that seemed to be more of a question for Flauros.

His expression was extremely contorted as he turned around in surprise.

[What, what!? Why is my Ouroboros...!?]

Suddenly, Vikir and Flauros' eyes met a familiar face.

The Harvester. Granola De Leviathan, the youngest of House Leviathan.

He was standing in front of a shattered jar with a sad expression under the burning curtain of the barracks.

Inside the jar, which had once contained the two serpents 'Ouroboros', the red death-making serpents, the oil boiling with tremendous momentum, spewed out a puff of extremely hot steam.

'Sometimes I have a lot of doubts about whether I am living well.'

'...Tch, why do you have such doubts? I'm always doing well, a man should be proud!'

Spotting Sinclaire's face in the crowd of Vikir's companions, Granola muttered in a daze.

“...Yes. A man should be proud.”

The voice sounded like it was coming from a distant memory.

Sinclaire shook her head.

...Chwaag!

Two snakes jumped out of the boiling oil.

Despite the horrific burns that fried their bodies, the Ouroboros summoned the last of their strength and grabbed the dazed Granola by the throat, dragging him into the jar.

Wasisisisisi-

Hot oil bubbled out of the large jar.

Soon there was nothing but silence in the barracks.

As Flauros watched the barracks burn, he cried out in horror.

[No way! How dare this bastard betray...!?]

What an outrageous, outrageous turn of events.

A truly unexpected and absurd event.

“...Last time, I only took your arm.”

His voice was eerily cold.

“This time, I want your neck, too.”

This was because Vikir had caught up with him before he knew it.

Chapter 474

Knowing the Fate of My Father (1)

◆

A severed head is terrible.

[Didn't I tell you from the beginning that your efforts are in vain?]

“....”

[It is impossible to kill me at this time, give up, Demon Hunter].

Flauros continued to click his tongue.

Truth or lies. To know and be deceived, or to pretend not to know and charge ahead.

Camus, standing beside Vikir, gritted her teeth.

“Hey, is what he's saying true? Does his death really open the gates of destruction or something?”

The answer came from two sources.

Seere, trembling on Camus's shoulder, and Decarabia, clinging to Vikir's chest.

[Flauros is a being of the power of deception, so we don't know if the words are true or not].

[... But I'd say it's likely, he's cunning].

In other words, even fellow demons can't tell if Flauros' words are false or true.

Faced with a choice, a crossroads, Vikir hesitated.

Should he let Flauros go, or should he kill him, knowing that it would open the Gate of Destruction?

Even now, Flauros was escaping slowly, his head like water vapor.

Sweat dripped from his face like molten lead.

Vikir clenched his teeth so hard they might break.

...Just then.

“Do what you want.”

A heavy voice came from behind Vikir's back.

Hugo. He cast a dark shadow over Vikir's back.

“Son.”

He called to Vikir.

Vikir didn't turn.

But Hugo continued.

“A father is responsible for his children, even if they make the wrong choices.”

Vikir thought the words were very refreshing.

When he finished, Hugo muttered to himself, 'It's funny to say this, but since when did I become a father?'

Then.

Gigigig-

There was the sound of feet scraping the ground.

“Now, wait!”

Vikir whirled around, but it was too late.

...Flash!

Hugo swung his sword.

A powerful strike flew out and struck the ground.

It was where the head of Flauros, who was almost ready to flee, was.

[Kkeuaaaaagh!]

A tearing scream rang out.

A merciless blow severed the demon's last hold.

Vikir's mouth hung half open as he watched Flauros' head shatter into pieces.

Demons kill. Vikir would probably have made the same choice, given a little more time.

But Vikir had been granted a suspension of disbelief for a choice that carried great responsibility.

By the hand of Hugo, a man he had never considered a father.

It was as if he had unintentionally made a fool of himself.

“....”

“....”

Vikir and Hugo's gazes meet.

A gap where complex thoughts flow.

Everyone gathered in that ethereal atmosphere was speechless.

...Just then.

Grumble! Kwakwang!

Suddenly, a wing fell on the dry sky.

Dark clouds gathered, and a pillar of red light appeared in the sky.

It was a huge and massive red line.

The red curve, which seemed to be round, soon began to form an intricate geometric pattern in the center.

And Vikir recognized it at once for what it was.

“The Gate of Destruction!”

The words Flauros had spoken before his death were true.

He had opened the Gate of Destruction, even as he shouldered a burden so great that it amounted to nothing less than annihilation, and he had woven his life into a cord to keep it closed.

And now that Flauros's lifeline is completely severed, the seal is broken and the gate is opened, as planned.

A gate that was summoned by a High Ranking Demon at the cost of his life.

Perhaps by now, Flauros's soul would be in a terrible state of agony for all eternity, with a penalty far worse than annihilation, but... none of that matters now.

The Gate of Destruction had been opened.

Vikir barely suppressed a frantic shudder that ran through his body.

The rainy season of fear would soon begin.

The long rainy season that signaled the end of the world.

The final weapon of the demons that had inflicted the greatest and most horrific damage on the human alliance by wiping out 98% of the living.

Endless, never-ending rains of fire, winds of fire, thunderbolts of fire, and floods of fire.

The searing raindrops that would fall on the earth and sky, scorching everything in their path.

The grass and trees of the mountains will burn, the forests will be reduced to ashen deserts, the oceans and lakes will boil over and turn into wastelands, and every living, breathing thing will be burned to death or dried up.

The great flood of fire that will flood for the next 150 days will wipe out all remaining life.

“...Was that real?”

“A portal of this magnitude, the Hell Tree is nothing compared.”

“I've never seen such terrible magic before! An overwhelming sense of foreboding....”

“I can't believe it. I can't believe such a thing exists.”

“It makes Nouvelle Vague seem like a cradle.”

Camus, Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko can't believe their eyes when they see the giant portal being drawn in the sky above them.

This is what it means to see with your own eyes and not believe.

Just then.

...Quack!

The entire sky began to shake violently.

Vikir shouted like a thunderbolt.

“Here comes the first explosion!”

Before he regressed, he clearly remembered the moment the Gate of Destruction opened.

First, the gate would open, a huge amount of hellfire inside will pour out.

The instantaneous firepower is enough to reduce tens of thousands of soldiers to a handful of ashes in an instant.

The Gate of Destruction that appeared here now was certainly powerful enough to do just that.

Crouching.

The gate slowly opened.

The crowd was stunned by the heat already emanating from it.

“...It's hot.”

“Pushishishi- We're already thirsty, and now we're going to burn to death?”

Even Orca and Sade could not fight back against the Gate of Destruction that appeared in the sky.

Even Cindywendy, standing on the watchtower of Tochka's main castle, spoke up.

“...If something like that spews fire, the entire Tochka will blow away.”

The countless refugees who had been furiously throwing stones at the city walls were mesmerized in unison.

A natural disaster that they dare not even think of resisting, a presence that brings overwhelming despair and fear.

That was the Gate of Destruction.

The red portal that had opened in the black sky was now fully formed.

And now, it slowly began to open and reveal its deep and vile contents.

Then.

Jeobeog-

Through all this despair, chaos, and terror, there was a man who took a step forward.

Vikir.

His expression was as calm as ever.

'...Now I know why I regressed.'

Perhaps it was to prevent a situation like this.

Chaang-

Vikir drew his sword.

He took another step toward the Gate of Destruction that was opening its mouth at Tochka.

To face the great firestorm that was about to burst forth.

And then.

Ku-leuleuleuleug!

A huge pillar of fire erupted.

A supernatural disaster on a scale as terrifying as the eruption of the Nouvelle Vague volcano.

Like a tongue protruding from its mouth, the Gate of Destruction unleashed its first blast of crimson flames, attempting to lick up anything in its path.

And Vikir set his whole body on fire to cut off its tongue.

All of this was what he had planned from the moment he first opened his eyes in his cradle.

...Kuleuleug!

Squeezing every last bit of mana from his body, Vikir formed a Black Sun at the tip of his sword.

The eight fiercely spinning teeth took on the shape of a sphere and stood at the Gate of Destruction.

But it was so small and fragile that it looked like a fire moth rushing toward a torch.

'Still, I can't give up.'

Vikir gritted his teeth and unleashed a blast of mana in his body.

A blow that gathers all the strength from the time when he strangled a poisonous snake in his cradle.

Vikir's charge, blessed by Dolores, met the flames of the Gate of Destruction.

Jilkkeun-

Vikir closed his eyes, imagining his body soon to be consumed by the flames.

....

...But nothing happened.

No shock, not even a hint of heat.

“?”

Vikir opened his eyes, puzzled by the lack of change.

And there it was, an incredible sight.

The Gate of Destruction. A feast of bursting hellfire. A wind-lit Tochka.

Something stuck in the middle of it all.

Black teeth.

One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.

It was holding back the flames from the gates of hell.

“No, not eight, but....”

Vikir fumbled for the number of teeth.

It had one more than eight.

Nine.

The ninth tooth was biting ferociously at the flames.

Nine teeth resisting destruction. Baskerville 9th Form.

The enemies that exploded with terrifying momentum and the black aura prevented the apocalypse from coming to Tochka.

It was certainly something Vikir had seen before.

The Grave of Swords. The words of a once noble man who had crossed the threshold of death.

Death Knight. And the Nine Teeth. Baskerville, the Supreme.

A being who has crossed the line between life and death.

An undead whose death has been postponed even though he has already died once.

'...Since when did I become a father?'

Hugo.

Hugo Le Baskerville.

The patriarch of the Baskerville family, the Iron Blood Swordman Family, was there.

Chapter 475

Knowing the Fate of My Father (2)

◆

'He will never again have to live such a painful life of being hung by a thick chain during the day and having the rope pulled by him at night.'

-Park Young-hee, from『Hound』-

◆

Hugo Le Baskerville.

The iron-blooded swordsman Baskerville was there.

The body that transformed into a Death Knight was covered in jet-black armor forged with the flames of hell, and the dark red aura was completely changed to black.

The life that was pledged is drained like a tide.

His skin turned white and bluish, and just as the horizon between life and death flipped, so did the black and white of his pupils.

A pact to give life and draw power in return.

In the final battle, Hugo pushed his entire body's mana beyond its limits and crossed the threshold of the 9th Formation, which he had only seen from afar for so long.

Kwakwakwakwang!

The flames from the Gates of Destruction clash with the aura of a single Death Knight.

Even the world-famous sword Balmung, which was at its closest point, was unable to withstand the rebound damage and slowly began to melt away.

That Balmung.

The sharp and sturdy sword.

The core that was colder and sharper than anything else in the world.

Slowly. Hot. Melting. Breaking apart.

Vikir looked at it and asked, unable to help himself.

“...Why did you do that?”

The voice was slow and hot, melting like a steel blade dropped into a furnace.

It was a heavy tone, but that made even the slightest tremor feel even bigger.

It was the first time Vikir had ever asked a question he was genuinely curious about, hoping for an answer.

Unreasonable paternal love? A false sense of responsibility? A bit of guilt? Belated atonement?

What was it that drove Hugo to make the choices he did?

....

Hugo didn't look back at Vikir's question, which left out a lot.

As always, he simply marches forward, facing straight ahead.

His broad back slowly dissolves into a blinding halo of light.

Suddenly, Vikir heard a small voice in his ear, distant and faint.

'I don't know.'

...Is there anything in the world that he doesn't know? Vikir wondered, subconsciously.

He looked at the back of Hugo's head with a newfound sense of dread and unfamiliarity.

He had crossed many lifetimes, and he was certainly older than his current father, but ... why? He could not understand him, could not fathom the depths of his heart.

The back, which moves away to a distance that cannot be reached, is wide and solid.

It was black and murky, as if sinking beneath the surface of lava.

And then.

...Pas!

His vision cleared.

He could see a black sky, and a red portal.

The initial impact from the Gate of Destruction had dissipated.

The one who blocked it in front of everyone.

The Ironblood Swordsman, patriarch of Baskerville and Master of all hounds.

...And in fact, he himself was a hound who had lived his entire life hanging on a thick chain.

Hugo Le Baskerville. He was 64 years old. Burning white on the battlefield.

The only way to describe it is that it was a very Baskerville death.

Even Major General Orca and the Marquis de Sade were speechless at the sight of Hugo's exertion and oxidation.

“...That was definitely the 9th Form Baskerville. Was that really possible?”

“I can't believe it. Cane Corso, the old man wasn't senile?”

It was overwhelming and spectacular.

Hugo's last stand had everyone in Tochka gritting their teeth in disbelief.

In the end, Fortress Tochka survived. And so did Vikir.

“....”

Vikir stared at the white ash scattered by the wind.

White, charred ash. Complete combustion that burned everything.

It was impossible to tell if that was what Hugo had left behind, but somehow Vikir thought it was.

...But.

Hugo's sacrifice did not end the whole situation.

...Rumbling!

The Gate of Destruction, summoned by Flauros with his life, still stood firm in the sky.

Only the firestorm that had first opened it had dissipated, but the rainy season of fear that followed had not.

Soon, tiny glowing red drops began to fall from the giant gate.

Patter-patter-patter-

It was fireworks. Tiny sparks, the kind you'd see when iron clashes with iron.

Soon they were falling in dots, then in clusters, then in countless numbers.

“It's a rain of fire!”

Someone among the refugees shouted.

They were right.

Countless drops of fire rained down from the sky, hitting the ground and scorching the surroundings.

No one stood a chance against this searing shower of fire, which fell in a searing trajectory.

The apocalypse. It was surely casting its dark shadow, starting here in Tochka.

Screams began to come from everywhere.

Refugees gathered on the ramparts fled down the stone walls, heads bowed to avoid the rain of fire.

Tents, wooden poles, and anything else that could be burned fell prey to the flames.

The ground was already smoldering with red ash.

“...It's over, there's nothing we can do about it.”

“Pushishishi- as expected. I was destined to burn to death.”

Orca and Sade also looked up at the red raindrops falling down and said with a sense of despair.

Just then.

Sammua, the girl standing next to Tudor, caught the raindrops that fell on her face with her hand.

“Huh?”

There was no pain or despair in the girl's expression.

There was only surprise and delight.

“Is this water?”

Tudor and Bianca turned their heads at the girl's words.

“It's not water, it's fire! We have to get away from it!”

“Run under the stone wall now!”

But Sammua is still dumbfounded.

“No, big brother, it's water!”

After saying this, Sammua wiped the raindrops off her face with her hand and held it out in front of her.

Moist water. It was clearly an ordinary raindrop.

“Huh?”

“Huh?”

“What?”

One by one, the people who were running inside the castle to escape the rain of fire raised their heads.

Fire droplets pouring down from the Gate of Destruction.

But soon, more and more droplets were falling through the gaps.

Pusisisisig-

Fire and water droplets meet in the air and turn into white vapor.

The red flames rising from the ground began to fade in power.

Soon, the rain from the sky began to grow thicker and thicker.

Sswaaaaa-

It was all water.

“It's raining! It's really raining!”

“Wa, water! It's water!”

“Water drops are falling!”

People looked up at the sky with their eyes wide open.

The Gate of Destruction, and the thick dark clouds that hung over it.

Hwiiiing-

A gust of wind from the southeast pushes the dark clouds this way.

Kwalkwalkwalkwalkwalkwal...

The raindrops, which had turned into a torrential downpour, were creating a raging torrent down the steep walls of Tochka Fortress.

It was a torrential downpour, sudden and maddening, powerful enough to overwhelm the rain of fire falling from the Gate of Destruction.

Camus, Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko opened their mouths to speak as they watched the sudden downpour.

“I've never seen anything like this before.”

“Even in the rainy jungle, we've never seen anything like this.”

“Oh my god, it couldn't be this timely....”

“This will solve our drinking water problem!”

“The climate on earth is constantly changing.”

The rainfall was so heavy that everyone else was speechless.

Of all the refugees gathered here in Tochka, there's probably not a single one of them who has ever experienced rain of this magnitude.

...Kuleuleug! Pusisisisisig...

The scorching Gate of Destruction began to cool.

A torrential downpour that would have dampened even the rainy season of fear.

Waves of floodwaters swept away the fires that had just begun to ignite on the ground.

“Everyone back inside the fortress!”

Major General Orca ordered.

Tochka is a plateau made of solid rock that is not subject to erosion.

The land is so high that it is naturally not subject to flooding.

The terrain is made up of huge boulders and sand between them, so the water drains away quickly.

“A fortress that can withstand any major flood. Avoiding fire and water... It's like an ark from mythology... oh!?”

Dolores was muttering to herself when she suddenly realized something.

'Only here will fire and water escape, and only here will true salvation be found.'

It was a false myth she had created and spread.

And the being who had earlier instructed to create that myth.

'There will be a great flood soon, so prepare the ark.'

'Hold on. All I can say is to hold on.'

'Just wait and everything will work itself out. I promise.'

A person who has made a home here in Tochka for a very long time.

Even in a situation where drinking water was running out and demons were running rampant, a person who endured everything alone and waited, and who promised salvation.

Vikir.

He stood at the very front of the fortress, peering through the Gate of Destruction.

Pusisisisisig-

Most of the raindrops evaporated before they even got near the Gate of Destruction, but the ones that followed, falling and falling, pushed through the heat and pushed forward.

The gate, scorching hot from Flauros's mana, was cooling rapidly under the torrential downpour.

Vikir turned his head.

He could see a star in the southeastern sky.

Seven stars commonly called guiding stars.

It's a special constellation, visible only from a specific direction, that has guided countless people throughout the ages.

Now, however, the constellation of the Guide Star was made up of eight stars.

...Kwaleuleung!

Vikir stared at the eighth star, which shone unusually brightly through the pouring rain.

“...Poseidon.”

All that hard work rolling around in the Nouvelle Vague was finally paying off.

The rainy season of fear that lies ahead. A 150-day shower of fire.

And the torrential rains that began to fall almost simultaneously. A 150-day flood.

It was essentially a declaration of the end of the war, completely cooling down the furnace that would open the Gate of Destruction.

The Gate of Destruction cooled and eventually ceased to function.

The wave of mana has dispersed, and the summoning circle that formed the door is also fading.

The Age of Destruction is no more.

Vikir gazed down at the corpses of the poisonous people, all of whom had been swept away, and the plain below, which had turned into an ocean.

Then he gave his final command.

“Tudor.”

Tudor responds to Vikir's call, raising his spear.

As if he's been waiting for this moment, Vikir speaks immediately.

“We need Donquixote's Armada.”

Everyone who heard the words could not help but think the same thing.

The destination is Imperial Capital. A symbol of the empire where the emperor resides.

The center of the world where everyone's youth and prime years have been at least once.

...And the final enemy, the First Corpse.

The last demon is lurking there.

Chapter 476

Tochka Annihilation Battle (6)

◆

The eruption of the Nouvelle Vague volcano. And the trigger that caused it, Poseidon.

Vikir's small ball ended up causing a massive butterfly effect.

A great flood that sweeps away the world.

Over the next 150 days, this torrential downpour would swallow up all but a few high plateaus.

The wildfires that had been raging across the empire, the monster hordes that had taken advantage of the vicious conditions, and the drought that had been lingering were all swept away.

Naturally, everyone in Tochka was able to receive salvation.

Not only did the waters never reach the high plateau, but the hard rock and fine sand of the ground made for excellent drainage.

The fortress were also strong enough to withstand the weather, and the lack of drinking water, the only drawback, was naturally solved by harvesting rainwater.

Under normal circumstances, the Great Flood would have been recorded as an unprecedented supernatural disaster.

But the flood that followed was a miracle because it was first preceded by the catastrophes of wildfires, drought, plague, monster hordes, and rainy season of fear that had spread across the empire as a result of the Gate of Destruction.

Destruction was offset by destruction.

◆

Deep drainage ditches were dug throughout the barracks within the fortress.

Large barrels were placed in front of the barracks, and the refugees caught the rainwater in them and drank to their hearts' content.

They hadn't had a drop of water for days.

“The situation outside the fortress is such that the enemy will not be able to get in. It is time to concentrate on internal security.”

Major General Orca released the personnel of the Nouvelle Vague to take care of the security inside the fortress and reorganize the discipline.

Meanwhile, Marquis de Sade was already wincing at how long it had been since the battle had ended.

“Pushishishi-we can finally complete the revolution we failed to do 40 years ago! Where is the crown prince? The emperor is dead, so we should kill that bastard!”

“Ugh grandpa! When my body gets better, let's go together!”

Sadi barely managed to stop Sade, who wanted to grab a small boat and go to the Imperial Capital right away.

Other than that, the reorganization after the battle was taking place slowly.

Everyone, including Osiris and Cindywendy, worked together to enlarge and rebuild Tochka Fortress.

Everyone was preparing and gearing up for the end of the Great Flood in 150 days.

The hope of being able to move forward. With that, everyone's faces were bright.

...But there was one person who remained expressionless.

Vikir.

He always stood at the top of the ramparts, facing the pouring rain.

...Cheolsseog!

Outside the fortress, now turned into the sea.

Hollow orchids bloom above the raging waves.

Vikir compared the Tochka that was before the regression to the Tochka that is now.

“....”

As it was, the wheel of fate should have rolled in an even harsher direction.

The present world has become hell due to the invasion of demons.

Sadi took advantage of the chaos to lead an army to attack Nouvelle Vague.

Marquis de Sade, who was able to escape Nouvelle Vague with the help of his granddaughter, Sadi.

Major General Orca, who detonated the Poseidon he found while working to prevent Marquis de Sade's escape.

The rainy season of terror was ended by the great flood that followed.

However, countless people had already been burned to death, and the unexpected deluge had dealt a devastating blow not only to the demons but also to humanity.

...But what about now?

The Great Flood began relatively on schedule, although it was off by a week or so, causing quite a bit of difficulty in securing drinking water.

The rainy season of fear has ended, and the Gate of Destruction has cooled.

[At this point, it is nothing short of a complete victory. Isn't that right, human?]

Decarabia said in a self-congratulatory tone.

But Vikir shook his head silently.

“We haven't won yet. We've won the big local battle, but there's still one more to go.”

[Are you talking about the First Corpse?]

“Yes.”

Vikir nodded, looking out over what had become a vast expanse of sea.

Decarabia's eyes widened in wonder.

[I see. So that's why you were the first to restore Donquixote of the Spear Sea Gun Family (滄海槍家) as soon as you escaped from Nouvelle Vague, so that you could get your hands on the Invincible Cavalry and the Invincible Armada that divided Donquixote's power].

“Yes, indeed. In a world like this, he who has the fleet will be the Overlord(霸者).”

At Vikir's words, Decarabia paused for a moment.

Then, after some thought, he spoke again.

[Speaking of Overlord, human].

“What?”

[This is Flauros, you faced before].

Decarabia continued speaking with a slightly uneasy expression.

[Flauros was one of the Overlord, known for his lies and persistence even in Hell].

“What are you trying to say?”

[Is he really immortal? I doubt that. If he faked his own death...]

Flauros is such a good liar that even his death is suspect.

But.

“I don't care about that anymore.”

[What? Why?]

“Whether he was alive or dead at that moment, he won't survive.”

Vikir smiled dryly as he looked out at the raging storm, the waves, and the distant enemy and tributaries of the Black Mountains beyond.

“This world, too. It's just as dangerous as Hell, when you get right down to it.”

◆

The jungle is pouring with torrential rain.

A man runs through a dense forest of sword trees, their leaves as sharp as blades.

[Heoeog! Heog! Keoheog-]

The man running, his body covered in blood, was clearly Thomas de Leviathan, second son of the extremely poisonous House Leviathan.

But the red aura of death emanating from his body and his sharpened teeth indicate that he is not the same man.

He was Flauros, who, shortly before his death, had used a trick to transfer his soul and take over Thomas's dying body.

It wasn't a strange situation, since all demons are merely demonic hosts, spare bodies that can be switched at any time.

After stealing Thomas's body at the last moment, Flauros fled the battlefield in desperation, carrying the body that was already in a state of destruction, and eventually succeeded in reaching this place.

[My body is crumbling... I can't hold out much longer... Damn it... I've forced open the Gate of Destruction... Even my soul is tattered... I must hurry to the Imperial Capital... I must ask First Corpse for help...]

Still, he had succeeded in killing Pigi, so there must be something to bargain with.

Flauros thought.

Just then.

Sssssss...

Flauros felt a chill run down his spine.

The temperature around him was dropping rapidly, starting with the valley he had just entered.

Cold Bone. The name given to the natives who lived in the jungle of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

Flauros could not have known that the climate here was frosty even in the middle of summer.

As his already low body temperature drops even lower, his body becomes sluggish and his joints stiffen.

More blood trickled from the puncture wounds in his neck, stomach, and other gaping wounds across his body.

Just then.

[...Hiig!]

Flauros was forced to drop to the ground as soon as he exited the valley.

Sssssss-.

A giant shadow crawled through the raindrops and leaves.

With an eerie sound, a single spider emerged, its body enormous.

The spider scoured the forest as if searching for something.

It wasn't the only spider in the forest beyond.

[...Is it looking for me?]

Flauros had a hunch.

If they found him now, he would die. No chance of escape.

Flauros crawled along the ground, desperately holding his breath.

He crawled, crawled, crawled, crawled, like a worm, to avoid the spiders' eyes.

...After what seemed like an eternity, he managed to escape the spiders' siege and reach the river.

The river is quite high up, but the stream is swollen from the heavy rains.

With a plop-

Flauros dives into the water to cross the river.

...Quack!

Suddenly, Flauros feels a violent pain in his lower body, and he has to jump back.

[Ugh!? Fish!?]

Fish with teeth like saw blades were clinging to him, biting into his flesh.

'Nateri'. Even on the surface of the water, the cannibalistic fish of the rivers of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain could be seen swarming around, smelling the scent of blood.

[...Goddammit!]

Flauros had just turned to leave the river.

Hissing-

A pitch blackness fills his vision.

A gigantic mouth was reaching up to swallow Flauros's head.

Mushuhushu. A giant snake that lives in the jungle. It approached from behind without making a sound, and in the blink of an eye, it swallowed Flauros whole.

[Kuuuuaaghhh! You lowly creature!]

Flauros used his last strength to burst the snake's belly skin.

Fortunately, it was an immature creature, so killing it wasn't too difficult.

It's just a shame that he'd spent most of his life force tearing through the tough snake skin to escape.

[...I must find somewhere to rest, or I'll have to stay the night, what a disgrace.]

Flauros desperately opened his eyes, which kept closing.

He ripped his eyelids away, leaving only his eyeballs, and his vision cleared.

Soon, he spotted a deep trench dug under the roots of a tree.

It seemed like a good place to stay out of the rain and keep warm.

Flauros staggered toward the trench.

But could it be that his concentration was disrupted due to his low stamina? Flauros didn't notice the large fingernail marks on the side of the tree.

...And the results were devastating.

[Keu-wo-aaaahhhhhh!]

A thunderous roar erupted from behind him.

Flauros didn't even have time to turn around.

The blind old oxbear female swung her forepaw with the destructive force of a dozen tons.

It crushed Flauros's skull with a sure crack.

[Keuaag! Kkeueoeoeoeoeo...]

Oxbear looked on in disgust as Flauros spewed poisonous blood from his body.

Oxbear washed the blood off her paws in the rain and went back into her den.

Not worth killing.

Flauros crawled across the ground.

[...! ...! ...!]

No words come out properly from the crushed mouth.

What is he trying to say?

The screams of his aching body? The hatred for those who have brought him to this point? The rage that comes from recognizing the horrors of his situation? The revenge he has vowed over and over again during his journey here? The fear of... annihilation? The regret that he should never have come here in the first place?

Complex thoughts are mixed in the muddy brain.

And.

There were those who greeted him.

Weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng-weng...

Mosquitoes.

Mosquitoes in staggering numbers, following the scent of blood.

There were blood-sucking mosquitoes attached to the body of Flauros, or rather, Thomas.

There were also some mosquitoes that sucked flesh.

There were also mosquitoes that only sucked skin.

There were even some mosquitoes that sucked on bones by sinking their saliva deeper.

...And then there were the mosquitoes that didn't suck anything at all.

It just floats in the air with hazy, murky eyes.

A mosquito that sucks nothing, yet somehow lords over the others, exuding an overwhelming sense of foreboding.

And Flauros, lying on the ground, groaning, stares bloodshot eyes at the mosquito.

[...! ...!]

Then, silently, the mosquito landed on top of Flauros' head.

It then stung him, aimlessly, but with a clear target.

Jjoooog-

The red-hot smoke enters the stomach through the mosquito's saliva.

Mosquitoes are the most feared and wary of natives living in jungle.

The soul-sucking mosquito adorned Flauros' soul.

[...!]

It was a shabby and degrading end to be reduced to a mere meal of insects.

Chapter 478

Downtown Naval Warfare (2)

◆

Donquixote's Invincible Armada.

As far as sea battles go, it is the Empire's most powerful force.

Darkness loomed ahead of the countless ships as they sailed across the blue waters of the large expanse of sea.

Vikir, at the bow of the foremost ship, was lost in thought as he faced the strong sea breeze.

'Infinite darkness, enveloping the world. This must have been one of the First Corpse's abilities.'

The normally clear Imperial Capital sky was now shows neither moonlight nor starlight.

Only.

...Kwakwang! Splash-

There is nothing but a tidal wave of enormous height.

“We're going to capsize!”

Bianca says worriedly.

But Tudor, standing beside her, merely snorted.

“Donquixote's ship would capsize in a tidal wave of this magnitude? No way!”

It was true.

The Invincible Armada lived up to its name and sailed through the tidal wave without a single ship running aground.

The massive ships were linked together by thick chains so that the whole was one, and one was the whole.

Yeonhwangye (連環計). A tactic of connecting ships with chains.

Vikir's strategy had multiplied the Invincible Armada's breakthrough power.

Seeing it, Camus nodded in admiration.

“It's a good method as long as you watch out for fire attacks.”

“With the rain pouring down like this, there's no need to worry about being attacked by fire.”

“Exactly. It's the best we have at the moment. You are my boyfriend after all!”

At Vikir's reply, Camus smirked and punched Vikir in the arm.

Just then.

“...!”

Vikir's expression changed as soon as Camus got closer.

“The smell.”

“...?”

Camus was greatly embarrassed by Vikir's unexpected remark.

She quickly sniffed the scent on her body.

“W-what is it? What? Do I smell? I wash every day? Hey, I just finished brushing my teeth! I'm meeting my boyfriend, but I don't know... Oh, or should I have at least sprayed some perfume? I was already worried because it didn't seem like it would be a good idea to carry perfume into the battlefield... Hey, maybe I was sweating when I did gymnastics in the morning...?”

“Not that smell.”

Vikir dismissed Camus, who blushed bright red.

“The smell of a demon.”

“...!”

“Half a unique, faint smell.”

Then Camus' expression hardened.

“That's strange. Right now, Seere only accounts for a very small amount of my body, so it shouldn't smell that much, right?”

“It's not coming from you.”

Vikir replied in a low voice.

In the past, Camus had shared half of her body with Seere during her reign as the Corpse Queen.

Vikir had smelled the scent of the other half of the demon once before, and had it imprinted on his nose.

And now. A similar scent was being carried on the sea breeze.

Straight ahead, from the direction of the imperial palace, which is considered a key area in the Imperial Capital, the center of the empire.

“...!”

Camus too could soon smell what Vikir was talking about.

Indeed, it was a thick, intense scent that could be felt even from a distance.

“It's an anomaly, not the usual demonic scent.”

Aiyen said, jumping down from the watchtower.

She had spent so much time in the Hell Tree, slaying countless demons, monsters, and fairies that she had become accustomed to smelling this type of scent.

“It's definitely... A different aura than I'm used to, much more ominous, but just as unstable. Different from the level of strength.”

Dolores, who had emerged from her cabin below deck, was equally grim.

“It's similar to what I felt with Camus, but it's also different. Where Camus felt like she was half human, half demon..., this feels like there's only half demon left.”

Sinclaire, who was organizing the anchor lines, agreed with everyone.

After being bathed in demonic dragon blood in the Hell Tree, she too had a feeling.

Buzz buzz-

Vikir heard Beelzebub's cry as it slumbered on the inside of his wrist.

And the exact same cry was coming from behind the deck.

Kirko.

Asmodeus, the magic sword, was emitting the same cries as Beelzebub from the strap around her waist as she stared at Vikir wordlessly.

Vikir turned to the Decarabia clinging to her breastplate.

“Do you know anything about the First Corpse?”

[...Am I a knowledge vending machine? Don't treat me like that saint over there].

Dolores, who was next to him, became angry at Decarabia's words, but was stopped by Camus and Aiyen's dissuasion.

“Calm down. It's not wrong.”

“Haha- In the Tochka Siege, you were practically a holy water vending machine.”

“You, that's too much! I worked hard to protect yourself from behind! This is why healers lose money! If I do well, it won't be noticeable, but if I don't, it will be noticeable....”

“Calm down. If it weren't for you, Tochka would have fallen long ago.”

“That's right. Holy power is a strange thing. I've never seen it before.”

Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko also chimed in.

But all the while, Vikir was focused on Decarabia's answer.

[Ahem! The First Corpse is. He's a heteromorph. Normal creatures divide individuals based on their bodies, but that concept doesn't work for him].

“...What does that mean?”

[I mean. You will divide and define human entities based on you. You, the human being, are one. And if there are other human beings who meet the same criteria, they are two. And three. Four. Five.... But not once. Two may be one, and one may be two. Since the criterion for separating the 'a' and the 'non' is outside the human concept, it is impossible to cut them according to conventional wisdom.]

“I have no idea what you're talking about. So, I guess it means he has a unique body structure like you?”

Decarabia is an object-type demon, which is a fairly unusual category among demons.

In that case, First Corpse could also be difficult to deal with.

[Anyway. I don't know much about him either, he's a secretive creature, but....]

Decarabia's voice tightened as if he were about to reveal a very important secret.

[I only heard that the roles of 'those who close the door' and 'those who open the door' are separate. This is all I know.]

Vikir furrowed his brow at the increasingly confusing answer.

He's been a straight and upright man all his life, and he doesn't like this kind of back-and-forth conversation.

Just when Vikir was about to ask another question.

“Emergency! Tsunami up ahead!”

Cindywendy shouts from the watchtower of the next ship over.

Everyone quickly grabbed onto the railing and fixed their gaze forward.

Koo-oooooooooo!

The water surged with tremendous momentum.

One moment it looked like a distant hill was rising, and the next, a wave that seemed to reach the sky.

It felt like watching the entire skin of the sea surface peel off.

“...Eueum!”

Tudor was getting pretty nervous, too.

In the face of a tsunami of that magnitude, even the most powerful ships would be in danger.

But.

“Pushishishi- Fools, what are you so worried about?”

Marquis de Sade, who was sitting in front of the bow and holding a fishing rod, looked completely carefree.

He tilted his head sharply and turned to Tudor and Donquixote's knights.

“Have you forgotten who you are with?”

...?

They all shook their heads.

At that moment.

Kwa-kwang!

A tremendous boom erupted from the front, and the tsunami in front of them tore apart in an instant.

The tsunami lying helplessly in a gaping hole.

And everyone on the ship saw it.

Just as the tsunami rose to engulf the armada, a hand grabs the back of the tsunami with tremendous force and pulls it down.

...Peopeong!

The next thing they knew, the hand clutching the line of Marquis de Sade's fishing pole shot out of the water.

It was a killer whale with white spots on its grayish skin that landed on the deck of the ship.

“Sometimes you have to warm up like this.”

Orca, in his killer whale form, puffed on a damp cigarette that Lieutenant Colonel Bastille lit for him.

Peopeopeopeopeong!

The tsunami debris that Orca crushed in the water was disposed of by the heads of each family.

Even though they were fragments, each and every piece of water was of considerable size and was flying in all directions.

...Teog!

It was Osiris, the Bizarre Bird, his black hair flowing and perched on the railing in front of Vikir.

He had just slashed through a giant tsunami and suddenly felt Vikir's gaze on him and turned his head.

Is it because he's his brother? Osiris quickly read the emotion in Vikir's eyes.

“Are you worried about your father's affairs?”

Vikir didn't bother to answer.

And Osiris didn't ask.

Instead, Osiris turned and added.

“I, too, could not understand his actions.”

“....”

“But I can sympathize.”

“...!”

Unable to understand, but able to empathize. The opposite is true, but it is extremely rare.

Osiris turned his head.

His gaze was fixed on Cindywendy on the watchtower of the nearby ship.

“Perhaps one day you will understand.”

Osiris muttered, 'It's not necessary to understand,' and vanished as quickly as he had appeared.

“....”

Vikir was lost in thought.

The women following him, his father's white-oxidized body, the Gate of Destruction that had cooled, the final battle with the last of the Tens.

His stomach churned wildly, and his mind raced.

Vikir breathed deeply.

The ship may be shaking, but the heart must not be shaken.

Especially not at a moment like this.

Vikir shook his head to clear his thoughts.

There is no need to think about the future.

Only one thing.

“Demons kill.”

All we need to do is go all in on the head-to-head battle against First Corpse, which is just around the corner.

And then.

There was something visible in the center of the world, which at first glance seemed to be a vast chaos, with the blackened sky and water.

A pointed building pierced the horizon, rising up.

Kirko stood on the railing and shouted.

“That's the Central Clock Tower! I've seen it in the books!”

The symbol of the Imperial Capital, which overshadowed the passage of time, was seen standing tall, showing off its unchanging majesty.

The center of the metropolis, where everything, including the Colosseo Academy, was submerged in water.

The armada advancing over a city that was once a symbol of prosperity and fashion.

It was a full-fledged yet somewhat bitter entry into the Imperial Capital.

Chapter 479

Downtown Naval Warfare (3)

◆

The Central Clock Tower, the symbol of the Imperial Capital.

The Central Clock Tower, which is considered the second tallest building after the Imperial Palace, was flooded almost to the top.

The great ship on which Vikir rode parted the raging waters to pass alongside the clock tower.

Suddenly, Vikir muttered to himself.

“I think we've been through this once before.”

Beside him, Camus nodded.

“Yes, it has.”

“..., Right?”

“Yeah. When we were eight years old, we got into a fight and my clothes came off, and I was in a lot of trouble, and you....”

“No. Not that.”

“Oh yeah, like at the festival, when we were fighting all over the place here in the Imperial Capital, and we wore masks. Oh, come to think of it, that was also the time I think my clothes came off at the end....”

“Not that, either. I'm talking about the smell of demons.”

Vikir was feeling the increasingly intense demonic energy directly on his skin.

Then.

“Is that the Imperial Palace? I can see something.”

He hears Aiyen shout from the watchtower.

Then he saw a flash of golden light on the horizon.

A radiance that shimmers like the aurora in the night sky. It was clearly like a symbol of the Imperial Palace.

The tallest staircase in the world, and the golden palace built atop it.

It looks like a replica of the castle on the clouds where the gods in mythology reside.

What had truly been a celestial castle in the clouds before the Great Flood now towered like a solitary castle on the sea.

“The Imperial Palace. It's really here, I didn't think there would be a demon in there....”

Dolores said with concern in her voice.

She sounded quite nervous, but there was no hint of skepticism or guilt in her tone for turning against the Emperor.

Perhaps it was because life after knowing Vikir felt so much longer and more complete than life before knowing him.

And it was the same for Sinclaire, a classmate at the same academy.

“Wow, is that all gold? What a waste of a building, I'll have to strip it all off.”

Sinclaire's eyes sparkle as she examines the palace's exterior.

The Rich Hat atop her head was already rattling.

Meanwhile.

“...That's the Imperial Palace. Where the Emperor lives.”

Kirko gazed at the Imperial Palace on the horizon with complicated feelings.

Even the guards of the Nouvelle Vague in the deepest depths had always been taught to be loyal to the Emperor.

However, the Emperor in the palace above and the guards in the prison below never actually see the Emperor.

For the Emperor, the Nouvelle Vague is a quarantine zone that exists only on paper, and he never sees it with his own eyes.

They could live a lifetime and never see each other.

So Kirko had only vaguely imagined what the Emperor was like in his daydreams, never imagining that she would ever meet him in person.

But now. They stood in front of the palace.

The rain was pouring down in torrents and the waves were crashing fiercely, but the palace was getting closer and closer.

...Just then.

“It's another tsunami! It's bigger this time! And there are more of them!”

Cindywendy warned.

Scanning ahead with her telescope, she warned all the ships behind her.

“Another tsunami? For an unusual weather change, it is strangely frequent..”

“Pushishishi- look at the magnitude. Who's creating this?”

Orca and Sade both frowned as they watched the massive masses of water rising and falling before them.

A series of waves of that magnitude would capsize any ship before it even reached the palace.

But.

“Hahaha, is this the place for this body great hero to step out!”

Despite his youth, Tudor's eyes shone as he skillfully led the Invincible Armada, not fazed in the slightest.

His eyes sparkle as blue as the vast expanse of the sea, guiding all in the darkness.

“One outskirts! Divide!”

Tudor's command came through the storm, clear to all ships.

And then.

...Pakang! ... Pakang! ... Pakang! ... Pakang!

The sound of breaking chains could be heard everywhere.

The large sailing ships on the outskirts of the fleet fell out of the annular system.

“...?”

Everyone's heads turned.

Tudor shouted out loud.

“The outermost ships consist of nothing but abandoned ships! There are no sailors aboard, only gunpowder and breakwaters!”

And now that they were out of the way, the fleet's forward speed increased by leaps and bounds.

Now that the heavy obstacles have been removed, the speed has increased.

“But won't the lighter weight make it unstable? The waves are so strong.”

“Why do you think I dragged all this stuff up here in the first place?”

Bianca said uneasily, but Tudor remained confident.

And then.

Tudor raised his spear Gungnir and gave the signal.

And then.

Kwakwakwakwang!

Flames and explosions erupted from the wrecks on the left and right wings of the fleet.

Heavy abandoned ships sink to the bottom of the water and scatter hot flames.

The heavy breakwaters they were filled with were slowly sinking toward the bottom.

Then a remarkable change occurred.

“The waves are gone!”

Orca, sensitive to changes in water currents, was the first to notice the change.

Not only had the abandoned ships on the left and right wings of the fleet exploded, stopping the waves, but the sinking breakwaters were also pressing down on the incoming tide from below.

The sea was safe for a moment. It opened a straight path to the Imperial Palace.

The Invincible Armada, which had become lighter and faster after removing the abandoned ships, was heading straight for the imperial palace along that straight path.

“It's a bold plan. My friend.”

“Haha- I'm the patriarch of the Donquixote, this is the least I can do!”

Tudor chuckled as Sancho patted him on the shoulder.

The raging tsunami moved out of the armada's path.

The Armada advanced, meandering through waves less than half the size of the others.

Then.

Something else happened.

[K-Aaaaaaaaagh!]

[Kkieeeeeg!]

[Hiss! Hiss!]

Just when everything seemed to be calming down, all sorts of creatures started poking their heads above the surface.

Crabs so huge that they could stand on the bottom with their legs, ancient placoderms with solid iron armor, sea serpents so long you could see the end of them, and deep-sea fish so hideous and grotesque that it's hard to describe them all were attacking the ships.

“Well, this is a monster that has been released openly.”

Faced with such creatures, Bianca simply clicked her tongue.

“God Killing Squad, prepare to fire!”

At Bianca's command, the knights of Usher took up positions at the front of the ship.

Even on the rocking deck, they didn't move an inch, bows and arrows raised and aimed at the large targets in front of them.

“Open fire from the ready shooter! Fire!”

Bianca gave the final command.

At the same time, countless iron bolts imbued with a gray aura flew out and began to pierce the sea monsters.

Each arrow was like an artillery barrage.

Whether they hid under the water or dodged behind the waves, the arrows followed them as if they had eyes.

Peopeopeopeopeog! Kwakwang! Kwakwakwang!

The sea was running red with the blood of the monsters.

Not a single one of them could break through Usher's fire net.

“The demon is showing its true colors openly.”

“You don't even bother to hide your identity anymore.”

“It was said that His Majesty the Emperor passed away, so the First Prince must be the demon.”

“With the fall of his supporters, the House of Leviathan, he no longer needs to conceal his identity.”

“Darkness and chaos itself. Such is the nature of centers of power.”

Camus, Aiyen, Dolores, Sinclaire, and Kirko.

They, too, drew their weapons, preparing for the great battle against the monsters to come.

Then.

Bugeulbugeulbugeulbugeulbugeulbugeulbugeulbugeulbugeulbugeulbugeulbugeul...

Things started to look a little different.

The swarming sea creatures suddenly scattered to the left and right.

The tsunami that had been raging steadily up until now had finally subsided.

A strange silence that came out of nowhere.

And in the middle of it all, a huge pool of water was rising.

Ku-leuleuleuleuleuleug!

Despite the sniper fire of Usher's knights, the water mass rising from the center of the sea lane, and the huge, dark shadow beneath it, did not flinch.

“...Could it be 'that guy'?”

The sight was enough to make even the mighty Major General Orca grunt and groan.

Behind him, the Nouvelle Vague's all-stars, including D'Ordume, Souaré, BDISSEM, and Flubber, were also showing signs of discomfort.

“Did they follow us here?”

“No. It looks like the demon brought them here.”

“Well, it's bad luck in many ways.”

[....]

A being that originally lived somewhere else, completely unrelated to the Imperial Capital.

The most feared enemy of Nouvelle Vague's guards.

They battled for supremacy of the deepest ocean.

Now that the Nouvelle Vague is gone, 'it' seems to have made the Imperial Capital its new territory.

Chwaaaaaak-

Eventually, the last gatekeeper of the imperial palace pulled its body completely out of the water.

Eight tentacles surrounded the surface of the ocean like a mountain range.

In the chaos, where sky and sea were indistinguishable, two eyeballs glowed as yellow as the sun in the inky darkness.

Kraken.

One of the two monsters said to have been born together when light and darkness were created.

At this point, the worst creature you could ever hope to encounter.

Chapter 481

The Marquis of Discord (1)

◆

A palace covering an area of about five square kilometers.

The largest and tallest structure in human history, the Imperial Palace is the result of over 100,000 mages and more than 1 million laborers over 14 years.

It consists of a total of six palaces, and the First Emperor Palace (始皇殿), which rises at the innermost center, shows the true pinnacle of architectural beauty.

A place of splendor, grandeur, and nobility.

It was supposed to be the residence of the emperor, but it was currently home to the first crown prince.

And now a hound, freshly drenched from the storm and wind, stood in front of the First Emperor Palace.

Vikir.

The veteran, who had crossed countless lines of fire, looked up at the signboard of First Emperor Palace with a bitter expression.

The one he had once been blindly loyal to. The ultimate master. A majestic existence that even the great Hugo had paid allegiance to.

But now, this place was just a demon's playground.

BANG!

Vikir smashed through the massive front gate.

In the old days, this would have been a capital offense that would have gotten him executed immediately, but no one cared about that now.

No man's land, a desolate battlefield that seemed to have been cut off from human contact long ago.

Vikir walked through the chilly central hall and headed straight for the interior.

Soon, the Emperor's throne room came into view.

Up the craggy staircase, a figure sat on the throne, looking down at Vikir.

Red hair, pale skin. A pair of cold eyes and a high, sharp nose.

The First Crown Prince, Golding Jack Meridieu, the little sun of the Empire, sat there.

Unexpectedly, he smiled broadly at Vikir and waved.

“Oh my– it's been a long journey and you've had a hard time, Mr. Demon Hunter.”

His tone is casual despite his appearance, but the meaning behind his words is anything but casual.

Vikir did not reply, but Prince Meridieu continued in his own jovial tone.

“I apologize for coming all this way and not being able to offer you a cup of tea. All the people are dead, and I'm the only one in this big palace. How lonely it is.”

“....”

“This is the first time we've met in person, isn't it? I think I've sent you a few commendations, but the first time was when you saved Morgue's life on Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, I believe?”

“....”

“Oh, yeah. What was her name? Camus? Camus, yes, Camus. She had a really pretty face and a really nice body. For a girl, she had skills. I fell in love with her at first sight, so I debated marrying her several times, but it all ended. Is there a guy who has already made up his mind? I'm so jealous of this~”

“....”

“Oh, I see, that's a sideways glance. Anyway, I thought you were dead then, though of course you came back alive and well. And when was the next time I saw you, when you were writing your thesis on Killer Ants at the Colosseo Academy?”

“....”

“Ugh- I tried to meet you in person back then, but I was turned down. Probably because you were undercover or something, right, right?”

“....”

“I wanted to go to the Colosseo Academy to check in person because I thought he was that friend of the Baskervilles, but I was so busy with work that I forgot. If I had known it would be like this, I should have gone and at least forced myself to meet you. Right? Huh-”

Vikir raised his hand to cut the crown prince off at the continued chatter.

Teong-

Vikir pulled the chain and set the coffin on the floor.

The crown prince smirked at the coffin Vikir carried.

“What's with the coffin? Did you come prepared to die, or something? It's old-fashioned. You're a bit old-fashioned for your age, you know.”

“I came to end the war.”

At Vikir's words, the crown prince's mouth quirked up in an amused expression.

“End the war? Oh, you mean the civil war? Geez~ Why do you all keep looking for my brother when he's already missing?”

“....”

“Yeah, well, I've heard about the Leviathan family, I'm sorry to hear that, but the Second Prince that the other factions are pushing for is long gone. I'm the only one with legitimate ancestry, so who becomes the Emperor?”

“....”

“Why don't you come under me? It's better to be a public figure than to be a traitor, and the stigma of being a usurper is a bit much, don't you think?”

The crown prince's words were bizarre.

They were so far removed from reality that they felt foreign.

The lines that didn't fit the situation or the mood seemed to go on and on and on, like the symptoms of schizophrenia.

Vikir finally bared his teeth in response to a series of questions.

“I have no interest in quarrels between humans.”

“Oh? A declaration of neutrality? But isn't it human nature to eventually take sides?”

“Yes. That's what humans are, and that's why they can't be demon dogs.”

Vikir's words were decisive.

[....]

With that last line as a turning point, the black and white masturbation in the crown prince's eyes changed colors.

His voice, too, began to take on an eerie tone.

[Hohohoho- Okay, I've had enough of this bullshit for now].

“....”

[Oh, but one more thing. The Kraken is a rare creature, that guy is a rare species that is hard to find even in the depths of the world. Originally, I was planning to make it into a spirit beast, but I just released it into the sea.]

“....”

[Did it fight that spider? Wow, that would have been a great picture... It's rare to see a battle of that magnitude even on the mainland. When did that tiny spider get so big? Did it absorb the poison and fraud that were signs before destruction? I never thought it would grow bigger than its mother. ...]

The crown prince, showing his true colors, but still chatty.

Vikir, of course, had no intention of joining in the chatter.

4th Form spewed out like breath.

Kwakwakwakwang!

Vikir's blow smashed through the throne.

[What the hell, did you really come here to fight?]

But the crown prince was undeterred.

He clapped his hands in genuine panic and tried to calm Vikir down.

[Okay, okay, let's have a conversation!]

“Demons kill....”

[Demons kill, right? I get it, just calm down for a second, I've got something interesting for you to talk about, too!]

The crown prince was still chatty.

Finally, he brought up something that made Vikir stop in his tracks.

[You. I called you.]

“...!”

Vikir's eyes widened slightly.

The crown prince, not missing a beat, spoke up.

[It means I was the one who brought you back.]

Vikir was confused for a moment.

...A regression to kill a demon was caused by a demon?

At first glance, the logic didn't make sense at all.

But the crown prince seemed to be sincere.

[The reason I wanted to regress you to meet with me was because I have something to ask you.]

“Something to ask?”

[Yes.]

The crown prince nodded, and then spoke in a serious tone.

[My brother. Where is he?]

Vikir's eyes narrowed at the question.

The crown prince smiles wryly and continues.

[I thought you might know who and where my brother is, for when I looked into the future, I saw nothing but a dying brother. And you were the last link in his dying bond.]

“....”

[And there was only one scene in the future that brought you back: me waiting in the imperial palace, and you, dragging the coffin. You clearly said, 'I brought your half-body,' so I waited patiently, so that you would come here exactly as I had foreseen, with information about my brother.]

The point is simple.

Andras realized that his brother and Vikir were linked by a bond.

He foresaw that if he brought Vikir back, he would one day bring information about his brother to him.

That was the beginning of all this.

A strange superpower that allows him to see the future.

All descendants of the imperial family, descended from the first emperor who was a prophet and astrologer, have this kind of uncanny ability.

'I'm pretty sure that's what Hohenheim of Magic Tower told me when I played against him in the old university league.'

So there was a good chance that what the crown prince was saying now wasn't a lie.

Vikir thought to himself.

'...He's a good person.'

A strange sound flashed through Vikir's ears.

It was a voice he had heard many times before.

It was a voice that brought back memories of his pre-regression days.

And the moment Vikir heard it, the crown prince's expression changed drastically.

[Yes, the blood of the First Emperor boils in my veins. Oooh- I see it again, my brother's future. My brother's words as he lay dying miserably!]

“....”

[I can tell, you are definitely related to my brother. Who is it? Where is it? Just tell me that].

The crown prince repeatedly asked.

But Vikir didn't answer the questions.

“Why should I answer your questions? What is it you really want?”

[You're a fool. There's no reason for me to seek out my brother].

“Bullshit. I already know that your body is not a typical structure.”

It's impossible to take his word for it.

The crown prince sighed heavily at Vikir's retort.

[You're right, I have two bodies, and it is my task to unite them.]

“....”

[Of course, I didn't expect you to just cooperate with me, so I had a reward in mind for your cooperation].

Then, the Crown Prince spoke up.

[I know because I have seen the future. That you were involved in my brother's final moments before his return. So, all you have to do is tell me the identity and location of my younger brother.]

“....”

[In return, I promise you one thing].

The Crown Prince then held a mirror before Vikir's eyes.

“...!”

Vikir's eyes widened.

Inside was a world after destruction.

The land had been scorched, but the trees had begun to grow again.

It rained, and there were oceans and rivers again.

There were people, though few in number.

They had overcome their miserable past and were rebuilding a happy life, spreading their offspring again.

Among them, of course, were familiar faces that Vikir knew.

They were comrades-in-arms who had crossed the line of fire together.

The original world was in the mirror. The original world that Vikir had lived in, before the regression.

The crown prince said.

[After your death, the world turned out just fine. In the final war, the demons lost and the humans won. The human realm is in ruins, but the survivors are rebuilding it].

“....”

[But it won't be easy, for too many heroes died during the War of Destruction, and now there aren't many people who can handle mana, and they need powerful heroes who can.]

People who can rebuild happiness after the end of the Age of Destruction.

If Vikir could return to his original world, he would be able to make a tremendous contribution to the humanity of his original world.

[I want to know who my brother is. Where he is now. Just tell me that. Then I will send you back to your original world. And I will allow you to see the faces of those you miss. I may even be able to bring some of them back to life, if you name them. It would be a stretch to bring the entire human race back to life, but it's certainly possible].

It was a radical offer.

However.

“I decline.”

Vikir cut off the crown prince's offer with a single word.

The prince didn't even bother to look surprised.

“I am well aware that you are not capable of such a thing. 'Andras. Marquis of Discord'.”

And at the same time.

[...Amazing].

One corner of the crown prince's mouth twitched.

And then.

Kurrrrr!

A black flame engulfed the crown prince's entire body.

Every trace of human skin had been burned, revealing the hideous malice that lurked within.

Chapter 482

The Marquis of Discord (2)

◆

First Corpse Andras, also known as the Marquis of Discord.

His white-feathered wings are sacred at first glance. He has the head of a raven, the eyes of an owl, and the lower half of a wolf.

In his hand he held a single, flaming sword.

A destroyer, always full of dissatisfaction.

A being that hates all that is in harmony, loves disorder, and joins with chaos.

Chaang-

Vikir immediately took out Beelzebub.

But.

[Huhuhu- Why are you so wary? There is no need for that.]

Andras was still smiling.

[I'm just showing my true self so we can have a real conversation. We can't have a conversation if we're hiding things from each other, right?]

“....”

[We both have our own goals, and they don't conflict with each other, so put the sword down].

At this point, Vikir had to admit, he was feeling a bit dumbfounded.

This was the first time he'd ever seen a demon in its true form and not fight.

'...A lesser demon hunter might have been fooled.'

But despite Andras's kindness, Vikir is not fooled.

The reason is that he has memories from before the regression.

The Marquis of Discord.

A demon who rode the battlefield with terrifying force, decapitating countless Alliance heroes.

Even though it was wearing a kind smile in front of him now, it was basically a demon, and the most terrifying one at that.

While Vikir was pondering these things, Andras sighed and opened his mouth as if he was tired.

[This is the first time I've ever shown my true form and not fought, but I can't help it since I want to talk, and I'm at a disadvantage].

“....”

[Now, can we continue what we were talking about earlier?]

Andras's eyes glowed.

[As I said before... the world has settled down a lot since your death, and I can return you to your original world, and maybe even bring back some of the people in your memories].

However.

“There is no way to bring back the dead. Even a demon can't defy Providence.”

Vikir's attitude was equally steadfast.

“Demons kill, that's the way it is.”

Hounds hunt. They don't talk to their prey. That's how he was taught.

So, the conversation ended here, and from then on, the only thing to talk about was the sword.

...Flash!

Vikir unleashed the full force of his sword from the very beginning.

Baskerville 8th Form. His teeth clashed together, creating a bright sun.

Kwazijijik!

The solid jade throne was shattered like tofu.

The words were quite hollow for a place that had been the residence of a Supreme Being for the past few decades.

[So. If it comes to this, is there nothing we can do?]

Andras swung his flaming sword.

A blast of hot flame shot out, aimed at Vikir.

Thwack!

Where Vikir dodged, a deep crack appeared, and it began to melt away.

The Baskerville 8th Form and the flames of Andras clash fiercely.

The atmosphere was shredded, and glowing cracks of mana were forming everywhere.

[It's a shame. It was half the truth.]

Andras smirked as he thrust the tip of his sword into Vikir.

Half-truths and half-lies were the demons' standard tactic when it came to seduction, and Vikir knew it well.

“You guys are basically beings who came to this world to use humans as food. It's absurd to make a deal with something like you.”

[Do you think so? I'm actually the opposite, right?]

“...?”

Vikir frowned.

Then Andras spoke up, as if it were obvious.

[Demons can actually make humans prosper, for the greater good.]

“Bullshit.”

[It is not. You misunderstand our purpose.]

Andras hadn't given up trying to convince Vikir.

[Do you know the animal called 'chicken'?]

“...?”

Who doesn't know chickens?

They are one of the most familiar domesticated animals to humans.

Andras asked again.

[You humans breed, slaughter, and eat chickens. What do the chickens think about this? Are they happy?]

“It can't be.”

[No. They will be happy If you look at it from the perspective of the entire species, not just one individual.]

Andras continued.

[Chickens, for example, were much smaller and weaker animals before humans improved their breed, and probably would not have survived and become extinct if they had stayed that way. Being small and weak, most of them would have been hunted to death by other animals as soon as they emerged from their eggs].

“....”

[But since humans chose chickens as domesticated animals, their population has grown exponentially. They now outnumber any other bird in the world. From a species-wide perspective, isn't that a pretty efficient choice?]

“What are you trying to say?”

Vikir's sword sliced through the air again.

Andras dodged it and moved closer to Vikir's ear.

[Aren't humans also weak, hardworking animals, and how many things make their lives so painful?]

“....”

[War, wild beasts, famine, drought, floods, wildfires, starvation, disease. And then there are the quarrels, the rivalries, the fights, the battles, and the... hardships of trying to find a place to live, of raising children, and of breaking your back to take care of your old parents].

“....”

[A bottomless, never-ending race where the one you want to breed with is always snatched away by a better-looking, better-financed competitor, and you have to fight tooth and nail to do well in all the tests and assessments society demands. But is there always happiness at the end of the race? No, there isn't.]

“....”

[Were you born into this world because you wanted to be? No. You were 'birthed' by your parents into this harsh, lonely world. You are a pitiful animal, forced to be born and forced to die.]

Andras jumped back with a start.

He sat back down on the shattered throne and spread his arms wide.

[At least the lives I mentioned before are better. Most human beings die shortly after birth. Do you know the infant mortality rate of the empire? It's over 80%. In this world where the average adult lifespan is in the mid-30s, most of the babies, even if they are born safely, end up going from orphanage to orphanage. And even then, war, disease, and starvation kill them before they reach the age of ten. Did you see the reality of the orphanage where Dantalian was located? It is said that volunteer work at the orphanage is a required course at noble schools.]

Darkness was gathering around Andras.

Vikir felt an unusual slant and slashed them with his sword.

But the black mist swayed in the wind, enveloping Andras' body even more thickly.

[Humans are pitiful animals indeed. Sad beings who have the intellect but can only recognize deficiencies with it. Lust, appetite, greed, jealousy, anger, sloth, arrogance... The wandering ego, unable to fully satisfy any one need, can only feel inferior, indebted, and defeated in an unequal and unjust society. Occasional happiness is nothing more than a temporary resolution of those dissatisfaction.]

An animal forced to be born and forced to die.

Life is hard when you're young, hard when you're old, hard when you die, always hard and burdensome.

[So I propose].

Andras chuckled.

[The overwhelming majority of humans die of poverty and starvation before the age of 30, or even before the age of 10. Wouldn't you be happier if humans were reduced to demonic livestock instead?]

“Nonsense.”

[You may think so, but do you think the children suffering in the orphanage, or the children who died in the back alleys before they were even allowed to enter the orphanage, think so?]

Andras continued, blocking Vikir's blow.

[Becoming a demon's livestock would guarantee humans a healthy life, averaging over a hundred years old. You can mate and reproduce to your heart's content, live a full and warm life, and live in blissful self-actualization in a world without disease, war, or hunger. And when they reach the age of one hundred, they give their souls to demons and their bodies are slaughtered, just as chickens are divided into No. 7 and No. 8 chickens depending on how long they've been growing. Is this the 'salvation' you speak of, how is it different from God?]

In the thickening darkness, Vikir could feel Andras's gaze studying him.

Its mouth tears red in the darkness.

[There was a being who first made this offer to humans a long time ago].

“....”

[That's 'God'.]

Andras chuckles.

[Of course, that god is far more evil than I am. Slaughter was done the same way as slaughter, but it did not give the promised happiness and peace at all. Even humans who aren't fully grown are captured at will, right? Well, since human farming has been so prosperous up until now, it's understandable that they're behaving like that. But I just don't understand you humans unilaterally upholding contracts even when they are all being broken.]

“What do you want me to do?”

[I want you to understand that I have a good offer for the humans, and that I need to find my brother to make it happen].

After Andras finished speaking, his face changed to that of the First Prince.

The Emperor's eldest son. The rightful heir to the throne.

He is now desperately searching for his half-brother.

[If you help me, I may even make you the head of the system, the emperor, just as the Golding family did in the past...]

But once again, Vikir cut off Andras's offer.

“Where have you learned to be so mean?”

[...What?]

“That logic of yours. Isn't this a trend that was popular during the ancient Warring States Period? It is a logic that would have only worked in the now-vanished 'Demonic Sovereign Country'.”

Vikir raised the tip of his sword.

The tip of his gaze was aimed at Andras.

“Human development desires and upward instincts cannot be confined in a livestock system. No matter how hard you try, they will eventually break through, like an awl in a pocket. That's what humans are.”

The magic sword Beelzebub shoots out an aura with its awl-like tip.

...Boom!

The throne completely collapsed.

Andras emerged from the cloud of dust, wings spread wide.

“Demon Kill.”

[Gee, that's hard to say].

Vikir's sword and Andras's crossed fiercely in the air.

Vikir brushed away the sparks and flames from Andras's sword, thinking to himself.

'...It's fortunate that there is no Asmodeus/'

The magic sword was Andras's signature weapon before the regression.

How surprised Vikir was when he first saw it in Nouvelle Vague.

Asmodeus is now in Kirko's hands, which is a relief.

Vikir burned all the auras at Beelzebub's tip.

Andras, too, was drawing darkness into his grasp, dark enough to swallow Vikir's aura.

[Very well, if you won't make a contract... I'll make you want to do it.]

Those words made Vikir tense up.

He may not have the sword, but the demon's unique supernatural powers are enough to be threatening.

And now, once again, Andras was about to use his unique ability.

[Soon you will be begging for a contract yourself.]

It was a moment of unmistakable power from the pinnacle of the demons who had led the Age of Destruction.

Chapter 483

The Marquis of Discord (3)

◆

Tsutsutsutsutsuts...

Darkness falls.

So dark that if you stretched out your arms, you couldn't even count your fingers.

But even in the darkness, some objects were unusually clear.

A figure rose up in front of Vikir's eyes.

“...Sergeant Janet.”

Vikir muttered, his voice cracking.

The person standing in front of him was unmistakably familiar.

A former comrade in the same unit before he was regressed.

One after another, familiar faces appeared.

Comrades-in-arms he had left behind in the Age of Destruction. Subordinates, comrades, and superiors stood bleeding and glaring at Vikir.

[You won't come back?]

[You could have brought us back].

[Are you abandoning your comrades?]

[Was the world after regression so comfortable?]

[Yes, you can live well after the sacrifices of your comrades-in-arms].

[I trusted only you....]

They shouted at Vikir with tears in their eyes.

A thick cold sweat drips down his face.

The trauma in his heart resurfaced like an evil spirit, tugging at his heartstrings.

[Did you regress to flirting with women?]

[Did you really try your best to prevent the destruction of humanity?]

[And yet you are a demon hunter?]

[You don't even remember the sacrifices of your comrades-in-arms anymore!]

[...Traitor! ...Traitor!]

The ghosts of the past began to wail in a mournful wail.

They opened their mouths wide enough for their lower jaws to fall out, and from within, they drew out their tongues, sharp as spears, and spat out words that flew toward Vikir.

...Peoeog!

One of the tongues became a spear and flew out, stabbing into Vikir's chest.

After that, countless tongues were flying like daggers.

Peopeopeopeog!

Vikir stumbled back, feeling his entire body covered in blood.

A quick check revealed that he was unharmed.

Was that fountain of blood just an illusion?

'Andras specializes in playing with the minds of his opponents. One should never be fooled.'

Vikir desperately tried to ignore the spears and daggers that pierced his mind.

Then.

Vikir turned around and saw something else this time.

[Who are you to refuse a contract at will?]

[You don't listen to us?]

[You were at least born into a noble family].

[I was buried in a garbage can as soon as I was born.]

[I froze to death in a coin locker on a magic train].

[Eung-ae- euaang-]

There stood the children who had died in the orphanage.

Children who didn't live long enough to live, or who died as soon as they were born.

Beings forced to be born by their parents.

They were casting resentful glances at Vikir.

And there was one girl standing at the front of the group.

[Brother. No, Mister].

Nymphet.

The one who had died so long ago, the one who had become his first sense of guilt since the Regression.

Nymphet turned to Vikir.

[You speak well of the human desire for development and upward instinct..., Are you qualified to say something like that?]

“...That.”

Vikir opened his mouth without realizing it.

But Nimpet didn't wait for it.

[It sticks out like an awl in your pocket? Hohoho – you mean my tongue?]

The ghost with Nymphpet's face chuckled hysterically, then spat out a long spear-like tongue from its mouth.

...Puck!

Nymphet's words, lodged in Vikir's chest, were sharp and cold as hell.

Just like this world.

Then, the remaining comrades from the Age of Destruction and all the children who had died in this world surrounded Vikir.

[How dare you, you unworthy bastard!]

[Hang him! Hang him!]

[Throw stones!]

[Kill him! We must kill him!]

At the same time, the daggers continue to strike.

...Peog! ...peog! ...peog! ...peoeog!

It was not only piercing his mind, but also his body.

It's not a metaphor or analogy, it's really hurting.

“...!”

Vikir drew his Beelzebub long and sharp.

Kwakwakwakwang!

Baskerville 8th Form. The stage reached through extreme practical experience. The final destination of the living.

After this, it is the realm of the dead.

It is a realm beyond the reach of mortal life.

Vikir bared his eight teeth, scattering the darkness around him.

But the stings of the tongues continued to fly, embedding themselves in Vikir's body.

'Where are you?'

Vikir continued to run through the blinding darkness.

Andras's voice echoed in his ears.

[You will die here, but if you accept the deal, even now, I can make it all go away.]

The voice sounded so sweet and soothing.

It felt like all you had to do was take the outstretched hand and everything would be fine.

Like the promised salvation, the flower path, for mankind.

...But.

Peoeog!

Vikir stood steadfast despite the barrage of daggers piercing his chest.

The surroundings have already become miserable with blood flowing down and spears and daggers stuck on the floor.

It is the thorny path of asceticism itself.

The flowery path promised before his eyes was in stark contrast to the thorny path I had walked so far.

[Are you scared? Are you afraid? You will be, because that's what humans are like. Well, even now...]

Andras's voice stuck like honey in his ears.

But.

“Demon.”

The aura Vikir emitted grew even more ferocious and wild.

“Kill!”

The crimson half-moon slashed through the black clouds around him.

Vikir. The scarred hound stood on the thorny path, gasping for breath.

The air around him was thick with blood, and his heated body scorched the air.

“I am not afraid of death.”

Vikir had already died once.

Twice, if you count his experience in the Hell Tree.

The end of a line he'd crossed countless times before. And now this.

“I've been decapitated by the guillotine and I've taken my own life. It's not a metaphor, it's a real experience.”

A man who has experienced death so many times that others have never experienced it.

An anomaly who had actually experienced death and was still breathing right here.

Vikir moved his hand and raised his sword.

The sword that had always guided him through the countless deaths he had faced.

Vikir swung the sword.

Perhaps it would be the last Sword Form he would ever use.

Eight trajectories began to glow like guiding stars.

However.

Peopeopeopeopeopeopeopeopeog!

There was nothing to be done about the countless tongue stings from the darkness.

Vikir fell to his knees, spewing fountains of blood.

“....”

Vikir shook his head, unable to utter a groan.

The darkness cleared before him. Andras appeared, clicking his tongue.

[Too much rigidity will break you].

Andras gently touched Vikir's bloodied head with his toe.

[Is he dead? Hmm – is his mind dead as well? Alas, I must have misjudged my power control. Where should I look for the Second Prince then?]

Andras tugged at his hair, his expression gradually turning to irritation.

...Peopeong! ...Bang!

A bombastic sound from far away. An earthquake that traveled through the floor.

The battle outside the Imperial Palace seemed to be getting more and more intense.

[I'll have to clean up the mess outside first].

Andras frowned in annoyance.

Then, as Andras was about to slowly turn away from Vikir.

“ ...Demon.”

There was a groan that sounded like a gut being ripped out.

Vikir lifted his unfocused eyes to stare at Andras.

“Kill.”

[Hahahahaha- You're like a bloody dog.]

Andras laughed at the absurdity of it all.

But regardless, Vikir could only move slowly, his body stiff with exhaustion.

...One. ...two. ...three. ...four. ...five. ...six. ...seven. ...eight.

His mana is drained, and not even a faint aura emanates from him.

His hands are moving, but the teeth can't be felt on his tips.

Just before reaching the threshold of death, the now familiar dry and crumbly sensation was repeated eight times.

Andras, of course, does not care for Vikir's final act.

And because of that, Andras missed one thing.

...Nine.

The trajectory of the 9th, the one that followed the 8th.

And finally.

Pas-

A frighteningly intense burst of light began to emanate from the tip of Vikir's Beelzebub.

[...Hmm?]

Andras turned his head.

There, there was a burst of light so bright that it burned out his pupils, who were accustomed to darkness, in an instant.

[Eeh!?]

His tightly closed eyes burned.

A thick cloud of pungent smoke was billowing out through his eyelids.

One. Two. Three. Four. Five. Six. Seven. Eight.

...And Nine.

When Andras opened his eyes, the tiny dots of light had transformed into a gigantic ball of light that filled his entire field of vision.

-[Only those who step into the realm of the Supreme, and continue to run without resting with the same mindset as when they first picked up the sword will gain something.]]

Cane Corso once said of the 8th Form.

-[You will probably not attain this in your lifetime, for the realm of the 9th Form lies beyond the threshold of death].

The 6th Form.

A state that can only be reached by transcending all emotions.

The 7th Form.

A state that can only be attained by reclaiming emotions that have been abandoned.

The 8th Form.

A state of mind that can only be attained by grasping a sword and fighting through a series of desperate battles.

And the 9th Form.

An incomprehensible zone at the core of the highest realms that only those who have truly experienced death can ascend to.

“....”

Vikir was staring blankly at the nine glowing trails beyond his fading vision.

Across the swirling darkness, he heard the voice of Cane Corso, a voice he had once heard.

-[This realm defies normal human understanding, empathy, comprehension, faith, common sense, probability, and causality. No being who has not experienced death can ever set foot here.]

-[Ah, it looks like you have a lot of regrets in life. But. You're not old enough to have even contemplated death yet].

-[You are not yet ready].

Words that, at the time, he didn't understand.

...But now, for some reason, it seemed to make sense to him.

As an anomaly who had experienced death so many times despite being alive, he had witnessed countless other deaths that he had missed at his fingertips.

And a certain realization that came unexpectedly at the crossroads of life and death had opened a new gate, one that lay somewhere beyond the other side.

Vikir stretched out his hand and peered into the world beyond the gate.

For a brief moment, a fleeting glimpse, a dot of light scattered into countless fragments.

The upper level of the Supreme realm seen in such a short period of time.

The landscape he saw with his mind's eye was burned into his retina, leaving a mark.

And as he absentmindedly moved his hand along the trace, it soon became the trajectory of a cluster of living stars.

...Flash!

Finally, the 9th tooth began to fully reveal itself.